mune no naka de zawameiteru nami no hontou no imi wo
I pondered over the sound of waves astir in my heart
hizashi ni saegirarete watashi wa mada shiranai
though the rays of the sun blinded me from the truth.
ano koro egaita enikki mitai
Just like the pictures I drew in my diary as a child,
subete ga irozuki hajimeru hora
everything around us is being immersed in color.
manatsu no sora to umi no aosa ni
I try to close my eyes and hide
mabushikute me wo tojite mo
from the brilliant blue sea and sky,
watashi no kokoro no hashikko wo
but your voice always finds its way
tsukande hanasanai kimi no koe wa
right into the corners of my heart and holds on tight.
kore ga koi kana
I guess I'm in love.
Episode 6
Punch
Kakeru-kun.
Oh, good morning.
Want a cup of tea or something?
You should take a break.
Morning.
Did I wake you?
No.
You were here?
I was looking for you.
I've always been here.
I guess I'm still a bit sleepy.
There's a line in an
old movie that goes,
"If a girl is sleeping on her stomach, that means she's in love."
Any mother worth her salt
would know already, though.
Still,
I bet there's no movie about being able to see what lies ahead in your love life.
You know what'll happen?
N-No, I don't,
but what if I did?
Would that make my love life uneventful?
Well, I'm not really sure I get what you're saying,
but doesn't that just mean
that you can enjoy it twice?
Mom, that's so beautiful.
I mean, even if you knew something unpleasant was coming up,
you'd be able to prepare yourself for it.
So it's win-win!
Enjoy it twice...
That sounds exciting!
If I completed a really great project, I'd be able to live it again,
and if I could do the same with love...
If I could do the same with love...
No!
What's wrong?!
I'm fine!
There was a bug... I think.
A bug? That's all it was?
We've raised her to be a good girl,
but I guess she's hit that age.
"That age"?!
Hello? Touko?
H-Hello.
It's me, Okikura. You free at the moment?
Yes!
You never got around to asking me that favor, so I was thinking—
Um, I'll, uh... I'll call you back later!
I hung up on him.
What's wrong?
She hung up on me.
The girl who came
over the other day?
I'll make some coffee.
What have you done now?
There's no way I'll be able to "enjoy" my first kiss twice!
No way!
My heart wouldn't be able to take it!
Okikura-kun?
I'm sorry for hanging up on you—
Sorry, it's Hiro, actually.
Hiro-kun
You okay?
Anyway, I wanted to talk to you about today's meet-up.
You still there?
Hey.
Breakfast is ready!
Coming!
God damn it.
I can't stay like this forever.
How am I supposed to face her?
Morning, sleepyhead.
Didn't you hear Mom calling for you?
I was changing.
Oh? Anyway, come down for breakfast before it gets cold.
Hey...
Yeah?
I have a few things to take care of
before coming to Kazemichi today.
Okay, sure.
To be honest, I asked you out here earlier than the others.
Me? Why?
The other day, I—
Oh, is this about you visiting Sacchan?
I think she wanted to tell me that you were over,
but she felt too shy about it to say so.
Y-You think?
Well, I'd appreciate it if you kept it a secret from Yukinari and Yanagi-san for now.
Huh?
But everyone al—
I want to tell them myself.
Right, sure! Of course you do.
It's quite hot today, isn't it?
It really is.
Coming right up.
I confessed to him.
Wow, you're so brave, Yana-chan.
Man, I love how you're so dense about these things all the time.
Huh?
How're things lately?
I can't stand this heat.
Yo!
Anyway, let's get down to business.
What about Sachi?
Yep, today's meeting is all about Sacchan!
Huh?
We're planning a surprise for her?
That's right!
She couldn't make it to the
fireworks display last time, right?
So I was thinking it'd be nice if
we could organize one just for her.
Well?
Sure!
That sounds great!
Shouldn't we be studying for our finals
instead of going out all the time like this?
Oh well.
I'll let Sacchan know.
Sorry, just a sec!
Hello?
Couldn't she just pick it up here?
There are some calls you can't take in public.
So who is it?
David. Who else?
Hey!
Oh? If they're that close,
why don't we invite him too?
You mean, get Touko to ask him?
Or I could just ask him myself.
I'll do it.
Huh?
I know where he lives. I think.
But why you?
Sorry about that!
Touko-san,
we were just talking about how we should invite David-kun too.
What?! Wh-Why?
It just kinda happened.
Ehh?!
Yes?
This is Imi.
I'm Okikura-kun's—
Gimme a sec.
I'm surprised you found my house.
Wasn't hard. Your name's well known around here.
Want to come in?
I'd rather we talked outside,
if that's fine with you.
I'm a certified idiot.
Hello. Okikura residence.
Hello. This is Fukami speaking.
Is Oki—I mean, is Kakeru-kun home?
He's not here at the moment, actually.
I see...
Imi-kun wouldn't happen to be a friend of yours, would he?
Yes, he is.
I didn't want to bring you out here, to be honest.
Why did you, then? What's the problem?
Well, sometimes we just have to do things we don't want to.
Right.
So, what's up?
Our group's going to organize some fireworks.
You're invited.
I see.
You didn't want to invite me, but you were in a position where you had to?
Right.
In that case, I'll decline.
I wouldn't want to cause
any trouble by attending.
You've caused all kinds of trouble just by coming to this town.
Have I?
You doing this on purpose?
To some extent, yes.
You having fun?
Of course not.
That's not why I'm doing it.
Just like you, I can't only do the things I want to.
The hell is that supposed to mean?
What's going on between you and Touko?
Do you have any idea how she feels?
She hasn't told me anything.
Not that I'd be obligated
to share it with you.
Hey...
Where do you think you're going?!
Did Takayama confess to you?
I didn't think it'd take you this long to give her your reply—
I don't think we should
invite Kakeru-kun to this one!
What happened to you?
Let's just say it hurt.
How did...
Wait...
No, it couldn't be!
Yuki-kun?
Yeah.
That's horrible.
No, I said something I shouldn't have.
What?
I'm guessing Takayama told him how she feels.
Could I have done something to hurt Yuki-kun?
Who knows.
It's been difficult to know
anything for sure these days.
We all chipped in to buy these!
I love sparklers.
Sparkling
Fireworks Show!
Their dazzling
lights are
captivating!
Their dazzling
lights are
captivating!
You'll have fun
with everyone!
Well, I'm glad we bought a bunch!
I mean, this is all about you this time round!
Sparkling
Fireworks Show!
Their dazzling
lights are
captivating!
Their dazzling
lights are
captivating!
You'll have fun
with everyone!
Sparkling
Fireworks Show!
Their dazzling
lights are
captivating!
Their dazzling
lights are
captivating!
You'll have fun
with everyone!
Sparkling
Fireworks Show!
Their dazzling
lights are
captivating!
Their dazzling
lights are
captivating!
You'll have fun
with everyone!
Sparkling
Fireworks Show!
Their dazzling
lights are
captivating!
Their dazzling
lights are
captivating!
You'll have fun
with everyone!
Sparkling
Fireworks Show!
Their dazzling
lights are
captivating!
Their dazzling
lights are
captivating!
You'll have fun
with everyone!
Sparkling
Fireworks Show!
Their dazzling
lights are
captivating!
Their dazzling
lights are
captivating!
You'll have fun
with everyone!
Sparkling
Fireworks Show!
Their dazzling
lights are
captivating!
Their dazzling
lights are
captivating!
You'll have fun
with everyone!
Sparkling
Fireworks Show!
Their dazzling
lights are
captivating!
Their dazzling
lights are
captivating!
You'll have fun
with everyone!
Sparkling
Fireworks Show!
Their dazzling
lights are
captivating!
Their dazzling
lights are
captivating!
You'll have fun
with everyone!
Sparkling
Fireworks Show!
Their dazzling
lights are
captivating!
Their dazzling
lights are
captivating!
You'll have fun
with everyone!
Sparkling
Fireworks Show!
Their dazzling
lights are
captivating!
Their dazzling
lights are
captivating!
You'll have fun
with everyone!
But y'know, this—
was supposed to be a surprise!
I appreciate the sentiment, regardless.
Welcome... back?
What's wrong?
He won't be coming for the fireworks.
Huh?
What happened? Tell me!
Nothin'.
The two of you, fighting over Touko,
and what am I?!
Sorry.
I don't want an apology.
I know that I can't leave things the way they are right now.
I'll work something out.
Want to come over to my place?
Huh?
My dad's home too.
Um, sure.
Oh, these are all albums of mine.
Well, of course. I'm your biggest fan.
Shall I play something for you?
What's wrong?
That'd be great.
It's my mom.
Please do.
I'll head home, okay?
Touko.
Have I finally found it?
Your mom's a pianist?
Wait, where are we going?
I can calm down when I'm here.
I know what you mean.
What's your mother like?
Let's see.
She doesn't stay in one place for long.
I can't be sure if it's because of her job
or if that's just the way she is.
She's a really active person, huh?
When I was a child, I used to think
everything my mother did was justified.
I guess I was overly fond of her.
No way!
I've felt that way before too.
I've tried calling you about it twice now.
It's about time you ask me that favor.
Sorry I dragged it out for so long.
Sacchan's going to the hospital again.
She told me that it's just for a checkup, so there's no need for concern,
but I saw a vision of her being hospitalized, and...
You're worried about her.
Yeah.
Oh, sorry!
Hello? Yuki-kun?
Hey, Touko.
Sorry, but I have a few things I need to get off my chest.
Like how you hit Okikura-kun, right?
You saw him?
I'm with him right now.
Huh?
Come to the schoolyard, and we'll settle this.
You're on my side, aren't you, Touko?
Yana-chan? Stop Yuki-kun!
If the two of them meet up, there's going to be trouble!
I apologize for punching you.
My bad.
Yana-chan...
If you really mean that,
let's settle this; man-to-man.
As luck would have it; there's a track here too.
A race?
You, against me?!
At least you'll treat a race seriously.
If you win, I won't see Touko again.
If I win, Touko is mine.
You have Takayama. I won't hold it against you if you lose on purpose.
I bet you're not going to race anyway!
I don't know what you're up to,
but whatever it is, you're making me sick!
Let's go.
Don't!
The Myth of Sisyphus
Camus
Downtown Bookstore
What? We're putting off the fireworks?
I wonder if it didn't suit David-kun's schedule.
Would you like to hold
a mini fireworks party instead?
Hinode Beach
High School
Was Yana-chan right about what she said?
Yeah. I wasn't going to race him.
I wouldn't have stood a chance.
Then why?
What was I trying to accomplish by picking a fight with him? I'm not sure I know myself.
That's terrible!
That doesn't explain anything.
Yeah, you're right.
I guess I was hoping you'd stick up for me, though.
What?
What are these fragments of the future to you, Touko?
A...
A means of preparing so I can enjoy things twice?
You really are something.
The reason I call them "fragments of the future"
is because I believe they're like pieces of one's self.
Pieces that I need to make my incomplete self whole.
But those pieces were nothing more than whispers and murmurs.
At least, until I met you.
And now I'm beginning to realize
that what I'd been yearning for
wasn't just some random pieces,
but something more solid and real.
You mean that...
All I hear now...
is your voice.
All the visions I see are of you, too.
Have I... finally found it?
katachi no nai sekai ni iki wo fukikomu
Take a deep breath and shape this world
mata atashi ga umareru
and bring me back to life again.
barabara ni chirakashita
Hearts are fragile like glass
kokoro wa waremono dakara
and shatter into pieces when they're broken.
sotto tsutsunde kimi ni okurou
I gingerly wrapped those of mine and sent them to you.
hitotsu dake erande misete
Let me know which shard you've kept close.
nande mo nai you na hibi no kakera
Memories of our days together calmly pass us by.
wasurarenu mono to tsui ni aru no wa
There's rarely ever a day we wouldn't look back on.
nando mo daitatte itsu no ma ni ka
And before we knew it,
surinukete shimau mono da
all our moments together had long slipped into the past.
toumei na garasu no mukou bon'yari to
The scenery I caught but a glimpse of
sukashite mieta keshiki wa mada
when I peered through the looking glass
atashi mo shiranai kimi mo shiranai sekai kana
was of a world yet unknown to both you and me
kira hikari wo sorashita
that shined ever so brightly out of our reach.
I don't like David.
You can't change the future.
And what are we?
I'm going home.
Episode 7
Bicycle
Don't turn into
someone unpleasant!