It's... It's nothing.
Touko!
Huh?
What's wrong, Onee-chan?
Touko!
Touko-san?!
Are you all right?
I'll let them in.
Don't go.
It's all my fault.
No.
I wanted to hear your mother's piano too.
I didn't hear any fragments.
But whatever you saw
made you lose consciousness.
Does this mean that our
experiment was a success?
Probably.
But I also put you in serious danger.
I'm totally fine, though!
And besides...
Whenever I'm around people,
I only get them involved in my problems.
Touko?
Is everything okay?
I want to stay here a bit longer.
Eh?
O-Onee-chan?
Maybe it'd be best if you
rested here for a while longer.
I want to make some more
glass beads when I'm back.
All right.
Final Episode
Shooting Star
Are you sure we shouldn't have brought her home with us?
Of course.
Still... I wonder what happened to her.
Yes, what indeed?
She's quite mature now, after all.
What?
Are you saying that I'm still just a kid?
Don't worry, Hina. You'll be an adult soon.
Before you even know it.
Oh? Another piece?
Yes, please!
I'll head home right afterward.
Are you sure you'll be okay?
Yeah.
Excuse me, um...
Could you play a really dramatic one?
All right, then.
I'm not afraid.
Why should I be? Those aren't glimpses of the future.
But still, Kakeru-kun is sure to be...
He's sure to be gone.
Here you go.
I must say, I never thought I'd see you
all gathered here to order some Mandheling.
I'm kinda nervous all of a sudden. I wonder why?
Yeah, I feel uneasy.
It's bitter.
I bet it'd be brighter
if Touko-san were here.
We used to meet up at this place every so often by chance.
I should give her a call.
What's up?
I'd prefer for us to meet by chance again.
You can sound pretty cool when you want to.
Yeah, sometimes.
Sorry. I went and stirred things up.
I'll tell you and Sachi about it too, Hiro.
You don't have to.
Huh?
Everyone has their secrets.
J-Just a few small ones, though.
I guess it's because we're all
here together, drinking coffee.
Morning.
Good morning.
Huh? Where's Onee-chan?
Dunno.
She's already in the studio again?
Hina.
Hm?
She came in here, panicking about her unfinished summer homework.
Leave her to it, okay?
Fine.
Oh, Hina. It says here there'll be a meteor shower tonight.
That takes me back to another
meteor shower we had in the past.
Your mother told me that
she wanted to see the stars,
so I made up my mind
to propose to her that night.
Dad, your newspaper's in my way.
Kakeru,
have you decided what you'll do?
Yeah.
You're a grown man now.
You get to do what you want to,
and I'll be supporting you the best I can.
You were really strict
with me back in middle school.
Middle schoolers are kids,
but high schoolers are adults.
I believed in that weird distinction.
Something like that, anyway.
Oh yeah, I've noticed you're still hiking.
Yeah, but I don't really climb up.
I walk around the foothills for half a day or so.
You weren't keen at all when
I first invited you to come with me.
Yeah. Well, I am now.
It's been a while since we've gone together.
You think you'd be able
to keep up with me, Dad?
Is that a challenge?
Honey, come give me a hand!
I'll answer it.
Thanks.
Yes?
Takayama?
sunflower
bubble powder
fireworks
flower parts
bam!
Let's take a break here.
I heard from Hina-chan that your mother
held a piano concert at your home.
I wouldn't call it a "concert".
Just a little gathering of sorts.
You should invite me too for your next one.
Takayama—
Yanagi.
You can call me Yanagi.
Do you like classical music, Yanagi?
I listen to it a lot, actually.
I love the black tea that you make, Mom.
Thank you, dear.
Say, Touko, whenever you
get blinded by a bright light,
you don't happen to see
something hazy, do you?
Eh?
When I was young, I would see
things like that from time to time,
and at one point I thought they might be glimpses into my own future.
But as it turned out, I was wrong.
My actual future was filled with things I'd never even dreamed of.
I still wonder what those visions were.
Do they give you direction?
I dunno.
But it's the best I can do for the moment.
Of course.
You've gotta make the most of now.
Yup!
I'm calling in your promise.
I'll be happy to remind you if you've forgotten.
No, I remember.
There's only one promise I made with you.
Wanna join us?
You can tell me later.
I got the gist of it from Sachi.
I see.
The incident at the beach that led to our promise
and Touko's fainting a few days ago
were both my fault.
How much of that am I
supposed to believe to be true?
I don't think I can bring myself to accept every word you say.
Believe whatever you want, but it's all true.
It's also true that I needed Touko to be with me.
However, if I didn't exist, Touko wouldn't have been hurt the way she was.
I hurt Touko.
I can't even begin to imagine what it was that Touko saw.
It's not always good, though.
To come to a realization, that is.
What?
Do you mean Imi Yukinari?
Yes, I do.
Even if he doesn't say a word,
I know exactly what's on his mind.
That sounds like quite a nuisance indeed.
Also...
Kakeru, are you going to disappear?
It kinda feels like you will.
I'll be leaving now!
Take care!
Where's she going
this late in the evening?
No idea.
She seemed really pumped, though.
Where's Onee-chan off to?
My, everyone's so worried about Onee-chan.
Kakeru-kun?
Touko.
Do you mind if I join you?
Not at all.
There's going to be a meteor shower tonight.
It'd be nice if we could see it as clearly as the fireworks.
I hope we'll be able to see
the fireworks together next time.
This cloudy sky doesn't look promising.
Winter fireworks...
Huh? Winter?
In the fragment of the future I saw,
everyone was going to see the fireworks in winter.
And you went to see them?
Yes.
I watched them alone.
What about everyone else?
They didn't recognize me.
I see.
You watched them by yourself.
That was the first time
I'd watched fireworks alone.
That was my sudden but
foreseeable loneliness, I guess.
I would have liked to have seen those fireworks with you.
You were there too, Kakeru-kun.
With everyone.
Was that "me" having fun?
Yes, very much so.
That's a relief.
What are these "fragments of the future", after all?
That's probably not the best name for them at this point.
My mom...
Huh?
Actually, never mind.
What?
I was just thinking you'd started saying "never mind" again.
But you say that whenever it's about
something important to you, don't you?
Am I that easy to read?
Not really.
I see.
You may be right.
Something important to me...
That day, at the fireworks display, I saw you, Kakeru-kun.
Was that just a coincidence?
No, I don't think so.
I refuse to believe it could be.
You saw me that day because
you wanted to see me.
That wasn't the future I saw.
It was something that hadn't happened yet,
but which would happen eventually...
Hang on, isn't that the same thing?
Do you think it is?
Um... no.
Then, it's not the same.
I wanted to see you, Kakeru-kun.
I wanted to see you, Touko.
And that's the reason we did?
I'm sure the bright lights and sounds of
the fireworks at that moment made it happen.
It sure was loud and bright, huh?
But why us?
Even in the world with the winter fireworks,
I wasn't able to do anything for you.
I feel like all I accomplished was to
understand a little more about how you feel.
But I didn't get to...
I didn't get to do anything for you.
You've accomplished more than enough.
You really think so?
I'm glad I got to meet you, in this town.
I'm glad you came to this town, Kakeru-kun.
We can't see the stars...
Oh, I know!
We can make these our stars.
You made all of those?
Yup!
That's amazing.
Ready, set...
Shooting stars...
Yeah.
Can you see them too, Kakeru-kun?
This year's meteor shower will be unusually active.
The Kappa Cygnids meteor shower reaches its peak tonight,
but unfortunately, due to cloudy skies across all regions—
Tonight's Forecast
Maizuru
Obama
Tsuruga
Fukui
Hikone
Ono
Kanazawa
Tonight's Forecast
Maizuru
Obama
Tsuruga
Fukui
Hikone
Ono
Kanazawa
I wanted to see them, too.
Same here.
I can see them!
Oh?
You can?
That was...
a beautiful proposal.
Right from the moment we met—our first date,
everything—you were so unbelievably earnest
that I completely fell for you.
Why is only Jonathan called "Jonathan"?
Yuki-kun, are you all right?
The late summer heat
hasn't gotten to you, has it?
No!
All the other chickens are
named after philosophers!
What?!
Then what about "Jonathan"?
The name of an adventurer, maybe?
Hang on, you've been sketching them this whole time and you didn't know?
Right...
Our summer break will be over soon.
From here on,
I hope that I'll be able to handle
whatever the future has in store for me!
Man, you never change.
Or have you?
nami no oto wo kikinagara aruite yuku
I listen to the sound of the waves as I walk.
mada saki no koto nante kangaeta koto nakute
Thoughts about the things ahead of us never crossed my mind.
He's gotten back into it lately.
Oh, here he comes!
What?
Huh?
Why?
warai atteru "ima" dake ga subete datta
All that mattered to me was the time we spent laughing together.
It's all over.
Hina!
Where's Hina?
Hey, Hina, tell us what's going on!
fuki nuketeru oi kaze ni yobare furi kaeru to
I turn around as the wind from behind sweeps past me,
Hina!
itsumono keshiki ga fui ni chigatte mieta
and the scenery in front of me suddenly looks different.
There's the focus knob.
konna natsu wa nido to konaitte kizuita no
I realize a summer like this will never come again.
I can see it.
Oh!
toumei na hitomi no oku wazuka ni hajiketa niji no kakera
An array of colors burst and shatter in the distance beyond these clear beads.
I think "Touko" is a beautiful name.
R-Right.
But I think "Hiro" is a beautiful name too.
C-Can I help you with anything?
kagayaki dasu shinkirou no mukou gawa
They shine brightly in the mirage on the other side.
You're a customer too for today.
Oh, welcome!
te wo nobase ba ashita ga hora,
See, if you just try to reach out,
Hey, why're you so late?!
kawaru yo
you can change your future.
Historical Atlus
Introduction
To Literature
Theories on
Finite Groups
The World of
Contemporary
Literature
Goethe
Poetry
Anthology
Journals on
Natural Science
Journals on Geology
Map of the
Geographical Botany
Is she still going to make it?
Huh?
Unlike you, Sis, this young man's summer break is over.
You're up already. How strange.
Something exciting happen to you?
Could the fragile glasses girl be back at school?
Well, good for you.
How about a celebratory ride in my car?
The only way I'm going to be
late to school is if you drive me there.
Tee-hee!
I guess all that jogging paid off.
I'll be going now!
I'm off!
Okay!
Watch out for cars, girls!
Morning.
Touko!
mune no naka de zawameiteru nami no hontou no imi wo
I pondered over the sound of waves astir in my heart
hizashi ni saegirarete watashi wa mada shiranai
though the rays of the sun blinded me from the truth.
ano koro egaita enikki mitai
Just like the pictures I drew in my diary as a child,
subete ga irozuki hajimeru hora
everything around us is being immersed in color.
manatsu no sora to umi no aosa ni
I try to close my eyes and hide
mabushikute me wo tojite mo
from the brilliant blue sea and sky,
watashi no kokoro no hashikko wo
but your voice always finds its way
tsukande hanasanai kimi no koe wa
right into the corners of my heart and holds on tight.
kore ga koi kana
I guess I'm in love.