Nervous?
Not really.
It's just a track meet, after all.
Yeah. Just a track meet.
mune no naka de zawameiteru nami no hontou no imi wo
I pondered over the sound of waves astir in my heart
hizashi ni saegirarete watashi wa mada shiranai
though the rays of the sun blinded me from the truth.
ano koro egaita enikki mitai
Just like the pictures I drew in my diary as a child,
subete ga irozuki hajimeru hora
everything around us is being immersed in color.
manatsu no sora to umi no aosa ni
I try to close my eyes and hide
mabushikute me wo tojite mo
from the brilliant blue sea and sky,
watashi no kokoro no hashikko wo
but your voice always finds its way
tsukande hanasanai kimi no koe wa
right into the corners of my heart and holds on tight.
kore ga koi kana
I guess I'm in love.
Episode 5
Hinode Bridge
He's smiling.
Get set!
Shiomi Stadium
Stadium Guide Map
Bleachers
Yo!
It's been a while.
How you been?
Not bad, I guess.
How'd it go?
It's hard when you're out of practice, huh?
Sorry!
競技場案内図
Stadium Guide Map
Bleachers
It's her!
Lucky guy.
Hi, I'm Matsuda. I run sprints.
I'm Nagai. I do hurdles.
I'm Hyouno.
Uh, hi. I'm Yukinari's—
Never mind them, Yanagi. Let's go.
Wow, they're on a first-name basis?
Yukinari, don't tire yourself out too much, okay?
Same with you guys.
If you hold it in for too long, it'll affect your performance.
The fireworks display was really good, y'know.
Really? Wish I could've gone.
I'll take you next year.
They looked so huge up close!
You sure you should've said that back there?
What if they start spreading rumors?
Let them say what they want.
I have something I need to do,
so I'll see you later.
Excuse me.
Is Hiro-kun out again today?
He's on a date, as I recall.
Sorry to ask, but with whom?
That I don't know.
Right. Of course.
He wouldn't tell you that much.
Touko-san, wasn't it?
Yes?
You've become even more ladylike recently.
Might summer be the season of love?
Eh?!
Oh, I beg your pardon. That was inappropriate.
No, it's all right.
Please accept some cookies on
the house as an apology for my silly jest.
Oh? Um, sure.
Thank you!
All Contacts
Edit
Information
Sacchan
Cellphone
Memo
Message
Add to Favorites
He wouldn't, right?
But then, who?
Who?
Thanks for the other day.
You frantically ran after me just to thank me?
I wanted to have a talk with you.
I'm sure you've had these moments too.
Like pouring your heart out to a bust in an art room
to sort out your feelings and whatnot.
Not really.
Oh? Touko said she had.
So it's fine for me to just sit here and listen, right?
Hello?
Is Sacchan at home?
Oh, Touko-chan's here.
What? Were you expecting her today?
Yeah.
Touko-chan?
Can I come in?
Hang on. I'll be right down.
Come in.
Sorry to impose.
Not at all.
Is something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Come inside.
Thanks.
It's probably my mother.
I should say hello!
You can say hi later.
Yuki hurt his leg a couple of
summers ago, and he's still in rehab.
Today, we had a joint track meet between the junior and high schools around here.
He didn't do so well.
Y'know, Hiro-kun...
Hm?
Apparently he went on a date today.
When I heard, I figured it would be with you,
but since you're here with me right now...
Sacchan, are you going out with Hiro-kun?
He was with me until just now.
Eh?!
Today's just been full of surprises.
I had no idea the two of you were together, though.
You're misunderstanding what I said.
I didn't say that the two of us were together.
We were just here together, reading books.
Right, of course!
That's all it really is.
How about you, Touko-chan?
Are you still seeing that boy?
Well, about that, actually...
Okikura-kun seems unfriendly on the outside,
but I think he's actually a nice guy.
I see. He is pretty good-looking.
No, that's not what I was getting at!
That's not it.
I'm going to the hospital again soon.
Huh?
It's just for some checkups,
so it's nothing to be worried about.
I see.
And once I'm out, there's somewhere I want to go together with you.
Oh, where?
It's a secret for now.
If only I could see the future.
I think Yuki's really anxious.
I guess everyone wishes they could.
You're really playing along?
Well, I wouldn't want to see it.
Hello, Okikura residence.
Hi, Okikura-kun?
It's me, Fukami.
Um, could we meet up? I need to ask you a favor.
Um—
Yeah, I know.
I've been thinking about what you told me the other night.
Er—
Uh, Kakeru's not home at the moment, and...
Sorry, this is his father speaking.
Huh?
Once he's back, I'll let him know you called.
Eh?
Ehh?!
Sorry!
B-Bye!
I'm home!
Welcome back.
Are you always like this?!
Oh? What's this?
It's nothing! Forget about it!
I was just thinking I should read books as well once in a while, y'know?
So this is yours, huh?
Yep, that's right!
The Myth of Sisyphus
Camus
Downtown Bookshop
The Myth of Sisyphus
Camus
Downtown Bookshop
The Myth of Sisyphus
Camus
Downtown Bookshop
The Myth of Sisyphus
Camus
Downtown Bookshop
The Myth of Sisyphus
Camus
Downtown Bookshop
Like hell it is.
The Myth of Sisyphus
Camus
Downtown Bookshop
The Myth of Sisyphus
Camus
Downtown Bookshop
The Myth of Sisyphus
Camus
Downtown Bookshop
The Myth of Sisyphus
Camus
Downtown Bookshop
As if you'd ever be reading someone like Camus.
The Myth of Sisyphus
Camus
Downtown Bookshop
The Myth of Sisyphus
Camus
Downtown Bookshop
The Myth of Sisyphus
Camus
Downtown Bookshop
The Myth of Sisyphus
Camus
Downtown Bookshop
Really? The Myth of Sisyphus?
The Myth of Sisyphus
Camus
Downtown Bookshop
The Myth of Sisyphus
Camus
Downtown Bookshop
The Myth of Sisyphus
Camus
Downtown Bookshop
Don't make me laugh.
Oh, that fragile girl with the glasses?
Hello? Fukami speaking.
Hey. Sorry, I was out before.
Um, it's okay. Actually, I—
My dad said, "Sorry for troubling the young lady."
I'm sorry too.
Don't worry. It was my mistake in the first place.
How about you come over now?
Huh?
My dad says if you have the time,
he'd like to cook you lunch to make up for it.
Lunch?
He's gotten pretty good at it
from living on his own for so long.
Well, but...
You wanted to see me, didn't you?
I did, but...
I have something I need to talk to you about too.
Huh?
Do you know where I live?
No... I don't.
Welcome.
Nice to meet you. My name's Fukami Touko.
I'll cook something up, so just think
of it as a light meal and help yourself.
Sure, thank you.
In the meantime, make her feel welcome here, Kakeru.
She's partly my guest as well today.
I know. I'll make sure to keep her company.
Anyway, let's go to my room.
Huh?
That's it over there.
What?!
Um...
Yes?
The other day, you know, when it rained,
on the hill up to the Kirinkan, you...
You were there?
I wasn't hugging Takayama back then, though.
I was just supporting her.
Hugging...
Her leg was hurting. You know that, don't you?
Yes. Let's not talk about this anymore.
So, when she was about to fall on that hill—
Anyway, it was nothing.
She's the reason I asked you to come here today, though.
Takayama's going to confess her feelings to Imi Yukinari.
What?
What?!
Hold on a minute!
How do you know that about Yana-chan?
Did you see her future?
She told me herself.
Eh?!
She asked me to tell you too.
Ehh?!
I want you to tell Touko as well.
Because—
I don't need you to tell me why.
Busts aren't supposed to talk back.
Whoops.
It's delicious!
So what do you think, Kakeru?
How about you take this
opportunity to get a cellphone too?
It's quite convenient, you know.
Is it really?
Um, well,
I wouldn't survive without mine.
Would anyone even call me if I had one?
Is Yana-chan's leg all right now?
Looks like it.
Ah, that's good to hear.
Look, I know your boyfriend's in the hospital too, but your inside knowledge is uncanny!
How often do you visit him?
Three days a week!
But those two looked so cute together!
I mean, their parents married each other even though they already have kids.
There they are in that complicated relationship,
their hearts battered like leaves in the winter wind,
tossed around like a tiny boat adrift in the stormy seas!
Okay, get out.
Friendship punch!
That was a lovely meal.
Thank you for having me.
See you.
I discovered an interesting spot the other day.
It's very close to here.
When I found it, I knew I had to show it to you, so I'd been meaning to ask.
Would you like to go there now?
Okay.
Hold on a sec.
I won't be long.
Thanks for today!
The food was delicious!
Thank your father for me.
I'm going to go home now!
Goodbye!
But you never asked for that favor.
Yanagi, you haven't gone home yet?
Nope. I'm resting here.
This is where I take a break, have some food
and water, and get ready for what comes next.
But you don't have
any water on you.
I have something I wanted to tell you.
I... love you, Yuki.
I know that you love Touko.
I know that you confessed to her, too.
And I know that it's going to be difficult for me to live in the same house as you once you reject me.
But like you said, we're family.
So I know what your answer will be.
Well, I might have been happier if you gave up on Touko,
but I'd hate you for it too.
I wanted to tell you anyway, though.
I don't know what will happen to us from here,
but this spot is where I'm going to move on from.
That's why I wanted to tell you here.
I'm going to head home now.
If we bump into each other there, I'd appreciate it if you didn't act any differently from before.
So today, I overheard some schoolgirls talking when I passed by them at the station,
and one of them was like,
"The Jokyu uprising was in 1221!"
Those high school girls
have it tough too.
Hina, could you set the table, please?
Fine.
Onee-chan, come help me.
Onee-chan, dinner!
Coming!
katachi no nai sekai ni iki wo fukikomu
Take a deep breath and shape this world
mata atashi ga umareru
and bring me back to life again.
barabara ni chirakashita
Hearts are fragile like glass
kokoro wa waremono dakara
and shatter into pieces when they're broken.
sotto tsutsunde kimi ni okurou
I gingerly wrapped those of mine and sent them to you.
hitotsu dake erande misete
Let me know which shard you've kept close.
nande mo nai you na hibi no kakera
Memories of our days together calmly pass us by.
wasurarenu mono to tsui ni aru no wa
There's rarely ever a day we wouldn't look back on.
nando mo daitatte itsu no ma ni ka
And before we knew it,
surinukete shimau mono da
all our moments together had long slipped into the past.
toumei na garasu no mukou bon'yari to
The scenery I caught but a glimpse of
sukashite mieta keshiki wa mada
when I peered through the looking glass
atashi mo shiranai kimi mo shiranai sekai kana
was of a world yet unknown to both you and me
kira hikari wo sorashita
that shined ever so brightly out of our reach.
I want to tell them myself.
That doesn't explain anything.
I'm a certified idiot.
And what am I?!
Come out into the schoolyard,
and we'll settle this.
Episode 6
Punch