Bring her into the shade.
You guys deserve each other.
That just then...
Touko, are you all right?
You scared me there! What happened?
Sorry.
I'm not sure.
Whatever it was, it looks like you're fine now.
Yeah.
I'll take you home.
Thanks. I appreciate it.
You've got a lot of explaining to do later.
So you can help her?
He's not coming.
This sucks.
Where could he be? It's already half-past five.
mune no naka de zawameiteru nami no hontou no imi wo
I pondered over the sound of waves astir in my heart
hizashi ni saegirarete watashi wa mada shiranai
though the rays of the sun blinded me from the truth.
ano koro egaita enikki mitai
Just like the pictures I drew in my diary as a child,
subete ga irozuki hajimeru hora
everything around us is being immersed in color.
manatsu no sora to umi no aosa ni
I try to close my eyes and hide
mabushikute me wo tojite mo
from the brilliant blue sea and sky,
watashi no kokoro no hashikko wo
but your voice always finds its way
tsukande hanasanai kimi no koe wa
right into the corners of my heart and holds on tight.
kore ga koi kana
I guess I'm in love.
Episode 8
Snow
Hinode Beach
High School
Track and
Field Club
Summer Camp
Hinode Beach
High School
Track and
Field Club
Summer Camp
Hinode Beach
High School
Track and
Field Club
Summer Camp
Hey, Yukinari.
Is our star finally making his return?
Glad to be back.
It's been a while. How're you feeling?
Just seeing how things go, y'know?
Take it slow, okay?
Gather around!
No...
No!
You listening?
The beach trip's off.
Oh, looks like he's here.
Coming!
Yanagi-chan!
Nice to see you again, ma'am.
It took an extra day, but she'll be discharged tonight.
Looks like I came just in time, then.
Thank you, Yanagi-chan.
Sure!
We're just going to the roof.
We'll be back in around twenty minutes!
Hiro told me about you.
You're in here for checkups, huh?
Yes.
I brought sake buns today!
Give Hiro my regards, okay?
Sure.
You've been spending a lot
of time with Hiro lately, right?
Yeah.
It was written all over his face, y'see.
Did something happen
between the two of you?
Yeah.
All right. I won't pry.
I know the beach trip was canceled at the last minute because your hospital stay was extended,
but I was looking forward to it, so I grabbed my swimsuit and went down anyway.
Oh. So you went with Yukinari-kun.
Well, that's the thing.
He packed and left for the track and field club's summer training camp.
Now, of all times.
I see.
Yeah. He didn't tell me about it either.
Well, I won't ask.
The reason I came here today was because I wanted to ask you something.
And to check up on you, of course.
I was just thinking there was something weird between Touko and David.
I don't know when it happened, but it looks like they're together now. Did you know?
Yes, I did.
It's like they're keeping a lot of things to themselves.
I was wondering if you knew anything about it.
If so, could you tell me?
Unless Touko asked you not to, of course.
She didn't ask me, no.
But I don't know much about it either.
That boyfriend of yours didn't come today.
Yeah.
I feel like having some cookies.
I'll make you some tea.
I hope you won't mind if I join you.
Sure.
Touko, are you awake?
Yeah, I am!
Mom asked me to bring you this.
Thanks.
Do you mind if I stay here for a bit?
Sure.
Yeah, yeah.
How is she?
Are you feeling better?
Yeah.
What was that back then?
Sorry. I'm not so sure myself.
Do you want to meet?
Aren't you afraid you'll see
something like that again?
Where do you want to meet?
Well...
I want to go see Jonathan.
All right. Sounds good.
See you in an hour, then.
Okay.
Touko said that your checkups would go just fine.
It was almost as if she knew
what would happen in the future.
I see.
Now that I think of it, when David first came to Kazemichi,
he said something about seeing
the same thing as her, didn't he?
"I saw the same thing you did," wasn't it?
You know something, don't you?
Like I said earlier, I don't know much.
I guess it'd be easier if I just
told you everything I do know.
I think Touko-chan and David have a special relationship.
Sachi,
could it be that you...
Not bad.
Thanks.
The other day...
Huh?
At the track meet. Sorry for what I said.
It's okay. I'm sorry too.
Imi!
Coach!
I ran into Yana-chan at the hospital earlier.
Oh.
Huh? You're not going today?
Nope.
I bothered to put in a good word for you with that fragile glasses-girl of yours, you know?
What's the point if you're not gonna make an effort yourself?
Dunno.
So something did happen.
Kakeru, are you enjoying your life here?
Yeah, I am. I guess.
Right.
I'm going to school, okay?
Oh, Onee-chan.
Yes?
Ah, sorry about earlier.
No, it's not that.
Oh?
Um, it's about Yukinari-san.
Huh?
Well, I'm not usually the type of person to do this, but...
Eh?
So, it was really unlike me
to get worked up like that,
but I ended up chasing him down on my bike and telling him not to stop being cool.
What? You talked to him?
Well, yeah.
What?!
But...
But what?
I don't think he was out jogging yesterday.
All the girls were telling me how much they'd been looking forward to seeing him.
Really?
I have practice later today too, so I'll see what happens.
I see...
He's not running.
Shall we see it next time?
The crafting process?
Yeah.
Sure.
What's up?
It's nothing.
Is he here?
Who's that?
Do you think we'll have to keep our distance
from each other from now on?
No, I'm sure we won't.
I wonder what that was.
I'm a little scared to be around you.
It sounds mean, I know.
I don't know what that was either.
But I'm a little hesitant to come close to you, too.
Sender
Hina
No Subject
Yanagi-san is running
instead of Yukinari-san.
What?!
Oh, sorry. It's from my sister.
She said that Yuki-kun turned into Yana-chan.
The other day, Hina-chan—
Oh, that's my little sister.
Hina-chan told me that Yuki-kun is their swimming club's—
Oh, you don't mind me talking about Yuki-kun, do you?
Her swimming club's what?
Right. He's her swimming club's idol!
I tried calling Yana-chan, but she didn't pick up.
From what you told me,
Takayama didn't seem to be in a hurry.
I don't think there's much cause for concern.
You think?
I hope so.
Kakeru-kun, are you worried about me?
Yeah.
I don't think you need to worry about Imi Yukinari,
but if it bothers you that much,
I'd be happy to take you to his house later.
Right.
The other day, I was sketching here
just like this when I ran into Yuki-kun.
Then we went to the art storeroom together for some pastels,
and in that storeroom...
Touko, do you have a thing for that Kakeru guy?
What do you mean?
Do you love him?
Right. I see how it is.
No, that's not—
I was really shocked!
Oh, sorry. I'm going on about Yuki-kun again.
I see. So that's what happened.
That's all that happened, though!
But you were taken aback by it, right?
Huh?
If we go to that storeroom again,
we may be able to learn something new about these fragments of the future.
You think so?
Why don't we go together?
But...
What?
You're right.
We might...
Which way?
Turn right at the foyer!
This way.
It's here.
All Contacts
Information
Edit
Shirosaki Hiro
Cell
The number you have dialed is currently out of range—
I think it would be a good idea
to talk to Imi Yukinari or Takayama.
Why?
Why do you think we should tell everyone?
How do you think Takayama felt
when she saw us at the beach that day?
"How"?
Well, I'm sure she was surprised.
Just surprised, you think?
Huh?
Takayama will most likely
ask you what happened.
But how am I supposed to explain it to her?
I doubt she'll believe any of it.
If anything like that happens again...
What? Do you think it will?
Huh?
What?
Kakeru-kun, this is...
Huh? Was that...
a fragment of the future?
Hey, what happened?
No!
Touko! What's wrong?
What did you see?!
No way...
Touko!
Mt. Shiomi
Sacchan
No Subject
Subject:
I'm out of the hospital.
Please visit me some time.
I have a book I'd like to lend you.
katachi no nai sekai ni iki wo fukikomu
Take a deep breath and shape this world
mata atashi ga umareru
and bring me back to life again.
barabara ni chirakashita
Hearts are fragile like glass
kokoro wa waremono dakara
and shatter into pieces when they're broken.
sotto tsutsunde kimi ni okurou
I gingerly wrapped those of mine and sent them to you.
hitotsu dake erande misete
Let me know which shard you've kept close.
nande mo nai you na hibi no kakera
Memories of our days together calmly pass us by.
wasurarenu mono to tsui ni aru no wa
There's rarely ever a day we wouldn't look back on.
nando mo daitatte itsu no ma ni ka
And before we knew it,
surinukete shimau mono da
all our moments together had long slipped into the past.
toumei na garasu no mukou bon'yari to
The scenery I caught but a glimpse of
sukashite mieta keshiki wa mada
when I peered through the looking glass
atashi mo shiranai kimi mo shiranai sekai kana
was of a world yet unknown to both you and me
kira hikari wo sorashita
that shined ever so brightly out of our reach.
The promised place...
Let's go to that storeroom again.
I'm going to make myself anew!
What a load of junk.
For tomorrow?
That'll be my line.
Episode 9
Moon