Let's go to the beach sometime.
The sound of the waves makes me feel a little uncomfortable.
Maybe we should head home.
Right.
mune no naka de zawameiteru nami no hontou no imi wo
I pondered over the sound of waves astir in my heart
hizashi ni saegirarete watashi wa mada shiranai
though the rays of the sun blinded me from the truth.
ano koro egaita enikki mitai
Just like the pictures I drew in my diary as a child,
subete ga irozuki hajimeru hora
everything around us is being immersed in color.
manatsu no sora to umi no aosa ni
I try to close my eyes and hide
mabushikute me wo tojite mo
from the brilliant blue sea and sky,
watashi no kokoro no hashikko wo
but your voice always finds its way
tsukande hanasanai kimi no koe wa
right into the corners of my heart and holds on tight.
kore ga koi kana
I guess I'm in love.
Episode 7
Bicycle
Morning.
I'm coming in.
Oh?
He wasn't here last night?
You've crushed on plenty of girls in the past.
I was only drawn to them out of curiosity.
I'm surprised by how different these feelings are.
I never would've guessed you'd fall for an airhead like her.
Don't make it sound like a bad thing.
It's not a bad thing.
Soon, you won't need us anymore.
I don't dislike your company.
All I hear now...
is your voice.
All the visions I see are of you, too.
Touko, Yana-chan's here for you.
Yana-chan?
Really? And what are you focusing on right now?
The fifty-meter freestyle.
I broke thirty-two seconds the other day!
I'm trying for thirty-one by fall!
Wow, nice going, Hina-chan.
You too! You're working hard toward your dream modeling job, right?
I'm cheering for you from the sidelines!
Man, you've got a great figure!
I'm so jealous of you.
Why, thanks.
Let's go clothes shopping sometime.
I'll pick out some outfits for you.
Seriously?
Of course! I'd love to!
Oh, Touko.
Sorry for dropping by out of the blue.
Let's chat outside.
See you later, Hina-chan.
Bye!
About the thing with
Yuki-kun yesterday...
You slapped him...
He kind of asked for it.
I think Kakeru-kun crossed a few lines too.
"Kakeru-kun", huh?
Wh-What's wrong?
Nothing.
Man, you're such an open book.
Am I really?
Yup.
Yuki's pretty dumb, isn't he?
Huh?
Doesn't he get that he doesn't stand a chance?
Did you hear? Sachi's going back to the hospital today.
Yeah. She said it's just for some checkups.
Oh, nothing to worry about, then.
We'll have to watch how often we visit so we're not too much of a bother.
Yup!
We wouldn't want to interrupt a lovers' meeting.
Yeah, there's nothing to worry about.
She seems to be doing fine.
Huh?
Nothing!
I think she'd be happy if we went to visit her.
Incoming Call
Yes, it's me.
Sure.
See you later, then.
It's been hard to get a hold of everyone lately.
Something's been up since that David guy appeared.
All ready!
One cola.
Y'know, the visiting hours at the hospital are really short.
Can't they let us stay till at least 10pm or so?
Whoa, those pianist hands of yours are firm.
Here comes the crescendo!
Ow!
And the fortissimo!
All right, I'm going to head home now.
If there's anything you need, give me a call, okay?
Sure.
Oh? Yes?
Oh my.
Is this your friend?
This is Hiro-kun, my boyfriend.
Really?
Pleased to meet you. I'm Sachi's mother.
N-Nice to meet you. I'm Shirosaki Hiro,
Sacchan's b-boyfriend.
My grandfather baked these cookies.
Thank you.
Hey.
I had no idea there was a swallow's nest here.
Oh, look! Chicks!
Yep.
There are at least two of them.
You seem to know a lot more about this place
than I do, even though I've lived here way longer.
It's kinda depressing.
I just know a few things. Living here your whole life is far more impressive.
No way! You're amazing in your own right.
I kind of embarrassed myself in front of you.
It's all right.
Actually, Yana-chan came over to my house earlier,
and we talked about what happened yesterday.
You're really close friends.
Um... and what are we?
Huh?
Sorry.
I couldn't face you for a second there.
Do you think we've become more than just
two people who share the same weird power?
Watch out!
I just saw a vision of you falling!
You'll be safe like this, though, right?
You can't change the future.
Let's go to the beach instead.
You'll be safer that way.
Come to the beach tomorrow, okay?
What're you looking at?
Oh my god, he's coming!
Huh?
He always passes by at this time!
The prince who appears at half-past five!
He's so cool!
That guy is one of Onee-chan's friends.
What? Really?
Do you know him?
Have you talked to him?
No, not at all.
Really? What a shame.
Aw, he's so cool!
Yeah, he is.
I think he's involved in some complicated stuff though.
Oh? What's he doing?
Imi.
Coach.
You never stopped training?
I saw your time at the last meet. I was impressed!
I was terrible.
Don't say that.
If you need anything, give me a call.
Oh, but I'm leaving for a week-long training camp in two days,
so call me either before
or after that if you could.
I see you're already up and working, Onee-san.
And you're always training hard at club, Hina.
Oh, right.
Hm?
I saw Yukinari-san yesterday.
We can see him run past our pool at the same time every day.
And somehow he ended up as our club's idol.
They were going on about forming a fan club for him!
Wow!
Yuki-kun's always so popular.
It's a small world, isn't it?
Yuki-kun's pretty handsome,
so I'm not surprised.
You said it! He looked really
graceful when he was running.
Yeah, he sure does.
Onee-chan, did something happen?
Why do you ask? Nothing happened, no.
Wow, Onee-chan, you're a terrible liar.
Huh?
A-Anyway, I need to go see Sacchan!
I gotta head off too!
They need to run some more tests today.
Ah, do they?
Guess I'll head home, then.
Thanks for coming every day.
No problem. See ya.
Sis?
Yes?
Sorry to bother you.
Welcome.
How are you feeling?
Great, thanks.
Oh, those are—
Hang on, lemme guess...
A gift from Hiro-kun!
Was I right?
You were.
So, Kakeru-kun?
Right, Okikura-kun.
And then Kakeru-kun said something kinda inappropriate, so Yana-chan...
When?
Tomorrow evening.
I see.
They say the good weather will hold out.
I'm hoping that if we watch the sea together, something...
Something?
Yeah.
I'm hoping that I might be able to see something new.
"See something"?
You mean those sparkly things?
When I'm with Kakeru-kun, I feel like I'm beginning to understand what they are.
Once I find out something more solid,
I'll be sure to tell you too.
Right.
Do you think he's feeling sick?
Hey, wait!
Where are you going?
What if the teacher comes?
Hina?!
Hi there!
I'm Fukami Touko's sister, Fukami Hina!
Um... Um...
Please don't stop being cool!
It's not about the future?
What's up, Sacchan?
Why're you calling so late?
I want to see the ocean.
I'll be discharged tomorrow,
so what if we all went in the afternoon?
I'd like to see Yukinari-kun and Yanagi-chan too.
We could light some
fireworks that night, too.
Sure. That sounds like a lovely idea.
Sorry for the short notice. I'll let Touko-chan know.
No problem.
I'll ask Yanagi-san and Yukinari.
So, what're you gonna do?
Dunno...
You didn't reply to my text last night.
You can come, right?
Yanagi-san said she'd be coming.
Huh?
Don't give me that.
Are you all right?
What are you doing, man?
He's with his girlfriend at the beach, isn't he?
How wonderful!
I raised him to be quite the oddball.
Oh? I dare say he's turned into quite the charming fellow.
And I dare say that's not something his mother would point out.
So, have you thought about it?
They need to run a few more tests on her,
so they're extending her stay until tomorrow.
Is that so?
Sachi, I thought I told you about this yesterday.
You did?
Good grief.
You've made things difficult
for your poor boyfriend now, too.
Oh, it's nothing at all!
Oh my gosh, "boyfriend"...
Sure, thanks.
Bye.
I'll be going, then.
Right.
Take care of Sachi for me.
Of course!
Anyway, I guess I should let
everyone know the beach trip's off.
I don't like David.
Oh? You don't?
Why's that?
Whenever he's around, we all fall apart.
Well, I guess it's true that we haven't all been together for a while now.
So what do you want to do?
Wanna go tomorrow instead?
Today, Touko-chan's on a date with David at Hinode Beach.
Huh?
That's why I didn't ask Touko-chan.
I see.
But... doesn't that mean that you tried to get us all
to crash their date because you don't like David?
Yes. That's right.
And you asked me to invite everyone.
Sacchan, does this mean...
I'm going home.
This way!
Hiro!
I'll take you home!
Sure!
Sorry.
I can't make it today.
Okay, I'll let him know.
The beach trip's off for today!
You listening?
The beach trip's off.
Did you wait long?
Don't worry. I don't mind waiting.
So you did wait.
Feeling uncomfortable?
Huh?
From the sound of the waves.
I guess it's a little different than before.
I think this is the first time I've come to the beach at this time of day.
These are for you.
Glass beads?
They match mine!
Thanks.
There's something that I've been thinking about.
Huh?
You said I'd fall, right?
Right. You're not allowed
to go anywhere high up, okay?
Do you really think that's going to happen?
Huh?
In the worst-case scenario,
I'd have to avoid any and all places
I could fall from for the rest of my life.
That's not going to happen.
Then what do we do?
I wonder if that really was
a fragment of the future.
But you were the one who told me that they were, Kakeru-kun.
Maybe we should reconsider the possibilities.
I'm going to go buy some drinks.
What would you like?
Water, thanks.
Y'know, I've always thought it was odd that adults would pay for a drink from the vending machine,
just to get water or tea.
They could always buy
the Halpis Water next to it.
I see.
You got invited out here too.
You're not with Touko?
She went to buy drinks.
Right.
Well, I might as well say this now.
It's all your fault that Yuki's not cool anymore.
Sorry for interrupting.
I'm gonna leave now.
Um—
You guys deserve each other.
Touko!
No...
No!
katachi no nai sekai ni iki wo fukikomu
Take a deep breath and shape this world
mata atashi ga umareru
and bring me back to life again.
barabara ni chirakashita
Hearts are fragile like glass
kokoro wa waremono dakara
and shatter into pieces when they're broken.
sotto tsutsunde kimi ni okurou
I gingerly wrapped those of mine and sent them to you.
hitotsu dake erande misete
Let me know which shard you've kept close.
nande mo nai you na hibi no kakera
Memories of our days together calmly pass us by.
wasurarenu mono to tsui ni aru no wa
There's rarely ever a day we wouldn't look back on.
nando mo daitatte itsu no ma ni ka
And before we knew it,
surinukete shimau mono da
all our moments together had long slipped into the past.
toumei na garasu no mukou bon'yari to
The scenery I caught but a glimpse of
sukashite mieta keshiki wa mada
when I peered through the looking glass
atashi mo shiranai kimi mo shiranai sekai kana
was of a world yet unknown to both you and me
kira hikari wo sorashita
that shined ever so brightly out of our reach.
You've got a lot of explaining to do later.
Well, I won't ask.
Touko! What's wrong?
What did you see?!
I want to go see Jonathan.
Episode 8
Snow