The moon is beautiful.
But isn't that...
A confession.
Eh?!
Sacchan, shouldn't you be
confessing to this guy here instead?
R-Right, Hiro-kun?
It kinda sounded like you were talking to me.
Huh?
I'm confessing to the both of you.
I love you, Touko-chan.
I love you, Hiro-kun.
Thank you.
I was finally able to say it.
I couldn't have without you, Hiro-kun.
So I was able to tell you too.
Yup.
The moon is beautiful tonight.
Sacchan, I still don't really get it.
Touko-chan, I hope we can stay
as close as we've been up until now.
Sure!
The moon is so beautiful tonight!
mune no naka de zawameiteru nami no hontou no imi wo
I pondered over the sound of waves astir in my heart
hizashi ni saegirarete watashi wa mada shiranai
though the rays of the sun blinded me from the truth.
ano koro egaita enikki mitai
Just like the pictures I drew in my diary as a child,
subete ga irozuki hajimeru hora
everything around us is being immersed in color.
manatsu no sora to umi no aosa ni
I try to close my eyes and hide
mabushikute me wo tojite mo
from the brilliant blue sea and sky,
watashi no kokoro no hashikko wo
but your voice always finds its way
tsukande hanasanai kimi no koe wa
right into the corners of my heart and holds on tight.
kore ga koi kana
I guess I'm in love.
Episode 10
Jonathan
Sacchan looks overjoyed, doesn't she?
She texts me every day, you know.
Really?
Yeah.
They're all messages "for tomorrow".
"For tomorrow?"
I'm home!
I wonder what's for dinner tonight?
Shove over a bit.
I saw Yanagi-san running today too.
Really? She's giving it her best.
Hina, have you told Touko yet?
Huh? About what?
You'll find out after dinner, so look forward to it!
Ta-dah!
You look so cute in that, Hina.
Don't you think it shows a bit much?
You got that from Yana-chan?
I wanted to give it back after she told me
Yukinari-san complimented her on it once, but...
Should I have?
No, no.
It looks amazing on you, Hina-chan!
I'm glad you kept it.
I know, right?
Could I have a word?
Here's your coffee.
Hina, that dress is a bit—
Drink up before it gets cold.
Right.
Onee-chan, Yanagi-san told me that
she's going to become a new person.
Huh?
Yana-chan's so awesome.
A new Yana-chan?
I can't wait to see what she's like.
I can't wait...
Sacchan
For Tomorrow
Subject:
"The Men Who Hoist The Moon"
"For tomorrow."
All Messages
Shirosaki Hiro
Sender:
For Tomorrow
"The Legend of the Greatest Master" was amazing.
It made me feel somewhat insignificant,
but I also felt empowered by it.
I'm looking forward to reading
"The Men Who Hoist The Moon."
"The Legend of the Greatest Master" was amazing.
It made me feel somewhat insignificant, but I also felt empowered by it.
I'm looking forward to reading
"The Men Who Hoist The Moon."
Hiro.
I still can't hear anything.
You can't hear the fragments anymore?
But why?
You think it's because you met Touko?
Or perhaps...
because you don't need them anymore?
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny today.
On Hinode Bridge, a mattress was laid.
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Black: 1     White: 2
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
One black, two white, huh?
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
I stopped by the gelato store.
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
It was sunny all day.
Yanagi
Today at Hinode Beach
One Thousand and One-Second Stories
Inagaki Taruho
Welcome—
Hi.
What can I get you?
An oolong tea.
We don't serve oolong tea.
Here's your coffee.
That's pretty grown-up of you,
ordering hot coffee in mid-summer.
That girl's name...
It was Nagamiya Sachi, right?
If you know her address,
I'd appreciate it if you'd share it with me.
I'm not gonna tell you just like that.
I thought as much.
What do you want to know?
Hey, do you like Touko-san?
You'd better be treating her well.
She's a dear friend of ours, you know!
I'll tell you Sacchan's address.
I haven't answered your question yet.
I... I'm not sure how to say this,
but I...
You don't have to answer me.
Today was sunny.
The skies were clear, too.
Hello?
Shirosaki Hiro told me your address.
I see.
Why did our five-thirty prince turn into a girl?
This is so lame.
Hina, you know something, don't you?
Hey, tell us!
That's my five-thirty prince!
Do you mind telling me about these "sparkly things?"
Yanagi-chan asked me the same thing a few days ago.
Did she?
You're not giving Touko-chan the care she deserves.
Yeah, I guess not.
Takayama told me that too.
But does Fukami Touko want to be looked after?
Huh?
I feel at peace whenever I'm with her.
Is it...
Is it wrong for her to look after me instead?
She might be looking after me, too.
I doubt that I know more about
those sparkly things than you do.
Do you...
love Touko-chan?
Don't tell me she's...
Hello!
Oh?
U-Um...
Are you the girl who called Kakeru the other day?
Um, yes!
Oh, you're adorable.
Pardon me, but could I have your name?
I'm Fukami Touko.
Um, is Kakeru-kun home?
I'm afraid not.
Oh, well, in that case, I'll be going!
Since you're here, how about a cup of tea?
Huh?
I'd love to have a chat with you.
Um...
Okay?
Sorry for making you wait.
Not at all.
He's an odd boy, isn't he?
Yes, he's very—
Er, I mean, just a bit—
I'm sorry.
Somehow, I feel that it's my fault.
Eh?
No, it's partly my fault too.
Huh?
Huh?!
Would you mind moving over a little?
You'll spill them!
Can't I do anything by myself?
I think the thing I hate most out of anything
is washing mustard spinach in the winter.
Have you done much of that?
I used to.
Kakeru doesn't have anywhere he belongs.
Huh?
I've dragged him around with me ever since he was little, you see.
We'd only stay in one place for two years at most.
He had no problems making friends when he was a child.
But every year, around when the local festivals started,
the kids would get all excited and forget about Kakeru.
He called that something, didn't he?
"A sudden but foreseeable loneliness."
Yeah, that's it.
You've got a good memory.
Well, it was my fault, after all.
Welcome back.
Thanks.
You've been running my course while I was gone?
Yeah.
Right.
When you take that path along the beach,
the cool breeze is nice and refreshing, don't you think?
Yeah.
Was the old man at the candy store there today?
And that last uphill stretch
isn't even that steep, but it takes a lot out of you, doesn't it?
Yeah.
Yuki.
Welcome back.
Thanks.
Wow, Grandpa, you were an avid reader?
Back then, we all read about twenty books a year.
Well, it was something they made us do,
so I can't really say I was "avid".
So, is it true that your boyfriend will be discharged soon?
Yup.
They say he can finally go back to work, too.
That's good to hear.
Right!
I'm happy for you, Sis!
Speaking of which,
I'd like to bring him here sometime.
That's fine with me.
Shouldn't we tell Mom and Dad too?
No, no, not like that.
It's just for some coffee.
What? Just for some coffee?
Yup. He wasn't allowed coffee
in the hospital, and he really missed it.
Oh. Right.
Yup!
Teehee!
This is the town I've always lived in.
This is the personal landscape that Kakeru-kun never had.
Here it comes, shortstop!
What now?
After all the problems it caused me,
now that it's actually gone, I can't help but miss it.
Fukami Touko, I want to see you.
You gonna start running again tomorrow?
Yeah.
Snow?!
Again?
I'm not afraid.
After all, this is where I belong.
I want to know more about Kakeru-kun's "sudden but foreseeable loneliness."
I want to know everything.
Jonathan.
Are you Kakeru-kun?
Wait, you're not Jonathan!
Huh?
One, two, three...
Someone's missing.
There's one missing!
I have to find Jonathan!
I'm not looking after them at all!
Jonathan!
Wait!
Kakeru-kun.
So you came here too, Kakeru-kun?
I thought I might be able to figure out why
I stopped hearing the fragments of the future.
I see.
That's not why you came?
I...
wanted to know about your
"sudden but foreseeable loneliness".
That's...
I heard about it from your parents.
Can you see the snow falling outside?
It's snowing?
Yes.
It's been snowing heavily for a while now,
and I've been out there in that snow.
It's not a fragment I'm seeing!
It's actually snowing around me!
Touko, you need to calm down.
Don't worry. I'm okay.
I'm not afraid.
But there's more.
More?
You...
You come up to me and...
And what?
Um...
You kiss...
Huh?
You... kiss me.
I don't know what I'm thinking,
because that wasn't even the first time I'd seen it!
What's happening to me?
I mean, you said so yourself, right?
You said that it might not be the future that we're seeing.
If not, then what is it?
What am I seeing?
Or...
is it...
going to happen?
Yes, what we've been seeing and hearing
might not be the future after all.
Regardless, you're saying
that you can see snow outside.
So we must be seeing and hearing something.
You're right.
We can't deny that something's going on here.
Yes.
And once I do this, we can call your vision a fragment of the future for sure.
katachi no nai sekai ni iki wo fukikomu
Take a deep breath and shape this world
mata atashi ga umareru
and bring me back to life again.
barabara ni chirakashita
Hearts are fragile like glass
kokoro wa waremono dakara
and shatter into pieces when they're broken.
sotto tsutsunde kimi ni okurou
I gingerly wrapped those of mine and sent them to you.
hitotsu dake erande misete
Let me know which shard you've kept close.
nande mo nai you na hibi no kakera
Memories of our days together calmly pass us by.
wasurarenu mono to tsui ni aru no wa
There's rarely ever a day we wouldn't look back on.
nando mo daitatte itsu no ma ni ka
And before we knew it,
surinukete shimau mono da
all our moments together had long slipped into the past.
toumei na garasu no mukou bon'yari to
The scenery I caught but a glimpse of
sukashite mieta keshiki wa mada
when I peered through the looking glass
atashi mo shiranai kimi mo shiranai sekai kana
was of a world yet unknown to both you and me
kira hikari wo sorashita
that shined ever so brightly out of our reach.
What are you saying, Kakeru-kun?
We spent all of yesterday together!
We'll be together for the
fireworks next year, won't we?
Onee-chan, this is bad!
Episode 11
Piano