mune no naka de zawameiteru nami no hontou no imi wo
I pondered over the sound of waves astir in my heart
hizashi ni saegirarete watashi wa mada shiranai
though the rays of the sun blinded me from the truth.
ano koro egaita enikki mitai
Just like the pictures I drew in my diary as a child,
subete ga irozuki hajimeru hora
everything around us is being immersed in color.
manatsu no sora to umi no aosa ni
I try to close my eyes and hide
mabushikute me wo tojite mo
from the brilliant blue sea and sky,
watashi no kokoro no hashikko wo
but your voice always finds its way
tsukande hanasanai kimi no koe wa
right into the corners of my heart and holds on tight.
kore ga koi kana
I guess I'm in love.
Episode 11
Piano
I didn't expect that.
I'm glad.
But...
Kakeru-kun, do you really like me?
I...
Am I only fooling myself that I do?
You think so?
Am I just trying to validate myself?
The snow's still falling all around me.
But you're not seeing it, Kakeru-kun.
I don't think we understand anything about each other.
You're right.
I don't see any snow.
I was thinking of asking my mother
to play the piano for me some time.
I'd like you to hear it as well.
Your mother's piano?
That sounds wonderful.
She's a professional pianist, so I know she'll treat it like a real performance.
And...
And, what?
You should come.
Do you think we'll understand
more about us if I do?
I'll give her a call now.
Hopefully she's free tomorrow.
Hello, Okikura residence.
Mom.
Kakeru?
What is it?
There's someone I've been hanging out with recently,
and I was hoping you could play the piano for them.
Oh, that's unusual, coming from you.
I don't think you've ever asked that before.
Yeah.
I'd love to.
I might as well play a few pieces.
Oh, why don't you invite their parents too?
Good idea.
Thanks, Mom.
Kakeru...
Huh?
What's the verdict on our
earlier conversation?
Verdict?
How about coming with me?
I'm still thinking about it.
So I'm guessing you're using
Fukami-san's cellphone right now?
I already had the chance to meet her.
She happened to drop by once when you weren't here.
I see.
Right.
She's a kind girl who has trouble being decisive,
and she pushes herself to keep the people around her happy.
I've only made things more difficult for her.
But she was the one who showed me how little I really know.
I see.
You really like her.
Yeah.
Let's head home.
I think I'll stay here a bit longer.
Huh?
I feel like this is where my summer began.
So I'd like to stay here.
This is where I belong.
I'm sure of it.
"Belong?"
It's something Sacchan told me.
Depending on the time, the occasion, and the people with you,
an ordinary place can become somewhere very special.
Don't stay out too late.
Okay.
Then I'll see you at my place tomorrow afternoon.
All right.
Hey, Hina-chan?
Could you do me a favor?
Yeah, I'll be back by tomorrow morning,
so could you make sure Mom and Dad don't worry about me? Please?
Thanks.
Bye, then. I'm hanging up.
Onee-chan, no way!
I'm home.
Welcome back.
You're home late today.
Y-Yeah.
Oh, welcome back, Onee-chan.
I hope she's all right.
Girls, dinner's ready!
C-Coming!
Onee-chan said she'll eat later.
Thanks for the food!
Oh, she said that she's not that hungry, so she'll just have a little.
What a picky sister she is.
Oh?
I want to go hiking again.
Huh?
Oh, okay.
Sure!
Hiking is great, isn't it?
I wonder if Sis can take us up this week.
No, I want to climb from the bottom.
What?
How's...
your knee?
The trainer who looked after me
at the camp said it should be all good.
Right.
I'm glad I went to that camp.
Are you going to go back to your
club once the second term starts?
Coach reckons I should.
I guess I will.
Though...
I bet I know nothing about what you do, Yanagi.
You wanna come watch me during my lessons?
Huh?
You're still here?
Look who's talking!
You said you'd go home soon.
I wonder if I'll belong here too if I stay the night.
Oh, that's...
If I were to find a place where I belonged...
Would you no longer experience that
"sudden but foreseeable loneliness" of yours?
Is it still snowing?
No, not anymore.
Good morning, Kakeru.
About your call yesterday—
He stayed out again?
Morning.
Will Fukami-san's parents be coming?
Probably.
In that case, let's ask them to come a bit earlier and join us for a meal.
Right.
You are going to tell Touko, aren't you?
Yeah.
You're still being indecisive?
Just because you have Touko doesn't mean you'll be able to escape from your fate.
Yes, I know.
Wh-What?
I was just thinking that you can really
take charge when it comes down to it.
Wh-What?
Those are the highest words of praise used at
Hinode Beach Middle School's Girls' Swim Club.
Oh...
Mt. Shiomi
I'm not carrying anything?
I'm not doing this because I'm a nice guy.
This is for your safety, Sacchan.
You don't seem to have a lot of confidence in me.
I'm a bit concerned for your health, so I'd rather play it safe.
What is it?
I'm here for you!
Thanks.
Mt. Shiomi
Morning.
Hey.
Good morning.
I won't be needing any breakfast.
Oh? That's a surprise, Hina.
A few things happened last night, and I ate way too much.
"A few things?"
I feel like I could eat a horse!
I'm so hungry!
Wow, it looks delicious!
Oh, Mom, if Hina-chan's not eating, I'll have hers too!
Grab on to those tree roots.
Okay.
oikaketemo oikaketemo todokanai yuki no you na
This indescribable feeling used to flutter out of my reach like snow
That sounds great. I'd love to go.
kotoba de arawasenai kanjou mitsuketayo
but I finally realized what it is.
What about you, Mom?
Count me in too!
All right, then!
Time to bust out that dress!
mune no naka de zawameiteru nami no hontou no imi wo
I pondered over the sound of waves astir in my heart
Guess I'll blow through the rest of today's work.
I'll help you!
hizashi ni saegirarete watashi wa mada shiranai
though the rays of the sun blinded me from the truth.
ano koro egaita enikki mitai
Just like the pictures I drew in my diary as a child,
subete ga irozuki hajimeru hora
everything around us is being immersed in color.
manatsu no sora to umi no aosa ni
I try to close my eyes and hide
mabushikute me wo tojite mo
from the brilliant blue sea and sky,
watashi no kokoro no hashikko wo
but your voice always finds its way
tsukande hanasanai kimi no koe wa
right into the corners of my heart and holds on tight.
kore ga koi kana
I guess I'm in love.
What?
Everyone was like, "Who is he?"
"Is he someone special?"
You made such a stir!
Whatever.
So, what did you think?
Think?
Yeah. What did you think?
You were the best dancer, as well as the prettiest.
You're going to move out
after you graduate, aren't you?
Excuse me.
I did my part yesterday!
Um, will you be going to Hinode Beach High School with Onee-chan starting next semester?
I haven't sorted out my transfer procedures just yet.
What're you guys talking about?
O-Oh, sorry. I'll give you guys some space.
Hina-san, would you like some cake?
I'd love some!
Kakeru, why don't you come for some—
Sorry, we were just about to go for a stroll.
We'll get started at five-thirty.
All right.
So you really wanna run with me?
I never said that.
But it's kind of a habit now, so I might as well.
Help yourself.
This is great!
There are pickled leeks, stuffed tomatoes,
soy-boiled spinach, fried tofu, and egg rolls.
Sorry. I'll get you some chopsticks.
Here.
Thanks.
The other day,
at the Kirinkan...
Yeah? What about it?
There's something I didn't tell you.
I'm sorry.
I was so cruel, getting you involved like that.
So this hiking trip was...
"For tomorrow."
Of course.
My father's a glass artisan, so I've been looking at sparkly objects since I was a kid.
I'm not sure what these visions are anymore,
but I wonder when I first started seeing them.
Lend me yours for a sec.
Okay.
We'll be able to test this soon.
It'd be nice if we found something out.
Yeah.
But I also wouldn't mind if we found nothing.
Huh?
I never would've thought both our families would come together to listen to my mother's piano.
Isn't that something to be happy about on its own?
Kakeru-kun, are you...
Yes.
I'm a little scared of knowing.
Can you see it too, Kakeru-kun?
Yeah.
Going downhill is pretty tough on your knees, isn't it?
Can you hear my voice?
Yeah, I can hear you.
It feels a bit strange not being able
to see someone who's close, doesn't it?
Can you see me from where you are, Sacchan?
No, not yet.
What is it?
I think I'm afraid of being together with you.
Huh?
Mom has asked me to accompany her around the world on her concert tour.
Kakeru-kun, what are you saying?
Do you mean that soon,
you might not be here anymore?
I don't think I can take experiencing that sudden but foreseeable loneliness every winter anymore.
But we spent all of yesterday together!
We're back.
Onee-chan, hurry up!
She's about to start!
Take a seat, you two.
If the fragments really are glimpses of the future,
that means that we'll be together
for the fireworks next year, doesn't it?
Once we're down at the bottom,
let's go to Kazemichi.
My pleasure!
Why're you stopping?
I need to talk to Touko again.
It's been a while since we've been to Kazemichi. Wanna go?
I guess.
katachi no nai sekai ni iki wo fukikomu
Take a deep breath and shape this world
mata atashi ga umareru
and bring me back to life again.
barabara ni chirakashita
Hearts are fragile like glass
kokoro wa waremono dakara
and shatter into pieces when they're broken.
sotto tsutsunde kimi ni okurou
I gingerly wrapped those of mine and sent them to you.
hitotsu dake erande misete
Let me know which shard you've kept close.
nande mo nai you na hibi no kakera
Memories of our days together calmly pass us by.
wasurarenu mono to tsui ni aru no wa
There's rarely ever a day we wouldn't look back on.
nando mo daitatte itsu no ma ni ka
And before we knew it,
surinukete shimau mono da
all our moments together had long slipped into the past.
toumei na garasu no mukou bon'yari to
The scenery I caught but a glimpse of
sukashite mieta keshiki wa mada
when I peered through the looking glass
atashi mo shiranai kimi mo shiranai sekai kana
was of a world yet unknown to both you and me
kira hikari wo sorashita
that shined ever so brightly out of our reach.
Anyway, can you guys introduce yourselves?
I'm Shirosaki Hiro.
Takayama Yanagi.
I'm Imi Yukinari.
I'm Nagamiya Sachi.
Um, can you see me?
Episode 12
Fireworks (Again)