N-Not bad.
I won't go easy on you just because you're a girl.
This kid... moves fast!
Fight like your life's on the line!
Also, if you can land a blow on him,
you'll get steak for lunch!
Steak?!
Don't get distracted!
Are you even being serious?
To think I came all the way out here for this.
This is why I can't stand girls.
Bring it on,
white-haired girl!
nan byaku nan sen nen mo
No matter the hundreds and
thousands of years between us
iroasenai telepathy
this unbreakable telepathy we share
douka tsunagatte
will keep us connected.
our bond glows strong
Our bond glows strong.
TOKYO ESP
hanpirei suru yume semete agaite
We struggle to close the distance our dreams have put between us.
TOKYO ESP
zero hearts
Zero Hearts!
kodou no pulse wo compass ni shite
Let my beating heart guide you back towards me.
zero hearts
Zero Hearts!
reincarnation nazeka kamisama wa konna kotoba sae
Why would the gods let the word "reincarnation" remain
gense ni nokoshi
in the world that we live in?
biru no mashita kaze no zankyou no naka de
Under these buildings in the howling winds,
kibou no hikari sagasu te ni wa
our hope shines towards our dreams.
juuryoku sae mo chigiri keshite mada tsuyoku
We'll tear away from the gravity that binds us and grow stronger!
aa zero ni naru shinka wo
Even if you hit rock bottom,
osorezu ni tondeyuke
don't be afraid to take flight and find another way.
kokoro wo gyutto tashikameatta kizuna to iu na no tsubasa
This connection we found with our hearts will become our wings.
nanajuuoku bun no ichi
No matter what comes my way,
yuzurenai jibun no iro de
not even a fraction of it will prevent me
kimi wo mamorasete
from protecting you.
never forget zero hearts
Never forget, Zero Hearts!
I've heard about you from the Sage,
He stopped her with ease!
and you've been all over the news, too.
How is he able to react so fast?!
But when you're this weak,
Ow!
you really think you'll be a match for those terrorists?
Is this kid dodging my attacks even before I make them?
If you're only motivated by a hot meal, you must be really simple-minded.
You shouldn't bother training at all!
You're too naive!
Rinka-san!
So what's your plan, little girl?
It's your turn next.
As if. I'm just messing with you.
I mean, look at yourself.
You're just a wuss.
Well, I'm gonna leave for cram school.
Something's off.
He's nowhere near as fast as Sage,
but his movements made it seem like he could predict my moves.
What if...
He caught it without turning around!
I knew it.
Cut it out already.
Rinka-san, what was that?
He didn't dodge it.
He knew I wasn't going to hit him from the start.
Then...
Yeah. He's just like us.
An esper.
Precognition?
Yeah,
but it seems like he can only see a few moments ahead.
Huh? How can you tell?
Because if he could see farther than that,
he would've known to take
a different route back to avoid me.
Right.
He's probably able to see a near future alongside the present.
But in order to win against him...
Even if you're able to predict the next blow,
a human brain only processes information so fast,
so I'll have to out-perform him with speed.
Maybe I could throw a hundred punches at once.
Hundred Shadow Fists!
Hundred Shadow Fists
That... doesn't sound realistic.
You think so?
Yeah.
You must be really simple-minded.
You shouldn't bother training at all!
I'm not simple-minded.
But if I can't beat someone like him,
I'll have no chance against Minami.
People often struggle when they approach an obstacle.
However, simply thinking about your approach won't always yield the right answer.
If thinking for a while gets you nowhere,
what would be your next course of action?
If that's how it is,
I'll just have to throw myself at it!
Very well then.
Countering is at the heart of CPC.
Any opponent is left vulnerable when they are attacking.
Once your opponent attacks,
follow up with one of your own.
Use your opponent's strength against them and counterattack appropriately.
Repeat this thousands,
if not tens of thousands of times.
Continue practicing the timing and
the moves until it's second nature for you,
and you can perform them out of reflex!
H-Hanako-san!
We mustn't, Taro-san!
I already have a husband.
You're too good for someone like him!
But...
I guess I still can't use my ESP
unless I directly touch the objects.
Don't do that, Peggi!
You can't play inside Rinka-san's bag!
Her baton...?
Now that I think about it,
I've never used my ESP on weapons before.
Taro-san!
Oozora Anakin
Ayumu, how are your studies going?
Summertime is your chance to get ahead of everyone.
Sure.
Just because you're only in 8th grade, don't think you can slack off.
You had better study like the entrance exams are around the corner.
How are you doing though, Mom?
The lower house elections are nearing, aren't they?
News Flash
Building Exploded By Terrorists
Suspects are ESP Users
Muted
I'm not letting those people who'd
terrorize our city roam free any longer.
I'm going to win and pass bills to protect everyone's future!
Right.
Goodness, they're monsters!
News Flash
Building Exploded By Terrorists
Suspects are ESP Users
Muted
Those ESP users.
I came all this way,
so give me your best shot.
What's the matter? I want to get this over with.
I'll catch a cold.
She's not taking the offensive.
Is she refusing to make the first move?
Last time, she took all the blows because she treated it like a normal sparring session,
but in every outcome I envision now
I get thwarted by her Transparency.
On top of that, every attack I make is going to be dealt with a counter.
But... we won't get anywhere if neither of us acts.
It doesn't matter if she counters as long as I can see it coming.
I can still attack back!
Kicks won't work on her.
Even if you manage to simulate every possible outcome,
you won't be able to keep up with the increasing rate of attacks, Ayumu.
The more you think, the slower you'll react.
Damn it!
Rinka on the other hand, is moving by reflex alone.
Throw her a thousand attacks,
and she'll counter every last one.
CPC's hidden technique:
Thousand Blows Counter
Thousand Blows Counter!
That's enough.
How could someone like me...
You did well in such a short time, Rinka.
Thank you very much, Sage.
Furthermore, it certainly helped that you learned the basics from your father.
Yes.
Ayumu, on the other hand, you're struggling with your Precognition and stamina.
Shut it! Like you know anything!
I was just caught off guard.
Give me a rematch.
There's no way in hell I'd lose to a girl!
Then how about you try me next?
You still haven't fought with me yet.
Murasaki-chan.
I'm gonna go all out.
Prepare yourself if you
don't want to get hurt.
My father, who absolutely loves Kung-Fu movies, won these off of an auction.
They're nunchuks that
once belonged to a master!
What?!
And here I was wondering what you'd use against me—
A lightning-fast strike too fast to counter!
Dragon Remembrance
Dragon Remembrance!
No way...
A miracle!
TOKYO ESP
The Girls in the Rain
It's useless.
Weren't you listening before?
The places you envision teleporting to are being subverted,
so you can't leave this place.
Haven't you had enough of all of this?
"Enough"? No.
It all starts here.
Everything is only just beginning.
Minami.
If only...
If only there was someone who could have been a symbol of justice for you like I had.
Then you could have been saved...
like I was.
Kyoutarou,
do you know the etymology
of the word "terrorism"?
Huh?
It's taken from the German word "Terror", which means "fear."
I faced it countless times in that place.
My parents and your mother became victims of it.
Sometimes, I wonder if everything that happened was a lie.
When I go through the same things everyday aimlessly,
I feel so detached from the passing of time.
We might go through the same things each day,
but I think you've changed little by little, Minami.
Like what part of me?
Huh?
Well, um, you've become more mature.
We're the same age,
but it feels like I'm being left behind.
Minami, I can't change the way you have.
But I'm...
I'm fine with staying the child I used to be.
ESP powers are capable of destroying the very foundations of our society.
tain a stable living
Reia
We must take immediate action to capture and interrogate all ESP users
to protect the peace in our daily lives.
Now is the time to bring ourselves together,
our hopes together,
and stand up against those ESP users.
If she found her that her very own son was an esper...
I guess she'd be devastated...
Oh? Ayumu-kun!
It's the Nunchuks Girl!
What are you doing here?
I was heading to my dad's place to return his nunchuks.
But you're totally weak without those.
Gonna stop playing hero now?
That's not it.
The master's moves through these nunchuks are too overwhelming for me.
With my strength, I can't last more than twenty seconds.
So I don't think I should use these.
My entire body was sore afterwards, too.
That's why I'm thinking about borrowing something else from my dad
that'll be better suited for me.
Sounds like you've got a happy household.
What do you mean?
N-Never mind.
Anyway, what's your motivation to fight this hard?
Motivation? None in particular.
Huh?
We've no other choice though.
I don't get you at all.
Even if people like us tried to make a difference,
it won't change anything about the world around us.
An explosion?!
No, this is—
A premonition!
Get down, Murasaki!
Huh?
Divine Punishment!
That guy's an esper!
So this is "terrorism"?
This is wrath from on high.
Stand up, you discriminator.
Damned authorities like you take advantage of the weak,
and use them to create this oppressing world!
Mom!
Let me give you a good taste of their agony!
Stop it!
My legs... Damn it.
Of all the times!
H-Hey!
What are you doing?!
That hurt.
Did you throw that at me?
He's looking here.
We're done for!
Get away from her!
And if you don't...
Oh, so it was you who threw it.
Remember this,
I absolutely hate it when kids look down on me!
Murasaki!
Wait.
Just wait a minute.
It's a premonition.
Get away from her!
And if you don't...
Oh, so it was you who threw it.
Wait! Just wait a moment!
We get it.
It's just like you said.
We're very sorry. Please forgive us.
Ayumu-kun!
She definitely won't do something like that again!
Lower your head, too!
That guy can control electricity.
You're gonna get turned to ashes if you get hit!
But...
At this rate, that woman will...
I can't let that future happen either!
Sorry, could you let her go?
What?
Are you some brats trying to play hero?
Wait!
But...
You two are getting annoying with your whispering.
I'll turn you into charcoal,
you and your shitty afro!
Did he just say "afro"?
Stop right there.
I'm an esper as well.
What did you say?
There's only one thing to do.
I've got no other choice.
My belt buckle's the only thing that can direct the electricity away from me.
But...
According to my visions,
it's going to completely fail,
and I'm definitely going to die!
What can I do?
I need to think of something quick,
or everyone here's gonna die!
Even the smallest thing can change the future!
Something!
Anything!
You say you're an esper?
You're saying you were one of the chosen?
Anything!
Isn't there anything at all?!
Anything that can change the future!
A waterpipe!
That's it!
Why you fucking brat—
Damn it! Did I not hit hard enough?
Why, you!
I'm screwed! It's too late!
What?
Damn... I overdid it.
Same here. My body's stiff.
But you went totally crazy there!
Especially for a girl like you.
Well, of course!
I'm a Defender of Justice!
Guess you are!
Is that you, Ayumu?
Mom! I'm so glad you're safe!
You...
Oozora
Reia
Don't tell me you're an ESP user?
araburu tamashii wa shukufuku no kuchizuke wo
A blessed kiss is granted to my unbridled soul.
annei yaburarete tsukurareta hinichijou
Severed from the peace I once knew, my life tumults into chaos
urotaeta sono mune no naraku e to maboroshi ga surinukeru
and apparitions slip into the dark depths of my restless heart.
onore no yoku ni
Have you been blinded
sono hitomi wa kegaretieru ka
by the greed that resides inside?
takanaru mune no
Feel your quickening heartbeat.
sono ishi wa shin ni seigi ka
Is your resolve what you believe to be real and true?
kotoba wo hanate
I'll set my words free!
kobushi kudaketemo tamashii ga
No matter how many times I'm crushed,
kowarenu kagiri ikudo mo
if my spirit stays strong, I won't be broken.
idonde wa yabure karada wa
My body bursts into a splash of red
barairo ni nijinde saku
but that won't stop my assault.
akeki inochi yo gin ni somare
My blood-red life will be bathed in silver.
araburi tsuki wa yoru ni
The savage moon lashes out,
tokasare maboroshi ni ochita
only to melt away into its own illusion.
TOKYO ESP
The Time Has Come, The Girls Have Started to Move