All alone?
Well, you went 'round beatin' up and turnin' in your own kind,
so o'course no one here'll warm up to you.
Now I finally understand
how fortunate I was to
be around such caring people.
nan byaku nan sen nen mo
No matter the hundreds and
thousands of years between us
iroasenai telepathy
this unbreakable telepathy we share
douka tsunagatte
will keep us connected.
our bond glows strong
Our bond glows strong.
TOKYO ESP
hanpirei suru yume semete agaite
We struggle to close the distance our dreams have put between us.
TOKYO ESP
zero hearts
Zero Hearts!
kodou no pulse wo compass ni shite
Let my beating heart guide you back towards me.
zero hearts
Zero Hearts!
reincarnation nazeka kamisama wa konna kotoba sae
Why would the gods let the word "reincarnation" remain
gense ni nokoshi
in the world that we live in?
biru no mashita kaze no zankyou no naka de
Under these buildings in the howling winds,
kibou no hikari sagasu te ni wa
our hope shines towards our dreams.
juuryoku sae mo chigiri keshite mada tsuyoku
We'll tear away from the gravity that binds us and grow stronger!
aa zero ni naru shinka wo
Even if you hit rock bottom,
osorezu ni tondeyuke
don't be afraid to take flight and find another way.
kokoro wo gyutto tashikameatta kizuna to iu na no tsubasa
This connection we found with our hearts will become our wings.
nanajuuoku bun no ichi
No matter what comes my way,
yuzurenai jibun no iro de
not even a fraction of it will prevent me
kimi wo mamorasete
from protecting you.
never forget zero hearts
Never forget, Zero Hearts!
This is Team A. We're in position.
This is Team B. We're now awaiting orders.
Good. Now get in there!
Ensure the end of the Professor!
This city is almost unbelievably peaceful.
Of course there's no need
for "justice" in a paradise like this.
What?!
Now, it's your turn to be scorched by the flames of rebellion.
Yesterday night,
due to the explosives set off by the enigmatic ESP terrorists,
the government has started discussing
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
an official evacuation announcement
for all civilians living in the city center.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
Due to the series of
terrorist bombings, an
evacuation announcement
is being considered.
An evacuation announcement for
capital civilians is under discussion.
The Self-Defense Force has received orders to create a barrier along Loop 7.
Self-Defense Force has
been dispatched. Security
are on high alert.
Prime Minister's
Official Residence
We've never dealt with
something like this before,
but this country will not yield to terrorism.
This is going to make us look even worse.
Damn it!
If this continues, we're never gonna get out of here!
The Self-Defense Force won't be able to stop the Professor and his group.
More people will end up dying in vain.
What should I do?
What...
What would Azuma-san do?
That's why it's our duty to uphold justice!
Only those with a power like this can do anything about it.
Azuma-san would definitely...
keep forging ahead with all his strength!
All right.
This should be enough food
and water to last me for a while.
All I need to do now
is teleport the raft with me
and take breaks as I make progress.
There's no time to waste.
I need to stop the Professor!
You are setting sail at last?
Who's there?!
Am I hearing things?
There shouldn't be anyone
else on this island, after all.
Humans are not the only ones to have received such mysterious powers.
Regardless, are you certain that you can reach the mainland safely on your own?
Tomorrow, I'm going to send you to the detention facility.
I can't protect you under these circumstances.
I'm sorry, Ayumu.
Where can I go?
What are we going to do?!
Barricading an entire prefecture is absolutely impossible!
However, if we're unable to defeat the terrorists before the end of the year,
the U.S. military is going to intervene.
Preposterous!
We can't afford to let that happen!
Good grief.
You're all still going on
with that ridiculous banter?
It's been five months since
the demand for a special esper zone.
The government still hasn't given us a reply and instead continues to belittle us as a terrorist group.
H-House Speaker?!
The House Speaker is dead.
Give me a situation report!
Yes, sir!
Captain!
What the hell is that?
The National Diet Building
has been seized!!
A previous report presented the following news:
Changes in Train Line Schedules
The National Diet Building
has been seized!!
The National Diet Building has been seized by a group of armed supernatural power users.
The National Diet Building
has been seized!!
Currently, the building is suspended in mid-air and is moving across the city skyline.
Due to the hazards—
Merry Christmas, dear ladies and gentlemen.
From today onwards,
we espers will be ruling over Tokyo.
Unless you submit to us,
your lives will end here.
This is not negotiable.
We apologize for the inconvenience. Please wait momentarily.
MTB Co-Prosperity Broadcast
Those wenches.
They've started making their move,
and they're targeting multiple areas all at once!
What?!
It appears this facility is also being attacked by some of their forces.
The enemy's coming!
Don't let them get through no matter what!
Roger!
Stop! Hold your fire!
They're ours.
Merry Christmas.
Now, you humans there,
it's time for all of you to say farewell.
Ladies and gentlemen detained in this facility,
your comrades are here to set you all free!
Be released from prejudice and
help us build a Shangri-La for the elite.
Let's create a new world together!
Would that get us out of here?
But that'd make us one of those terrorists.
So what?
If it'll get us outta here,
we've got no other choice.
I'm going to fight.
Are you for real?
I've got no other choice.
There isn't a normal person
out there who'd take our side.
Besides, there's only death here
for us if we don't join our "comrades".
I have something I want to get back.
Well, well...
Looks like the time for rest is over.
Sage!
Hm?
What's this?
We came all this way
to save them, but no one's here.
It's also pitch black.
That girl...
she's still alive?
You thought you could blind me using the dark?
You're nothing but a walking corpse!
She has her eyes closed...?
Not bad moves.
But you never got those powers back from the shining fish, did you?
Your face says it all.
You won't be able to pass through my Hundred Godly Fists then!
She shoots energy by channeling her powers through her fists.
If I can change the direction
of the burst before she releases it...
Rinka!
Skull-Smashing Psy-Kick!
TOKYO ESP
On an island that stretched beyond this sun,
I came across the shining fish when I flew over its skies,
and there I obtained the power to read the human heart.
That's where I want to go.
As a migratory bird, I can show you the way,
but in exchange, I'd like you
to introduce me to a fine partner.
A partner? As in, a mate?
Yes, that's it.
I, too, wish to experience love.
Even if we were to part ways in death,
I want someone whom I could value more than my own life.
Yes,
someone like who the
white-haired girl is to you.
Urushiba Rinka is dead.
Rinka-san...
No...
I haven't found out for sure.
She must still be fighting in the city!
Off we go, Pelly!
Huh? "Pelly"?
Everyone who was detained
is going to be released?
Shouldn't we be worried?
I don't know about that,
but I do know that they're the
only ones who can face the terrorists.
You will not!
You're not going, over my dead body!
But if I don't,
more and more lives will be lost while I sit here and do nothing!
I don't care!
Even with our powers, there's nothing we can do to change this situation!
Other people don't need to be saved.
As long as you're safe, that's all I care about.
You wouldn't have said that before.
I don't want to see my daughter
at death's door again.
You were my hero.
I always wanted to become someone like you,
because you were my hero, Dad.
Rinka.
It's true that I might not make a difference by going there,
but there has to be at least
one person who'll face them!
I'm doing this to let everyone know that not all espers are bad people!
Rinka! You—
Oh dear.
Dad, I'm sorry!
Wait, Rinka!
It's okay!
I definitely won't die!
What an idiot.
There she goes...
You're the idiot.
She's the spitting image of your younger self,
Urushiba-san.
Nabeshima!
Who are these people?
These people
were previously called upon at my request and
are the best match for the white-haired girl's style.
What?!
I'm begging you,
fight alongside us!
I know I'm asking a lot of you,
but we won't even be able to save this town without your help!
Every one of us is willing to risk our lives,
so lend us your help!
Please!
Urushiba-san!
Geez,
everyone around here is jumping to put their life on the line.
Retreat! Retreat!
Skull-Smashing Psy-Kick!
That girl with the white hair is finally here.
Urushiba!
Are you all right, Rinka?!
Dad!
We're here to fight with you,
white-haired girl!
Listen up,
head straight to where the hostages are being held once you're inside.
Understood.
Thanks, Dad.
We'll be fine in there.
This is the last time I'm helping you with something this reckless!
I know.
Even if it takes a miracle,
I'm putting my foot down!
I'll handle this!
This is bad!
An electrokinetic is standing by!
Be blasted into smithereens!
What?!
A shield out of psychokinesis.
To think you held such power!
Wait a minute, why are you even here?
I also...
have something I want to get back.
Miracle!
I'm leaving the rest to you, Rinka!
Don't leave any openings uncovered!
The enemy is starting to gather!
Behind us!
All right,
we'll be able to make our way
to the hostages now.
Wait.
I'm returning these to you.
I held onto them personally
so they wouldn't be confiscated.
Thank you very much, Inspector Nabeshima.
Aw man,
they're makin' a lotta flash and bang in the sky,
but here we are babysittin' a penguin.
Down in the mouth, huh?
Huh? What's with that girl?
This baseball...
is a treasured item from my father's baseball club days.
Strike Remembrance!
Strike Remembrance!!
Damn you!
Just what are you tryin' to pull—
Don't you point that at a kid!
Nice job.
Looks like I didn't even have to break a sweat.
Peggi!
Thank goodness!
I'm never letting go of you again!
All right, now I can fly to the Diet Building.
I'm going with you.
Huh?
My mom's there.
I'm going too.
I don't want to be separated from Peggi again.
Well then, let's get started.
We'll smash their noses in.
This is the assault team!
The hostages have been secured
in the First Committee Meeting Room.
It seems the white-haired girl has secured the hostages.
I'll let you handle the rest.
Make sure to give them a big, warm welcome.
Let's go, Minami.
Wait.
I'm staying.
This time for sure, I'll put an end to Urushiba Rinka.
There she goes.
Is that all right?
Let her do what she likes.
Listen up,
we're going to take down the espers who
are controlling the National Diet Building next.
Then we'll have Urushiba use his magnetic abilities to land the building safely.
This is the only way we can save everyone here!
Minami.
I'll take care of the unimportant ones.
As you will.
Urushiba!
araburu tamashii wa shukufuku no kuchizuke wo
A blessed kiss is granted to my unbridled soul.
annei yaburarete tsukurareta hinichijou
Severed from the peace I once knew, my life tumults into chaos
urotaeta sono mune no naraku e to maboroshi ga surinukeru
and apparitions slip into the dark depths of my restless heart.
onore no yoku ni
Have you been blinded
sono hitomi wa kegaretieru ka
by the greed that resides inside?
takanaru mune no
Feel your quickening heartbeat.
sono ishi wa shin ni seigi ka
Is your resolve what you believe to be real and true?
kotoba wo hanate
I'll set my words free!
kobushi kudaketemo tamashii ga
No matter how many times I'm crushed,
kowarenu kagiri ikudo mo
if my spirit stays strong, I won't be broken.
idonde wa yabure karada wa
My body bursts into a splash of red
barairo ni nijinde saku
but that won't stop my assault.
akeki inochi yo gin ni somare
My blood-red life will be bathed in silver.
araburi tsuki wa yoru ni
The savage moon lashes out,
tokasare maboroshi ni ochita
only to melt away into its own illusion.
TOKYO ESP
Tokyo ESP Girl