Urushiba Rinka is dead.
There's...
There's no way that's true!
Damn it... I can't go on.
I'm hoping
that you're all right, Rinka-san.
nan byaku nan sen nen mo
No matter the hundreds and
thousands of years between us
iroasenai telepathy
this unbreakable telepathy we share
douka tsunagatte
will keep us connected.
our bond glows strong
Our bond glows strong.
TOKYO ESP
hanpirei suru yume semete agaite
We struggle to close the distance our dreams have put between us.
TOKYO ESP
zero hearts
Zero Hearts!
kodou no pulse wo compass ni shite
Let my beating heart guide you back towards me.
zero hearts
Zero Hearts!
reincarnation nazeka kamisama wa konna kotoba sae
Why would the gods let the word "reincarnation" remain
gense ni nokoshi
in the world that we live in?
biru no mashita kaze no zankyou no naka de
Under these buildings in the howling winds,
kibou no hikari sagasu te ni wa
our hope shines towards our dreams.
juuryoku sae mo chigiri keshite mada tsuyoku
We'll tear away from the gravity that binds us and grow stronger!
aa zero ni naru shinka wo
Even if you hit rock bottom,
osorezu ni tondeyuke
don't be afraid to take flight and find another way.
kokoro wo gyutto tashikameatta kizuna to iu na no tsubasa
This connection we found with our hearts will become our wings.
nanajuuoku bun no ichi
No matter what comes my way,
yuzurenai jibun no iro de
not even a fraction of it will prevent me
kimi wo mamorasete
from protecting you.
never forget zero hearts
Never forget, Zero Hearts!
Murata Electronics
Ten days have passed since the
ESP Regulation Laws were enacted.
The terrorists are attacking the enforcement squads located throughout the cities,
News Flash
Terrorist attacks rising.
Are they focusing on the enforcement squad?
leaving those areas in chaos.
Hey, you—
Hey!
Aren't you the white-haired girl?!
Sorry, but I want you to leave.
I'm gonna get into deep shit if I'm seen with you.
You're able to see them too,
Urushiba Rinka-san.
Azuma-san...
No matter how much I was beaten,
I continued to fight.
That's why it's our duty to uphold justice!
"Our duty"...
I was able to come this far
because I believed in that.
But...
All I did was endanger everyone,
and I lost my ESP without being able to protect anyone.
I was never meant to be a hero at all...
You promised you wouldn't leave me behind, no matter what!
Come back,
Azuma-san!
You really are my hero!
Azuma-san?
Azuma-san!
There's no point in being a hero.
If Azuma-san isn't with me,
there's no point.
Rinka-san—
Is this... the island I was on before?
Stop doing futile things.
Even with your Teleportation abilities,
you won't make it back to Tokyo.
Why did you save me?
Wasn't I supposed to be publicly executed?
That's what Father said.
But I'm not him.
What makes you any different from him?!
You killed countless people for no reason!
It wasn't without reason.
Huh?
You're only saying that because of your ignorance.
My ignorance? About what?
The reason why my mother and your parents died.
We just injected a tracking device with a wiretap into you.
Welcome to the ESP User Detention Facility.
Hey, look.
Hm?
Everyone in here is an esper...
It's a detention facility, after all.
It may look like a prison,
but it's actually pretty comfortable here.
Sage!
Though, right now I can't stand due to the after-effects of the tranquilizer.
Are you all right?
There's nothing to worry about.
Rather, I'm relieved to see that you are well.
U-Um, Sage.
What about my dad?
What? A Sleep Capsule?
Yes.
Espers who have the ability to teleport or fly,
and those with pyrokinetic or electrokinetic powers are hard to supervise.
So they're put into a medically induced coma.
No way...
I'm sorry.
I was with him back there, but...
Don't do that.
Get too close, and it'll steal your ESP abilities.
Oh my!
If it's that dangerous, shouldn't we just kill it?
If we did, all the fish that the Collector has gathered so far would scatter.
Furthermore, I wouldn't want anyone else getting their hands on them.
It can't do anything dangerous if it's kept like this.
Oh, so you mean this caged bird won't sing, huh?
Anyway, what is this thing that gives us these powers?
It looks just like the Ark of the Covenant from the Old Testament.
The story starts in a land far away from here.
Eh?
That's right.
At the very least, the miracles we came across there were real enough.
What do you mean?
Didn't my parents and your mother die because they were caught in the middle of a civil war?
That may be the reality that you know,
but the truth is different.
Huh?
You're both going to stay over there?
Yeah.
We won't be able to leave the site for a while.
We're sorry, Kyoutarou.
Sorry about that.
Y'see, we found somethin' real big.
"Somethin' real big"?
That's right.
Dad!
Mom!
This is spectacular!
What a spectacular discovery
you've made, Professor!
Thank you.
However, we haven't yet been able to surmise how it came to be here—
I don't care about that.
This is the key to becoming God!
If the Old Testament is accurate,
then this is the ultimate weapon that brought down countless armies and castle walls!
The Ark!
The chest that holds the Tablets of the Covenant!
General!
These are...
The tablets of the Covenant!
Finally...
Finally, they are mine!
What have you done?!
Fish?
What's going on?
TOKYO ESP
In the Midst of Sorrows...
Dear, are you all right?
What about you? Were you injured?
I'm fine.
Thank goodness.
Man,
can you believe that general though?
To think he ruined that precious artifact.
Yeah.
But what was that?
Those shining fish that swam out from the tablets...
Fish?
You didn't see them, Juutarou-san?
We lost our consciousness because of those fish.
That's what happened?
I totally thought you'd fainted at the horrific sight of the broken tablets.
Oh, you're awake now too!
This is great!
You know, Juutarou,
you're being really loud.
Huh? Oh, sorry about that.
I said,
you're being loud!
We're in a hospital!
Wh-Why is there a fire?!
Seira!
Bring some water, Juutarou-san!
I-I got it!
Quickly!
Wow.
You can really materialize an object just by thinking about it?
Yeah.
C'mere.
Ow!
I'm sorry!
How perplexing.
It's an illusion that doesn't exist,
yet you can feel everything as if it does.
There's no doubt.
The light from the tablet is the cause of this,
transforming our bodies in some way.
That's the only explanation I can think of.
Just what exactly was concealed in there?
You're going to get more wrinkles.
Don't fret so much over this.
All right.
That was spectacular, Mister Azuma!
General!
I read your reports.
They were truly spectacular!
So?
What do I do to obtain these powers like you?
We're not exactly sure yet,
but we should at least form an international research organ—
Not happening.
The research will be carried
out solely in my country.
Huh?
The Ark belongs to my country.
Until I get my hands on that power,
I won't let any of you leave here either.
That poses quite a problem, I'm afraid.
And who do you think you are?
I assumed something
like this might happen.
He's an ambassador I called for from Japan.
What?!
Greetings.
I'm Washibana, an ambassador sent by the Ministry of Foreign Affairs.
Please conduct all negotiations through me,
General.
That's it.
If what the General said is any indication,
it's much too dangerous for
us to stay here any longer.
Therefore, you two should make preparations to leave for Japan immediately.
What?
But then, the Ark...
But your safety is more important.
And what about you two?
Don't worry.
Once we finish things over here,
we'll leave this country ourselves.
I see...
Well, why don't you come over
to our place for lunch tomorrow?
Yeah.
I want to introduce our son to you before we leave.
His name is Kyoutarou.
He says he wants to be just like us when he grows up.
I see.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Oh, Washibana-san.
What's the meaning of this,
gathering everyone here at this time of night?
Right.
Actually, I wanted to bring up the decision to let all of you return home, but...
the General's late.
He's supposed to be here as well.
I'll go look for him.
What's going on?!
Wh-What?!
Wh-What just...
Juutarou...
Kyouka...
Seira!
As agreed, I'll be taking one of the tablets.
I'll let you keep the remaining one as well as the Ark itself,
but this exchange and what happened here is to be kept secret—
I know that.
Oh?
Well, well.
What's going on here?
Why is an ambassador involved in this?
Don't tell me...
Did the Japanese government order you—
You've no need to know.
No matter what you try,
you won't be able to interfere anyway.
I can't wait!
Wow!
See you!
Father!
I was the only one who escaped from that place.
However, what awaited me in Tokyo was...
I'm glad to see you returned alive but...
You disregarded the evacuation recommendation and got all the other researchers killed.
I'm afraid not even the university—
Wait a moment!
Evacuation recommendation?
We didn't receive any!
They were all killed as part of the Japanese government's schemes!
You just want to blame the government for losing your colleagues.
You're just refusing to admit that it was your fault!
It's your fault.
Are you even still sane?
Not a single person believed in what I said.
The ambassador must have all the answers I need!
I then began my search for him.
Pedestrians
and
Bicycles
Only
Pedestrians
and
Bicycles
Only
Hurry! Call the ambulance!
The truth was buried far from my reach
by a hand in the shadows.
Why?
Just why?
Why this?
This is wrong...
There's something wrong with this world!
Th-That monster!
Y-You're...!
Wait, please!
It was him!
It was all that ambassador's doing!
He's dead.
The mastermind that disposed of him must be hiding in the government's fold.
That person is going to make use of that stone tablet in their plans, I'm sure.
If that's the case, I'm going to need this tablet to draw them out
and kill them,
as well as every person they hold dear.
Kyoutarou!
Damn it.
You brats—
Huh?
His name is Kyoutarou.
St-Stop...
Seira...
No!
Seira!
Don't go!
You have... wrinkles...
Soon.
Soon, this world full of wrong will come to...
an end.
They were killed.
My mother, along with your parents.
But that doesn't mean you should take revenge.
Doing that won't bring any of them back!
No, it won't.
Huh?
So, can you forgive the people
who killed your parents?
Th-That's...
Can you swear from the bottom of
your heart that vengeance is wrong?
Damn it!
What would you do at a time like this,
Rinka-san?
I never could stand terrible people.
These are bad guys, right?
Yeah.
That's good, then!
There's no other answer.
What's wrong will always be wrong.
You were always the type to act first
and save the words for later, Rinka-san.
araburu tamashii wa shukufuku no kuchizuke wo
A blessed kiss is granted to my unbridled soul.
annei yaburarete tsukurareta hinichijou
Severed from the peace I once knew, my life tumults into chaos
urotaeta sono mune no naraku e to maboroshi ga surinukeru
and apparitions slip into the dark depths of my restless heart.
onore no yoku ni
Have you been blinded
sono hitomi wa kegaretieru ka
by the greed that resides inside?
takanaru mune no
Feel your quickening heartbeat.
sono ishi wa shin ni seigi ka
Is your resolve what you believe to be real and true?
kotoba wo hanate
I'll set my words free!
kobushi kudaketemo tamashii ga
No matter how many times I'm crushed,
kowarenu kagiri ikudo mo
if my spirit stays strong, I won't be broken.
idonde wa yabure karada wa
My body bursts into a splash of red
barairo ni nijinde saku
but that won't stop my assault.
akeki inochi yo gin ni somare
My blood-red life will be bathed in silver.
araburi tsuki wa yoru ni
The savage moon lashes out,
tokasare maboroshi ni ochita
only to melt away into its own illusion.
TOKYO ESP