This way, everyone!
Kaname!
Akari-san!
Where are Hikari and the others?
I'll go check again!
Wait, I'm coming too!
Manaka! Manaka!
Manaka!
When Miuna-chan held me,
All the feelings I lost flowed into me—
like air into my lungs.
That's because my Ena is
crying out that it loves Hikari.
Yes.
Just like taking a breath,
my feelings as well as the feelings of other people flowed into me.
Like the love Miuna-chan's mom had for her father,
which brought her to live on land.
As well as the love that Akari-san, Tsumugu-kun's grandfather,
the candy shop owner Satsuki-san,
Kouji-niisan, and countless others had felt.
They all fell in love with someone above land.
The Lady was no exception.
But she had tears in her eyes.
The glow I felt in the sea was the
dissolved pieces of the sea's legend.
It was the legend of the Sea God.
The Sea God fell in love with
the Lady only to be heartbroken.
For the Lady had a lover above land before she became the sacrifice.
The Sea God could only hold himself at fault
for pulling her away from her lover.
But the Lady never once accused him of doing so.
However, the deeper the
Sea God fell in love with her,
the more pained his heart became.
Seeing the Lady silently weeping,
unable to forget her lover,
the Sea God decided to return her to land.
But the Sea God already knew.
The lover the Lady had left behind
was unable to bear his loss
and disappeared into the sea.
And so, this led the Sea God to
dispossess the Lady of her heart to love.
If she could love, the news of her lover
ending his life would only succumb her to despair
and the Sea God feared
she would follow the same fate.
The Lady's feelings of love calmed the sea.
Hereafter, the sea would stay still.
Like a heart that has lost its love.
Manaka! Manaka!
Manaka!
Chisaki!
How's Manaka?!
Look, Chisaki!
Ena...
Manaka!
Chi-chan.
Manaka, thank goodness!
The sea's so pretty...
Miuna...
A beautiful ocean.
How pretty...
What's going on?
It looks like the sea's starting to move.
Miuna!
Wait, Hikari!
Stop for now.
If you try to force her out from there, she'll end up like Mukaido.
So you're telling me to do nothing?!
There's nothing...
I can do!
Miuna was always looking at the sea.
What's wrong?
I'm waiting for Hikari.
I see.
There should be a way to save her.
It's better not to act so rash.
I'm going to check if anything's
happened at the village.
This ended up as another disaster.
Uroko-sama...
Why are you here?
The Sea God told me to bring him to Shishio.
"I want Manaka to fall in love with me."
That's all I wished for.
I wanted to be the closest
to her and smile by her side.
I'd do anything to protect her smile.
But, when I started living on the land,
the one who saved me from
being overwhelmed by my fears
and stayed by my side was...
And yet I...
I was blind to how you felt for me.
I love Manaka.
Again!
I love Manaka!
Again. Again!
I hurt you so much...
Just... what were you thinking?
You're... such an idiot.
How did you ever come
to like someone like me,
while knowing my feelings
were for Manaka?
Miuna, this can't happen to you!
Because you loved Akari so much,
I'm able to see this happy
scene in front of me now.
So, I want Manaka to feel again.
But really, I was wrong...
It's just like you said before,
"If you didn't love anyone,
you wouldn't have to be sad."
When one finds love, another is brought pain.
If there's no choice but to make someone suffer...
If that's what love really brings...
...then being able to
love someone is the worst!
Take it all away, Sea God!
Take every ounce of love
I can feel away from me!
In exchange, please save Miuna!
Manaka.
It'll be okay, Hi-kun.
Huh?
Since Miuna-chan's feelings are...
He's crying.
Really, Hikari's such an idiot.
The Sea God is just as foolish too.
Sea God, why did you take
the Lady's heart away?
The waves pick up the dry pieces of coral,
nami wa kawaita sango wo saratte
Because after all, she...
gently tossing and turning them to the sea shore.
sotto umi ni kaeshite mata uchiyose tsuzuketeru
I really want to let them know...
The Sea God.
Hikari.
Miuna...
I want them to know what
it means to love someone.
I wake up
zarazara to ochiru
to the sound of moving sand.
sunatsubu no oto de me wo samasu yo
The spirit flames...
No, the Sea God's consciousness!
Forget what tomorrow will bring.
ashita wo wasure
Stir up your heart and call out to me,
sashi dasareru koui mo zenbu yobi samashite
I want to tell Hikari
Shioshishio...
because I'll be here building a castle of sand.
suna no shiro wo tsukutteiru
that I'm glad I fell in love with someone
who cares and cries so much for me.
Forget about everything else,
subete wo wasure
Miuna!
because even if you can't call out my name,
namae sae yobenakunattemo
tomorrow will still come,
asu wa kuru
and I'll be reminded of my sorrow each morning.
zankoku na hodo hitoshii asa
But even so,
soredemo ima wa
I'll gather everything I love and continue
itoshii subete orikasanete hashirudake
Miuna...
until it gets swallowed by the sea.
umi ni majiru hi ga kurumade
You're the one who taught me, Hikari.
Although my memories are failing,
kioku nante tayorinai film dakedo
I don't want to believe it's useless,
or that you shouldn't love anyone.
You're right. It's not useless.
I call out to you,
yobi samashite
because I'll still be here building a castle of sand.
suna no shiro wo tsukutteiru
Loving someone... isn't useless.
Miuna! Miuna!
This is...
The Ladies?
Sea God, why would you do this?
Sea... God.
Miuna!
The Lady's feelings of
love are inside the sea.
I don't want to forget.
It's coming from the sea?
I didn't want to forget him.
But above all, I didn't want to lose the days I spent with you and our children
or my heart that loved you.
Such foolishness. Even a god would tire from hearing this.
Listen, Sea God. You took away her love without knowing who it was really for.
And now you finally know of the Lady's
true feelings after they dissolved into the sea.
The spirit flames are
reacting to the Lady's heart.
After acquiring Manaka to replace the Lady,
the Sea God's emotions stopped flowing
out into the water, and the sea became calm.
Without pain, there was
no need to make waves.
However, while there was no loneliness, neither was there happiness.
The spirit flames are also a part of the
Sea God's consciousness, correct?
That's right.
Until now, the spirit flames burned as what remained of the Sea God.
But they most likely awakened to the Lady's feelings that dissolved into the sea.
Uroko-sama...
That's right.
I am but a scale.
A scale of the Sea God.
But, just like the Sea God himself,
I will love the Lady until the end of time.
Dad...
Dad!
Why are you awake?
You scared me!
What happened to the cold sleep?
You're grown up, Miuna.
Grandpa.
A child made between the
land and sea lose their Ena.
Hence with the approaching crisis above land,
people from the sea needed to be in cold sleep.
This is to preserve even the smallest hope of having descendents.
However, Miuna is here.
And she has Ena.
If that's the case, we can still have hope for what the future entails.
I-Is this all right, Uroko-sama?
There's no use asking me;
I was not the one who awakened them.
Let me see Akira.
Huh?
How do you know about Akira?
Actually, how do you also
know that Miuna has Ena?
Have you forgotten?
You were the one who told me.
You talked about how Miuna acquired her Ena and how Akira was born, too.
Your voice reached me,
as well as how you felt.
Dad...
A love that never changes.
A love that changes over the flow of time.
Neither way to love is wrong.
Welcome back.
The sea!
Huh?
The once calm sea is stirring!
What's this? The sea stayed still until now.
Look over there.
Bring out the ships!
Hey!
Hey! Hikari!
Love comes from the sea.
Hikari!
Hey, Hikari!
Glad you're back!
I believed in you, buddy!
A love that is gentle and kind,
but also fierce and painful.
But really, it's like a sea
with everlasting love.
Manaka.
Love is like the ocean.
Miuna-chan!
I'm so glad!
Thank goodness, Miuna-chan!
Hey now. Weren't you worried about me?
You're strong so it's fine, Hi-kun.
What do you mean?
Like ridiculously strong!
Manaka-san...
What the heck?
You're still the Manaka-san
that I used to know!
Welcome back, Manaka-san!
I should be the one saying
welcome back, Miuna-chan!
Welcome back!
Everything starts from the sea.
Oshiohshi Fishing Company
Great king squid!
Akira, wait!
Oshiohshi Fishing Company
Whale shark!
Get some good shut-eye?
More like I didn't sleep enough.
Here, your rice.
Thanks.
So Ayakawa's dad hasn't woke up yet?
He's always been a worrywart so
he'll probably continue cold sleeping.
Today's
Yesterday
Salinity Report
I see. So I won't see him for a while.
Yeah, everyone has their own timing.
I guess.
Shrine St.
Dandan St.
Center St.
Nami Middle
Dandan St.
Hm? Manaka's still not here?
Shrine St.
Dandan St.
She said she forgot something,
so we can leave first.
Geez. Let's wait above then.
Dandan St.
Are things still the same
between you two?
Why are you asking suddenly?
You should take her
on a date some time.
You finally know you two
feel the same, after all.
Isn't it gonna be troublesome
if nothing progresses?
Wha—
Everything's fine between us!
Are you going to be like
Chisaki and hope nothing changes?
No, I'm okay if things change.
Oh?
But, it's fine if things
don't change either.
It'll happen on its own.
Yeah, you're right.
kata wo saratta awai shiokaze
The faint sea breeze brushed my shoulder
I wonder if Hi-kun's mad.
Mamaka!
kakeru chiisana senaka wo
as I could do nothing but watch
Akira-kun! You swam here again?
Akari-san's been complaining that you've been visiting ever since you could swim.
Backflip!
boku wa damatte tada mitsumeteta
your small figure run off,
The water's gotten fairly warm,
but you might catch a cold
if you stay too long.
You're not used to this, after all.
fumidasenai hazama de
unable to close the distance between us.
Let's go up together.
yawarakai hizashi tsutsumu kyoushitsu ni wa
Bathed in the soft sunlight, we laugh radiantly
Tsumugu-kun, good morning!
kazatta shashintachi ga waratta mama
in the photographs that hang from our classroom walls.
Mornin'!
Want a ride?
I do!
tomedonai asu ni kawaranai bokutachi wo
We'll be reflected forever by those still waters
You're leaving today, right?
There's just something I wanted to see
before I head back to the university.
nagu minamo no saki doko made mo utsushite
no matter how many tomorrows come.
I wonder if Chi-chan's going to feel lonely.
I'll be coming back during breaks.
I see.
kono mama de ii
We don't have to change.
I like this view of
the ocean from the land.
Just gently hold onto those fragile feelings in our hearts
sono hitomi ni yureteta hakanai omoi mo
That's something you
should tell Hikari, not me.
Wh-What I said just now
has nothing to do with Hi-kun!
sotto shimatte
and hide them away...
Let's meet again!
Again!
nami ga uchiyose hiiteyuku
These waves ebb and flow
When Manaka and Tsumugu met,
I thought they were led by fate.
kokoro kyori hakaru mitai
just like the distance between us.
Hi-kun!
Hey!
But...
Hurry up or we're going to be late!
kimi no kimochi ga shiritai keredo
I want to know how you really feel
Tsumugu, you can stay where you are though!
Get over here, guys!
fureta te wo haratta
but you refuse to let me near.
Fate and destiny don't exist.
Everything begins from your own actions.
I don't look weird, do I?
nobotteku mizu no awa hajike sou na
The time we have to share our dreams
You look great.
Do you think I look more mature like this?
You're fine just the way you are, Sayu.
ayaui toki ga kizamu tagai no yume
is as fleeting and fragile as foam on the waves.
I'm sure Kaname-san would agree too.
While I led my life so far on land,
I fell for someone from the sea.
tomedonai asu ni kawarenai bokutachi wa
We'll remember forever our pasts beyond these still waters,
Good morning.
G-Good morning.
Hey!
nagu minamo no ue tadayou shinkirou
even if our reflections start to waver.
I think Shiodome's gotten prettier lately.
You still haven't given up on her?
mamoritai dake de
''I just want to protect you...''
sou ii kakete tsumaru kotoba ga
I stuttered over those words,
The tears I cried from my first love
dissolved into the gentle sea.
todokanai yuugure no umi
as we watched the sun set over the sea.
Oh, they're here!
Hey!
The sea that took in everything...
Don't rush, Manaka-san—
Manaka!
Thanks, Miuna-chan!
kono sakamichi noboreba hirogaru
Just like the view on top of this hill, things will change,
From now, I'll enter a new life
and make new memories.
nanigenai hibi ga mata chigatte
and each enjoyable day will bring something new.
I'm going to visit my home in the sea,
so I'll be back a little late.
mizukagami terasu hikari hanete
Together, we watch the light dance on the water's surface.
It's fine if you return to the sea, you know.
The miso soup you make is too salty, Grandpa.
I'm worried about your blood pressure.
ima ga tokubetsu ni kanjita
I just want to enjoy this moment.
Today, my mom's going to teach me how
to cook food that's good for your health.
I see.
tomedonai asu ni kawaranai bokutachi wo
We'll be reflected forever by those still waters
Tsumugu, you're going?
I'll go to the station with you.
nagu minamo no saki dokomade mo utsushite
no matter how many tomorrows come.
Okay.
I'll be going.
I'm leaving now.
I'll make sure to come visit
by the end of the month.
All right.
mata sono basho de kagayaku egao mitsuzuketai yo
I'll bring back that dazzling smile of yours when we meet again,
The end of the land
could come at any moment.
And we won't know
what'll happen.
Oshiohshi Fishing Company
Shishio
&
Oshishi's
Joint
Campaign
Sea's fortune and
land's blessing
Shrimps &
Tomatoes
&
Broccoli
Sea Cucumber
Edible Horrors
Squid Salad
But with our will, we can
probably change its course.
kanarazu yakusoku shiyou
I promise you.
Sea God, humans are truly fascinating creatures.
Even if they face pain,
or come across dead ends,
they pick themselves up and
continue moving towards their dreams.
And these feelings even have
the power to overcome the impossible.
It appears the sea snow has stopped falling.
Final Story
The Nature of the Sea,
Land, Wind, our Hearts, and You.
~Earth color of a calm~
Final Story
The Nature of the Sea,
Land, Wind, our Hearts, and You.
~Earth color of a calm~
Hey, do you remember, Hi-kun?
The Sending from five years ago.
There was something you
wanted to tell me after, right?
So you do remember.
You were the one who forgot.
But... even if I don't say it...
I know what you wanted to tell me.
They become one with the sea,
the air, and overcome time.
They're the feelings I wanted to tell you.
This world is brimming
with different kinds of love.