You should kiss!
What?! H-Hold on! What are you...
What do you mean...
Ah!
No! I meant you should kiss Manaka-san!
Huh?! It doesn't matter who! More like why?!
That's because you need to kiss her to wake her up!
That makes absolutely no sense! And why do I have to k-kiss her?
Like I said—
That's absolutely not a reason!
Hi-kun! Don't yell at a girl like that!
Shut up! She's the one saying—
Who are you?
Hi-kun...
M-Mom...
Mom!
The powdered snow falls thick
as these abandoned dreams still
ebb and flow like that day.
I looked at the smile you always had
as the wind that brushed my reddened cheeks
flew high into the sky.
I've always watched you.
So close, yet so far...
Always out of my reach...
"Why?"
I asked with a trembling voice.
The moon that swayed on the rolling waves
said nothing and only watched helplessly.
"Just like me."
My clenched fists hurt.
Story 21
Messenger from
the Ocean Floor
Story 21
Messenger from
the Ocean Floor
I'm going now!
Miuna, you're leaving already?
Oh, she's already gone.
What's up with her? She's not coming with us?
She left pretty quickly.
Hi-kun!
Wait! Don't leave me behind!
Why would I do that?
Anyway, later.
We're going now.
It'll be just for a little bit.
Hikari, don't make Manaka-chan push herself too much, okay?
I won't.
Don't force her to follow you around so much.
You always rush off ahead.
I won't.
And if she starts feeling ill—
All right, I get it.
Manaka-chan, ask Hikari to do whatever you want, okay?
Okay!
Mamaka!
It's been a while for you,
so relax and enjoy your time outside.
Akira will be staying with me at home.
Mamaka!
We won't be gone for long!
Mamaka, Mamaka, Mamaka!
He really likes you.
Likes?
Let's go.
Okay.
Seriously?
You're all finally together.
Huh?
At last, the four from Shishio have gathered.
But that's great.
It's not the same if any of you guys are missing.
Anywho...
A present for you!
Make sure to eat it.
See you guys! Tell Mukaido I said hi!
There's five in here. We have one extra.
Chi-chan! Kaname!
Manaka...
Chi-chan! It's so cold today!
You're seeing her after so long, and that's the first thing you say?
Huh? But it's cold, isn't it?
It's actually summer, you know.
Well yes, it is, but...
How confused can someone be?
I know, right?
I mean you!
Normally, shouldn't you be surprised?
Over... how much people have grown.
Hm? But isn't she just the same as before?
Is Tsumugu not coming?
He's busy with his field work.
So he's out on the ice...
Do you want to go see him?
He's busy, right? I can see him later.
Hey, let's go to the docks instead!
Hurry, hurry!
Sorry about this, Sayu.
My skin was starting to feel dry.
It's freezing!
I don't mind.
So when your Ena dries out, you feel dried out too?
Rather than dried out, it's more like it's hard to breathe.
This is the first time, though.
Sounds like a lot of trouble.
Hikari and the others didn't tell you about that?
Well, they did...
You should've joined them.
They invited you, right?
I shouldn't.
Why not?
I don't feel like I'm good enough.
Good enough? For what?
Just... to go.
You are!
You've done so much for them!
What? Are you unhappy that Manaka-san is back?
No!
She's...
"She's finally awake!" is what I thought,
and I was relieved that I felt that way,
but at the same time,
what I felt was a little different to what I imagined.
I'm not following at all.
I don't know how to face them.
You should've seen your face!
Geez, what was that for?
That's freezing!
I don't have Ena, you know!
Wow!
It really has frozen over.
We can see that from our home too.
But it's so much more shocking to see it up close.
Right, Chi-chan?
The Sending was only a few days ago for you, after all.
Yeah.
What now?
There's so much sea snow!
It didn't pile up this much before.
Yeah, that's true.
This is like playing a game of spot the difference.
Spot the difference?
Yeah.
So cold!
You close your eyes, then open them,
and then point out what's different from before.
Sea snow!
More sea snow!
Come on, you're only pointing out the sea snow.
Manaka!
Oops.
What are you doing?
Hi-kun.
Hi-kun is being nice.
I...
I was always this nice!
Hi-kun's face is red.
Shut up!
Save me, Chi-chan!
There's even sea snow over there!
Running around here isn't safe, Manaka.
It makes you wonder what we were worrying about, y'know?
Huh?
Manaka woke up without us needing Uroko-sama's help.
All's well that ends well.
Yeah, of course.
But it's still pretty anti-climatic.
Look at her.
She's so full of life.
She's been awake less than a day.
What were you like, Hikari?
Huh?
When you had just awakened.
I was frightened.
I was in a town that felt familiar, but at the same time, it wasn't.
I didn't know what I would do if the world I thought I knew had become full of unfamiliar faces.
It was terrifying.
I don't want to see how different things are anymore!
I don't want to think about it!
I don't want to know!
Whee!
How is she able to laugh like that?
Isn't that because you're here?
And the rest of us too.
And here I was, worried she'd just want to see him first...
She... says she doesn't remember.
Hey,
before the Sending... I mean...
What exactly happened after the Sending?
You were pulled to the bottom of the sea,
and then?
Well, there was a voice...
A voice?
Whose voice? Uroko-sama's?
No, not his.
The Sea God's voice?
Maybe.
Did you see him?
Did you meet him?
I don't remember.
Just something about giving. And taking too, I think.
"Taking"? Taking what?
I don't know.
Stop! Manaka, wait!
Even at school,
there's sea snow!
Wow, it's so soft!
She doesn't have her Ena, and she can't return to the sea anymore.
So how...
Hikari...
But it's true.
How is she able to...
She'll always be Manaka.
Right. That's what matters.
From here on is my side!
Then me too!
Too bad, that's taken!
There, there, there, there, and that entire place too has already been claimed!
What are you doing over there?
Hm?
Huh? You guys.
I don't get it.
Why would you want to visit school on a Sunday?
You're one to talk. Why are you here?
What?
W-We're here to study!
Huh?
We were going to study for exams.
Didn't you know? Our finals are next week.
I don't think I wanted to be reminded...
Studying is important.
Very, very important.
What are we learning right now?
For mathematics, we're doing simultaneous equations.
As for English, it's conjunctions and verbal nouns.
I'm not good at either.
Man, there goes my good mood.
I'd get it if it was on arithmetics,
but who uses mathematics these days?
That right there is an excuse only an idiot would give!
Wha—
Yep, that's an excuse.
Huh?!
I believe studying is very important too.
You're saying that?!
Huh? It's important, right, Chi-chan?
Well, it's probably wise to keep up with your studies.
See?
If you don't realize it now, you'll realize it too late.
Too late!
I should head to the hospital now.
To the hospital?
Tsumugu's grandfather was admitted there.
He's fairly old, so yeah...
Oh, that's right.
Take this.
It's from Sayama-kun for everyone.
Salt Cream Puffs
Made with salt full of minerals from Oshiohshi
There's just enough.
Chisaki-san's so nice!
Yeah!
Who wants one?
I do! You want one too, right?
Yeah, I do!
Me too!
Hey, me too!
Naminanami Public Hospital
Q
G
T
I didn't think you'd be here before me.
I was free.
What about you, Tsumugu?
Same, we finished early today.
You should've joined us to see Manaka, then.
I thought she might get overwhelmed if we all showed up at once.
Really now?
How was Mukaido?
Energetic.
Her abundance of energy really surprised me.
She said she'll come visit next time.
I see.
Would you like a mandarin?
Oh, sure.
There's coffee jelly too.
You were awake?
Grandpa remembered my favorite food.
It's delicious!
I think this tastes better than the cream puffs would have.
Why cream puffs?
Just because.
I think I'll be going back to the university at the end of the month.
The professor is being pressured by the board to compile his findings.
Oh.
So when will that be?
Like I said, by the end of the month.
Mm!
What's wrong?
It's sour!
Having something sweet makes everything after that taste sour.
I'll send these to your apartment.
You can share them with your colleagues when you get them.
Okay.
I won't be that far away.
Yeah.
I'll try to come back as soon as I can.
I'll call too.
Yeah.
I'll let you know immediately if I find anything.
Jeez, Tsumugu.
Are you going to be lonely?
No, but you will be.
Wh-What are you saying?
I'm going to have my hands full, too.
Will you be all right?
Like I said, I'm going to be busy now that everyone's back.
I have to take care of Manaka too.
I can't leave her on her own. Manaka's still...
So, don't worry about my end, Tsumugu.
Focus on your research at the university.
You and the professor are the only ones who can do this.
There's still so much we don't understand.
Even though Manaka's awakened,
and Hikari and Kaname seem fine for now,
we don't know much about their situations.
Or even about the sea or land, the Earth's future,
the weather, the tides...
It'd be nice if we could ask Uroko-sama.
Uroko-sama? Why?
He seems like he would know everything about the sea.
Really? I feel like he'd just make up some answers.
But he's a scale of the Sea God.
Technically, yes.
Only technically?
Whether he'd tell us anything is a different story.
He has a twisted humor and a devilish side.
Perverted too.
What about bribing him?
Bribing him? Using money?
No, using adult magazines.
That—
...might work, actually.
Really, really well, actually.
I thought so.
Sorry for returning late.
Oh, welcome back. Good timing.
Huh, why?
Well, I'm not against it.
Daddy. Where's Daddy?
Sure. I'll stay over.
Watch out!
He's going to be late from work.
Don't put the fish in so soon.
It's fine. It'll bring out the flavor.
What did Tsumugu say?
He said that he and Chisaki can't make it.
Eh?
That's too bad.
Why not?
Crab!
He apologized and said it's something related to taking care of his grandfather.
Chi-chan must be really busy.
Tsumugu too.
Those two make sure to study as well.
What do you mean "make sure"?
That makes it sound like we—
Well you don't at all.
Before you know it, there'll be nothing but exams.
I'd rather go back into cold sleep again.
Don't say something foolish like that.
Sayu-chan, please look over how Hikari studies.
I heard you're at the top of your class.
Um, sometimes.
Not just sometimes. It's always!
That's really amazing.
Not really...
But everyone's going to apply for Hama High School, right?
Well, there's no high school in Shishio, anyway.
But I'm perfectly fine as it is.
Here's the crab.
Make sure to blow on it before you eat.
Akira!
Is it hot? Are you okay?
Does it hurt?
I-It's cold.
Sorry for startling everyone.
What if this is making the Sea God angry?
Manaka! Come with me.
Eh?
Just come.
Hi-kun?
What's wrong, Hi-kun?
Are you angry?
There was something you wanted to tell me after the Sending...
I'll tell you after the Sending.
I'll hear you out now.
What was it about?
Don't make such a scary face...
Is it about Tsumugu?
Huh?
So it's not about him?
What are you talking about?
Hi-kun?
Good morning!
Hm? Tsumugu-kun. You're here so early.
Is Mukaido here?
Good morning.
Everyone's up so early—
Huh? Tsumugu, what's wrong?
Fishie!
Tsumugu-kun, that's...
I was cursed. By Uroko-sama.
You were cursed...
That man casts curses on people.
I wouldn't call him a man, though.
But this means that Uroko's nearby.
I play cat's cradle with my silent words
mugon no kotoba de ayatori shite
and tried smiling at my feat.
jouzu ni dekita to waratte miru
The only thing I'm any good at
tokui nano wa dare ni mo kizukarenu you ni
is stifling my heart so no one knows what's in it.
kokoro oshikorosu koto sore hitotsu dake
But this beautiful loop surrounding me
demo torimaku kirei na ruupu wa
very gently winds me in
yowai chikara de taguriyosete kureru kara
and it becomes clear.
azayaka ni
I don't want to let go of these feelings.
musunde kono kimochi goto
Bind them tightly so they can't escape.
hanarenai you ni kataku kataku aa
We are all tied together,
hitomusubi hito wo musunde
heading towards our uncertain future.
kitai no yamanai saki he asu he yukou
You dare crash into a lady and just run off?!
I told you not to follow me!
This isn't good...
Maybe I should... try and confess again.
A confession...
Story 22
That Which Was Lost