Manaka-san...
What’s with you looking so tense?
There’s nothing to be worried about.
But—
Like I said,
Manaka's gonna wake up soon,
just like me and Kaname.
Why wouldn't she?
It's been a week since Manaka-san came back from the sea.
Hey, let's get going.
Everyone held the same hopes in their hearts,
Okay.
Having English for first period is such a drag.
that, just like Kaname-san and Hikari, she would open her eyes from her slumber.
But... Manaka-san shows no sign of waking up.
The powdered snow falls thick
as these abandoned dreams still
ebb and flow like that day.
I looked at the smile you always had
as the wind that brushed my reddened cheeks
flew high into the sky.
I've always watched you.
So close, yet so far...
Always out of my reach...
"Why?"
I asked with a trembling voice.
The moon that swayed on the rolling waves
said nothing and only watched helplessly.
"Just like me."
My clenched fists hurt.
Story 20
Sleeping Beauty
Well everyone, that's all for today.
You may all leave after cleaning duty.
There's quite a lot of homework
this time, but make sure to do it all.
All right! Let's hurry and finish cleaning this place up.
Today I'm definitely going to find that Uroko!
Yup, Uroko-sama might know how to awaken Manaka.
Yeah, he's the one who made us go into the cold sleep after all.
Kaname, hurry up!
Right, sorry about that.
What were you doing? I'm leaving without you.
I was expecting Hikari to be more shaken up about Manaka's situation, but he's being rather positive.
Is Manaka-san by herself during the day?
Mom's taking time off from work at Saya Mart to take care of her.
Really?
Dammit, where's he hiding?
The water's gotten colder than before.
You think so?
It's probably even colder than the day we found Manaka at the village.
What if this is making the Sea God angry?
You wanna leave Manaka here to drown?
The cold's no big deal.
I can just warm myself up a bit on land.
Wait, Hikari! What are you doing? You just came up a minute ago!
Yep, this temperature's not a problem.
Maybe not, but...
It's not, really.
Hm? Chisaki's here too?
She told me she was going to be late because of her training.
Did we pass each other?
Sorry for coming late.
Is something the matter?
I-I'm going to check again.
M-Me too.
Are you okay with not
accompanying them to Shishio?
I thought I should let Hikari and the others work it out themselves.
What's wrong?
I was thinking,
now that we're all around the same age,
it’d be nice if we could spend more time together.
And if we could all get closer to each other, that'd be even better.
You're right.
Hey, what if we do something to stimulate Manaka-san's senses?
Like make her listen to a song? To stimulate her hearing?
That might work!
I wonder where Uroko-sama is.
Miuna-chan said she met him in Shioshishio.
How about we look around the village premises tomorrow, Hikari?
Sure.
The tune was changed, right? It kinda reminds me of the Sending.
This time of day always brings back those memories.
That's it! Manaka knows this song too.
I just thought of something that might work!
Oshiohshi Fishing Company
That's a great idea!
Right? If we can bring back that festival's mood and have her listen to it—
She'd be reminded of that day.
So we thought it might wake her up.
But as of the Sending, there's been quite a few changes to the members at the fishery.
Please, I don't mind if it’s just a few people!
We're grateful for every single person!
Please!
You guys...
I got it. I'll try to contact some of them right now, so give me a moment.
We're back.
We're back!
Welcome back, you two.
Tsumugu, I'm home.
Welcome home. The bath's ready.
Thanks. Take care out there.
Sorry for taking my time. I'm ready to go now.
You really do take your time.
Hikari's late.
He should be with Chisaki-chan and Kaname.
Yeah.
At first, I was worried if those three would get along again, but Chisaki-chan's visiting our place more often.
Now, if only Manaka-chan would open her eyes...
Yeah...
Speaking of those three, it looks like they asked the fishery to record the Hymn for them.
They gathered people from the Sending five years ago to make the recording.
Hopefully, Manaka-chan might wake up if she listens to it.
Itaru-san called me earlier. He sounded so ecstatic about it, even though it wasn't his own idea.
I see...
Welcome back.
Hikari?
Oh. I'm back.
Looks like I let that Uroko slip away from me again today.
Do you want do to today's homework together? There was a lot assigned.
That's right. Everyone in class was complaining about it.
There's just not enough time to do everything. Maybe I should skip school for a while.
What?
That way, I'd have more time to put into other things.
Y-You shouldn't!
Why not?
Because... we're still going through compulsory education!
Why are you getting so serious about that?
Also, Mom would be worried.
Akari isn't my mom.
Maybe so, but you can't just skip school!
If she doesn’t wake up—
What did you just say?
No, I didn't...
Fine, I get it! I get it! You want me to go to school?
Hikari! Wai—
That... That wasn't what I wanted to say to him.
Dammit.
Hi-kun.
Manaka? You're...
I was fine like that, you know.
But now that I've left, the sea and land are starting to freeze over even more.
And so am I...
Where's Hikari?
He already left for the sea.
He said he'll head to school right after.
Ketchup!
Akira, what are you doing?!
As you can see, the tensions created from these conflicts ended the Sengoku Period. And finally, 260 years later—
Don't you think people who force their feelings onto others are the worst?
Library
Q
T
O
Wh-What are you talking about?
I'm talking about the protagonist in this book.
You can't be idling today and reading books that won't help Manaka-san.
I can't help it. I've been sitting here for the past three hours.
Even my attention span is starting to...
Wait, what are you even reading?
A book that might help.
You really think so?
You never know. There might be some helpful hints in here.
Are you really thinking this through?
Yes, I am. And what are you reading?
Me?
Actually, this has been on my mind for a while. It's what the prince usually does.
They kiss the sleeping princess awake.
It's worth a shot.
I think someone should kiss the sleeping Manaka-san.
K-Kiss her?!
I don't think it's unreasonable.
It's possible that someone's strong feelings for another have the power to create change.
Strong feelings?
We know someone who holds such feelings. Like maybe... Hikari.
B-But kissing her based on a theory like that is wrong!
Well, do you have a better idea?
Not... at the moment.
Then what's the problem?
But that's—
Miuna, you sound like you don't want Manaka-san to wake up.
You're the one who said we need to keep looking for clues!
I'm trying my best here.
Do I actually... not want Manaka-san to wake up?
umi no sato ni wa hoihoi
In the village of the sea, here,
Hymn of The Sending
sazanami yosete wa yurayura
the nearing ripples roll on the tide,
hayarasu hikari ga ikue ni mo
oft bringing light, again and again
No good, huh.
Guess I'll keep lookin' for Uroko-sama.
Hymn of The Sending
Here, here.
Ow.
Hymn of The Sending
Geez, Akira!
I do want Manaka-san to wake up. Or at least, that's what I believed at the beginning.
Am I the only one who's feeling differently about this situation?
Manaka!
When did you wake up?
Oh, it's Miuna.
My bad.
Hikari!
Hikari! Hikari?!
He must have been exhausted.
We'll let him off from school tomorrow.
You should head to bed too.
I don't want you to end up like him.
Miuna? Are you still in here?
It's almost time for school.
Miu has a fever too?
Well, let's say she does.
Good morning.
Miuna and Hikari are sick.
So both of them will be absent today?
Um... How are you feeling, Kaname?
You dove into the cold water with Hikari, right?
I'm all right.
I see. I'm glad.
Hikari keeps straining himself.
Miuna and I can help him too, you know.
Get to your seats. Class is starting.
I need to take notes for three people today.
For three?
Miuna's been taking notes in a separate book for Manaka-san this entire time.
Ah, so that's what you mean.
I'll lend a hand with the notes.
Pass me a book.
Miuna, Hikari's sound asleep, so I'm going to take Akira with me out shopping.
Look after the house while we're gone.
He ends up skipping anyway...
Do I really not want Manaka-san to wake up?
This is...
hayarasu hikari ga ikue ni mo
Oft bringing light, again and again
Ow. Geez, Akira!
Hikari feels hot.
Get off me.
Hikari has fever?
I need... to go look for Uroko-sama no matter what.
I'm going to wake Manaka.
I'm...
Hikari was always straight-forward and shining in every aspect.
His feelings for Manaka-san were probably what drew out this side of him.
In comparison, all I am is...
I'm just...
Naminanami Public Hospital
Q
G
T
This is similar to when climbing high altitudes and free diving.
In rare cases, such hazardous environments can stimulate rapid changes of the body.
Your dormant survival instincts respond so the body
can sustain itself— or at least that's what's been reported.
In order to find out why Mukaido-san is losing her Ena, while Shiodome's is growing...
The same goes for your Ena.
When you were suddenly thrown into danger,
your abilities as a sea dweller awakened to protect you.
That's what the professor and I believe, at least.
He'd like to have a talk with you.
Is there a day when he can visit you?
What does she say, Tsumugu? When can I see her?
Ah, well...
Miuna, can you come out right now?
Are you awake?
I...
You had a really high fever. It's gone now, though.
You should thank Miuna. She was looking after you until a bit earlier.
How's Manaka?
She's still the same.
Hikari, I know how you feel, but you need to rely more on people around you.
Really, you're giving me this talk when I'm sick?
You're not the only one who's trying to help Manaka-chan.
I know that.
Do you really?
Oh, Kaname-kun and Sayu-chan brought you those notes
so you won't fall behind in your studies.
Here.
Thank you.
Are you okay with that one?
Yeah. This is one of my favorites.
Am I... that hard to figure out?
What makes you say that?
Well, the guys from Shishio are brimming with emotion.
I always liked that part of them.
You're just like them.
I... don't know. I'm no good.
I'm not like Hikari and the others.
One time, Hikari looked at my Ena and told me that we're the same.
But why...
Why is Manaka-san losing her Ena,
and why do I have it now?
I'm the only one who feels differently about Manaka-san waking up.
I said something to Hikari that hurt him.
If she doesn’t wake up—
I thought about something terrible.
Do I actually... not want Manaka-san to wake up?
You know, I thought that it would be better if those two never came back.
I really did think that.
Eh?
I was scared that Chisaki would disappear from me if they did.
But in the end, I was happy when they returned.
You were happy?
Weird, I know.
But I truly was.
You were scared, but also happy?
Yeah, that's right.
I wonder if I can be happy for them too.
It's hard for you because the two of them are so important to you.
Hikari, of course. And Mukaido too.
I... want to be happy,
and I want to be able to admit that from the very bottom of my heart.
I'm sure you will be.
These are notes for while you are away.
Miuna and the others made them for you.
Hikari.
She'll wake up, right?
Yeah, she definitely will.
Of course.
Hey, Hikari.
Sayu told me about something earlier.
She did?
A person's strong feelings for another have the power to create change.
Something like that can really happen.
And if it's you... I'm sure...
So...
Hmm?
Anyway... You should kiss!
Huh?
You should kiss!
What?! H-Hold on! What are you...
What do you mean...
Ah!
No! I meant you should kiss Manaka-san!
Huh?! It doesn't matter who! More like why?!
That's because you need to kiss her to wake her up!
That makes absolutely no sense! And why do I have to k-kiss her?
Like I said—
That's absolutely not a reason!
Hi-kun! Don't yell at a girl like that!
Shut up! She's the one saying—
Huh?
I play cat's cradle with my silent words
mugon no kotoba de ayatori shite
and tried smiling at my feat.
jouzu ni dekita to waratte miru
The only thing I'm any good at
tokui nano wa dare ni mo kizukarenu you ni
is stifling my heart so no one knows what's in it.
kokoro oshikorosu koto sore hitotsu dake
But this beautiful loop surrounding me
demo torimaku kirei na ruupu wa
very gently winds me in
yowai chikara de taguriyosete kureru kara
and it becomes clear.
azayaka ni
I don't want to let go of these feelings.
musunde kono kimochi goto
Bind them tightly so they can't escape.
hanarenai you ni kataku kataku aa
We are all tied together,
hitomusubi hito wo musunde
heading towards our uncertain future.
kitai no yamanai saki he asu he yukou
How was Mukaido?
Her abundance of energy really surprised me.
How confused can someone be?
She'll always be Manaka.
You're all finally together.
The four from Shishio have gathered.
Story 21
Messenger from
the Ocean Floor
Story 21
Messenger from
the Ocean Floor