The ice is in the way here.
Then we can have two
boats from this shore...
Tomorrow's going to be the day.
All the work was done in a flash with all these adults helping.
Yeah, it really was!
Hey, nice going!
We brought you something to eat.
Okay, thanks.
It's just leftover bread though.
It's more than enough.
You've been helping out, too?
Huh?
Akira-kun...
What's with him lately?
Don't worry about him.
This should do it.
Oh, you dropped by too, Akira.
This is going to be your first time, isn't it?
Well, we haven't had one for a while now.
Wanna see it up close?
Mamaka's...
Yup, this pendant here,
is filled with all of
Manaka-san's love.
Mamaka's love...
Hey!
Akira!
Miuna!
How is it moving so fast?
There aren't even any currents...
It's dissolving!
I love Hi-kun.
I love... Hi-kun?
I knew it.
Tsumugu?
What do you mean, you knew it?
I'd longed for it.
Beyond the sea, beyond the sky...
there was the always-distant sun.
Always shining...
Always bright...
Warm and exciting...
But...
But?
Hi-kun's the sea.
Huh?
When I first left the sea and felt the rays of the sun on land, I was thrilled.
But it was because the sea was there, that I was able to long for the land.
That's what I realized.
If I leave the sea for too long, my Ena dries up,
and it's hard for me to breathe.
Does that mean that you love Hikari?
Why are you crying?
I understand how Chi-chan feels now.
"Don't tell anyone
that I love him," she said.
I don't want you to
tell anyone either.
Are you okay with that?
Why?
Why didn't you tell
us all this time?
Because I was told not to.
Didn't you see how much
pain Hikari was in?
He believed so strongly
that she was in love with you!
He really tried so hard
to bring her back...
Hikari said so himself,
that we would need the person
she loves to bring back her feelings.
So, Hikari's already gone
and made that happen.
I think that love is like the ocean.
Like the ocean?
Not only happiness
and endearment,
but feelings of sorrow
and pain mingle together,
bringing into life new emotions.
They both loved each other...
Story 25
Love is Like an Ocean
Hikari and Manaka-san
loved each other.
If Manaka-san's ability to love
comes back to her at the Sending...
Then...
There's something
we need to discuss.
Do you mind?
I'm sorry, Manaka-san.
No, I'm the one at fault.
It's because I don't
know what "love" is.
Manaka-san?
The sound of waves won't go away.
The sound of waves?
For some reason, when I'm
here like this with you,
I feel a bit better.
Can we stay like this
a little bit longer?
Chisaki,
can I come in?
S-Sure.
What are you doing?
I was thinking I'd adjust the cuffs of
the kimono the Lady will wear tomorrow.
Kaname told me everything.
What?
About how you feel.
What do you mean?
You don't have to
keep it up anymore.
No, I—
And not just for yourself,
but Mukaido too.
Huh?
Manaka and Hikari...
I'm such a terrible person.
I used to hope...
and still do even now,
that Hikari would
always love Manaka,
and that Manaka would
always want to be with Hikari.
Because I didn't want anything
to happen to the four of us.
I wanted Hikari and Manaka
to love each other.
Because that's how things had
always been in our group of four.
But things aren't
that way right now.
It's not because you want to
preserve your group of four,
but because you're in love with me.
That's why you hoped that those two
were in love with each other.
You're overly self-conscious.
Well that's the conclusion I came to.
Was I wrong?
All right then.
I'll have another think.
You've still been thinking about
who it is that I'm in love with?
No, I'm convinced that
you're in love with me.
I just need to figure out how
to make you realize that yourself.
I'm serious about this.
I know.
No denial this time?
Would you let me hold you?
No...
Chisaki.
I can't.
I just can't.
I can't let myself be
the only happy one.
Hikari!
What is it?
Where are you going, Hikari?
It's so late at night...
Oh, I wanted to go
check on the boats.
The boats?
Well, tomorrow's the real deal.
I was worried we'd gone
and missed something.
It would be great if Manaka-san's
ability to love came back again.
Yeah, but that's not the only thing.
It would be good if we can do
something about the land, too.
Yes, but I hope
it does come back.
That's all girls ever think about, huh?
You never see the whole pic—
You're in love with
Manaka-san, aren't you?
What kind of question is that—
You are, aren't you?
Yeah. I am.
Say it again.
What?
Say it again!
Say that you love her!
What? Why?!
Say it!
In return for all I've done for you!
Do you enjoy listening to people say—
Say it. Please.
I'm in love with Manaka.
Again!
I love Manaka!
Again. Again!
All right, that's enough—
Miuna?
Where are you—
Home!
It hurts.
My love for Hikari is in pain.
It's getting worse and worse.
When it gets absolutely unbearable
to the point where I want to scream,
will I...
ever be able to give up on Hikari?
Thank you very much.
Isn't this great, Kihara?
You get to go outside for today.
It's finally here.
Gosh, I'm so nervous.
I should double-check the program.
All right, look up for me.
Okay.
Yep, there we go.
Um, so first Uroko-sama
gives the spirit flame...
It looks a lot more complicated this time round
without the help from the guys in the sea.
Akira-kun!
You know, I realized I'd
forgotten to tell you something.
Thank you for your letter.
Kanchou!
Does love mean to be thankful?
I knew that outfit would look better
on you once you were older.
Kaname...
Um...
Hm?
Thanks.
For what I told Tsumugu?
For everything.
Chisaki, you're not having
any strange ideas, are you?
Huh?
Like "I should be the replacement
for the Lady this time."
We were all together for so long.
But I was alone on land, all that time.
You can't.
Kaname...
You can't, okay?
All right!
Uroko-sama has arrived!
This way, Uroko-sama.
Honestly, squeezing me into
a cramped space like that...
This will do quite nicely.
Quit acting so
high and mighty.
But I am high and mighty.
It's to be expected.
Is that the Lady?
It looks less and less like her every time.
I heard the first Lady was very beautiful.
No, not in the slightest.
She was short, and covered in freckles.
Not the healthiest girl, either.
She is spoken of as a great sacrifice,
but to her people, she was likely just a convienient castaway.
Hey, you were in love
with her, weren't you?
Yes, I suppose I was.
You said that you were the same as the
Sea God right until you broke away, didn't you?
Did you ever regret sending
the Lady back to the land?
I was but a scale on his shoulderblade.
If it had been on his right hand,
I may have been able to stroke her hair.
Or if it were his left hand,
I may have been able to hold her waist.
But the moment I became separated,
I was no longer a part of him.
I was simply a scale.
A shoulder blade's scale, at that.
What could I possibly
tell about the Lady?
Uroko-sama! Would you do us the honor
of beginning the ceremony?
Show me, Hikari.
What are you able to change,
and what can not be changed.
Look, there's Hikari with everyone!
Good luck!
umi no sato ni wa hoihoi
In the village of the sea, here,
sazanami yosete wa yurayura
the nearing ripples sway over the tide,
hayarasu hikari ga ikue ni mo
oft bringing light, again and again.
Sea God,
how will you answer to
the efforts of these children?
umigamisama no megumi de
With the sea god's blessings,
kyou mo kagayaku hoihoi
the days are yet bright, here.
umi no yoru ni wa hoihoi
In the night at sea, here,
konbu mo wakame mo yurayura
where the kelp and seaweed sway in the tide,
O Sea God, under your
sacred and benevolent gaze,
we, the people from Shioshishio
ebi ya umiushi iwama ni nozoki
shrimps and sea slugs peer among the rocks.
since the beginnings of time,
have respected, worshipped,
and served you as our sole deity.
Our mighty and divine Sea God,
we pray for the protection, blessings,
and wealth of our descendents.
umigamisama no mamori de
With the sea god's protection,
A storm is brewing.
yasuragi nemuru yo hoihoi
we are at peace, here.
The sea...
Manaka!
Manaka-san!
I have to save her!
Manaka doesn't have any Ena!
Chisaki!
Guys!
Kaname...
Everyone, hold onto the boat!
Grab on and don't fall off!
What?
Mamaka!
Miuna! Save Manaka!
Hikari!
The sea's so suffocating.
It's violent. It hurts!
I'm terrified.
The sea that's kept me safe for so long...
Manaka-san!
Miuna-chan!
The sea is reacting to Miuna's feelings.
What?
Mukaido loves Hikari.
And so does Miuna.
Mukaido's feelings are
closely related to Miuna's.
So, the feelings drifting in
the waters are coming to life!
Manaka-san!
I know. I can understand how you feel.
I knew it.
When I'm like this with you,
I feel really safe.
That's because my Ena
is screaming "I love Hikari."
What?
Not just Hikari.
It's screaming that it loves
the sea, and everyone in it.
Manaka!
Chisaki, take Manaka!
Hikari!
This presence...
That's...
The graveyard of Ladies?
Miuna!
You sea god bastard!
Hikari!
I love Hi-kun.
I love Hikari.
I love Hikari very much.
Very... much...
Miuna!
I play cat's cradle with my silent words
mugon no kotoba de ayatori shite
and tried smiling at my feat.
jouzu ni dekita to waratte miru
The only thing I'm any good at
tokui nano wa dare ni mo kizukarenu you ni
is stifling my heart so no one knows what's in it.
kokoro oshikorosu koto sore hitotsu dake
But this beautiful loop surrounding me
demo torimaku kirei na ruupu wa
very gently winds me in
yowai chikara de taguriyosete kureru kara
and it becomes clear.
azayaka ni
I don't want to let go of these feelings.
musunde kono kimochi goto
Bind them tightly so they can't escape.
hanarenai you ni kataku kataku aa
We are all tied together,
hitomusubi hito wo musunde
heading towards our uncertain future.
kitai no yamanai saki he asu he yukou
Love is like an ocean.
If I hadn't fallen in love...
I'm glad I fell in love...
Miuna, a beautiful ocean.
The once calm sea is now stirring!
Final Story
The Nature of the Sea, Land, Wind, our Hearts, and You.
~Earth color of a calm~
Final Story
The Nature of the Sea, Land, Wind, our Hearts, and You.
~Earth color of a calm~