That Iizuka guy keeps offering to carry Manaka-san's bag for her.
You can totally see right through him.
Geez, you're always so quick
to judge people, Sayu.
Manaka-san?
Hm?
You look a bit pale.
Isn't that Hikari?
Huh?
Hi-kun!
That's... the stone.
Yeah, Miuna-chan made this for me.
So I won't lose it.
Won't... lose it?
Over these past five years,
I've always been watching
you from your side.
And just like how I learned about the ocean by living alongside it,
I began to understand more about you.
When you were feeling upset,
when you wanted to laugh, or even cry,
I became able to tell.
And now, I can tell
that you have feelings for me.
Or, am I wrong?
Let me go!
If I'm wrong, I'll let you go.
Tsumugu...
But if I'm not...
Stop it!
I don't feel that way about you, Tsumugu!
Our feelings are floating aimlessly.
The powdered snow falls thick
as these abandoned dreams still
ebb and flow like that day.
I looked at the smile you always had
as the wind that brushed my reddened cheeks
flew high into the sky.
I've always watched you.
So close, yet so far...
Always out of my reach...
"Why?"
I asked with a trembling voice.
The moon that swayed on the rolling waves
said nothing and only watched helplessly.
"Just like me."
My clenched fists hurt.
Story 24
Detritus
It's been only five years.
I've only spent five years with Tsumugu.
But I've been with Hikari
and the others since we were born.
So...
How is it that in just five years...
Tsumugu?
Huh?
You haven't changed at all.
When it comes to someone you love,
you're not quite yourself.
If you're okay with it,
you can tell me about how you feel.
If that helps in any way...
Don't worry about my feelings.
Kaname...
I've always been watching
from the sidelines, anyway.
I knew that even if it didn't
work out between you and Hikari,
the next in line wouldn't
be me, but Tsumugu.
No, you're wrong!
I don't love him!
I... can't fall for Tsumugu.
If I were to fall for
anyone other than Hikari,
I knew it would be unfair to everyone,
everyone that is frozen
in time while they sleep.
That's why I always told
myself that I loved Hikari,
so I wouldn't ever forget about them.
When Hikari came back,
I was so scared.
Not just because I was the
only one who had grown up,
but because I was scared
that he would see me differently.
Still, Hikari told me
that nothing would change.
That made me so happy.
Because it made me believe
that I had been faithful to Hikari
even after all that time.
But...
It's all right.
All of us are here now.
We've returned.
There's no need for you
to deny your feelings.
Manaka loves Tsumugu...
But in order to open her heart,
I can't accept Tsumugu's feelings.
Manaka has nothing to do with this.
She does!
You're as stubborn as always.
I'm hearing...
the sound of waves again.
Are you out, Manaka-chan?
Can I come in?
Ah, yes.
Akira here wrote a letter
at his kindergarten for you.
Would you read it?
A letter?
You're giving it to me?
I love you, Manaka
I love you, Manaka...
As his mother I feel a bit conflicted,
but I'm glad he's attached to you.
Would you accept his letter?
What are you turning red for?
Right, Manaka-chan?
Manaka-chan?
Ouch, rejected, huh?
It'll be fine, don't worry, Akira!
Be more ambitious!
That's right.
The first letter "A" in your name
stands for "Ambitious!"
I love you, Manaka
/\/\/\/\/\/\/\/\/\/\
What... am I feeling?
What is this?
It's unbearable.
It's loud.
Terribly... loud.
No matter how much
it would hurt him,
Hikari's thinking about how
to bring Manaka's feelings back.
Is there anything I can do?
Miuna.
Y-Yes?
Manaka's pendant...
I hate to admit it,
but I owe a lot to you.
Why is that something
you hate to say?
I dunno.
But you made me that flag, and it was thanks
to you that we got to Shioshishio, too.
It's like I have to see you
in a different light now.
I kinda get the feeling that I'll always
be in your debt, or something.
That bad, huh?
What's wrong with that?
This isn't like you.
I guess you'll do anything
if it's for Manaka-san, huh?
What? What are you implying?
The very least I can do for the person Hikari cares so much for...
We should get to bed.
R-Right. Goodnight.
...is to hide away
my feelings from Hikari.
Good morning, Hi-kun!
Morning.
Good morning.
Here you go.
A nice, big helping.
Thanks.
Huh? Where's Miuna?
She said something about
needing to go to school early.
And Akari and Akira?
Something about going
to kindergarten early.
What the heck?
I can't hear it this morning.
Hmm?
Hi-kun, who do you love?
Wh-What kind of question is that?
I don't really understand
what "love" means.
It's so strange.
I think I love everyone,
but, I'm not so sure either.
Why?
Hmm?
Well, that's just one of those things.
What things?
Y'know, those things.
In any case, don't let it get to you.
It'll all be fine in the end.
What do you mean, "fine"?
By "fine", I mean "fine"!
What? That doesn't explain anything!
Don't let that bother you.
Naminanami Public Hospital
Q
G
T
You look healthy today.
Yeah.
Would you mind if I moved out
into a dorm from next year?
I talked to the doctor, and he said
that there was a vacancy.
I'll pay for the rent
through a part time job.
So...
Do whatever you want.
Okay.
Grandpa,
about the legend you
told me the other day...
After having something important
taken from her by the sea god,
what happened to the Lady
once she was returned to the land?
Her lover was already dead.
What?
He dove into the sea
in search of her and drowned.
A-And?
There was no one else waiting
for the Lady's return on land.
That's all.
Tsumugu.
On your way home?
Y-Yeah.
Is that hand-made?
Is it that easy to tell?
Don't say that.
It's wonderful.
The red sea slug
would be very proud.
Red sea slug?
You mean the one that
will grant you a wish?
Wow, you really do
know a lot about the sea.
Hikari, Kaname,
come here for a second.
We need to talk man-to-man.
Man-to-man?
Could you put a
curse on me again?
I have less of a desire to do so
when you request it so earnestly.
I guess you would.
What? You dragged us along
for something like that?
The Sending.
If we were to offer another Lady,
would the land return to normal?
And by doing so, Mukaido's
feelings could return, too.
Wait, but what does the Sending have to do with Manaka—
Detritus.
The remains of plankton, and other
microorganisms are present in the sea.
I felt it when my Ena awakened.
The mass of emotions
floating in the sea, like detritus.
"Mass of emotions"?
Is that what you meant by the sea god's
emotions dissolving throughout the sea?
It wasn't just the sea god.
I'm not sure if it was from the people
at Shishio, or from the swimming fish,
but amongst the nameless,
ageless fragments of emotions,
I felt a very familiar presence.
I'm sure that was Mukaido's feelings.
Oh?
You said that because
Mukaido became the sacrifice,
the sea god's emotions became one
with his consciousness, creating equilibrium.
If that's the case,
we should send another sacrifice—
Hey! Are you suggesting
we send Manaka again?
That pendant.
If that really does hold
Mukaido's feelings within it,
we can just place it on a wooden Lady
in place of Mukaido, can't we?
If we can trick the sea god into thinking
that Mukaido has come back to him,
he may return the feelings
he took from her.
Do you have any idea
what you're saying?
It's a long-shot!
We have to try.
Will you help us?
Wait, what if nothing ends up happening
after we get all those people involved?
It's all or nothing.
There'd be no point otherwise.
Still...
You said exactly the same thing
five years ago, Hikari.
Very well, this sounds amusing.
I'll lend you a hand.
Uroko-sama!
However, a Sending carried out with only
the powers of the land is at best, an imitation.
Are you satisfied with just that?
Of course.
It's better to try than
not try anything at all.
Thank you.
We're doing it again this year.
We're having a Sending!
We appreciate your support.
Wow, there's so many
people here already.
Everyone had actually
wanted to do it again.
Yo!
Huh? You're...
Man, you're totally still a kid!
Talk about a shock!
Egawa-kun!
I brought along my wife.
Hello, nice to meet you.
I contacted all the people
who had moved away, too.
We're here!
It's been so long!
Everyone!
Hey, Sayama.
Grab a hold of that.
You're just as bossy as ever.
This brings back
so many memories!
This is so fun,
right, Hi-kun?
How's the costume going?
Will this really work as
a replacement for the Lady?
We won't know
for sure until we try.
Right.
The whole five years I was on land,
Manaka was being
a substitute for the Lady...
So this time, maybe I—
Chisaki!
You're ditching?
So you're in love
with Chisaki-san...
Oops, you got me.
You thickhead!
You go and put on a face
like nothing is wrong...
You confessed to her, didn't you?
You heard that as well, huh?
Of course I did!
I don't know whether
you were rejected or not,
but you have to be more
upfront about how you feel!
You have to, you know,
show Chisaki-san that pained look
on your face you had back there!
I show it to her,
and then what?
Even if she were to understand me,
the way the two of us are now...
It'd be no different to how
Akari tries to comfort Hikari.
And I wouldn't be able to take that.
I've wondered before what
I'd be doing if I hadn't cold slept,
but I guess it wouldn't
have made a difference.
Chisaki even had an eye
for Tsumugu five years ago.
I've always been watching
from the sidelines.
It was always someone other
than me that Chisaki had eyes for.
I was just—
Quit sounding like a tragic heroine!
"Heroine"?
Wouldn't I be the hero?
You're just the same as Chisaki!
What?
I... I've always been watching you.
I've...
I've always had eyes for you!
I've been waiting for so long!
Because of you, I worked hard.
Just so I could match up to you,
so I wouldn't be treated
like a child by you,
but most of all,
so you would see me as a girl,
I kept you here the whole
time you were gone.
I kept you right here!
I see...
Huh?
I...
was in your heart the whole time.
Honestly, I was lonely.
Hikari had Akari's family
waiting for him on land,
and Chisaki had Tsumugu's family,
but I was sure that there was
no-one who was waiting for me.
What? That's such a childish worry.
Well, I am a child.
Did I disappoint you?
This is what your
crush is really like.
Don't put yourself down like that!
It'd be best for me to give you
an answer, wouldn't it?
It's going to be no anyway, right?
Well, I could only
see Chisaki until now,
I know that!
Forget it!
But from now on, Sayu-chan,
I'll make sure to
give you my attention.
Not as a little girl,
but as a girl of my own age.
Would it be okay to start this
from that first step?
That's a rather pretentious answer.
Hey...
Yes?
Thank you.
Hikari!
I'm headin' back now!
Right! Do you mind dropping
off Miuna on the way?
Sure thing. Hop in!
But...
See you tomorrow.
Well, today, I guess.
Thank you.
No problem.
You're still here?
The sunrise was too beautiful.
I see.
Hi-kun, you look a bit down.
Yeah, well,
a lot has changed since that day.
So, I'm kinda scared this time around.
I'm looking forward to it though.
Manaka...
I don't know how it's going to turn out,
but I get to be with everyone,
and being with everyone is fun!
I see.
Y'know, I have someone that I like.
Really?
Yeah.
That's great! You can tell me, then—
what it's like to "love" someone!
Oh, who is it, anyway?
That's not something
I can just tell you.
Oh, I see. That's a shame. Sorry.
Don't worry, you'll understand soon.
Yup, as soon as the Sending is over.
The Sending?
Let's make this a good one.
I'll be waving that flag
with all my strength.
Flag?
Sure!
I play cat's cradle with my silent words
mugon no kotoba de ayatori shite
and tried smiling at my feat.
jouzu ni dekita to waratte miru
The only thing I'm any good at
tokui nano wa dare ni mo kizukarenu you ni
is stifling my heart so no one knows what's in it.
kokoro oshikorosu koto sore hitotsu dake
But this beautiful loop surrounding me
demo torimaku kirei na ruupu wa
very gently winds me in
yowai chikara de taguriyosete kureru kara
and it becomes clear.
azayaka ni
I don't want to let go of these feelings.
musunde kono kimochi goto
Bind them tightly so they can't escape.
hanarenai you ni kataku kataku aa
We are all tied together,
hitomusubi hito wo musunde
heading towards our uncertain future.
kitai no yamanai saki he asu he yukou
Mamaka's love...
Manaka-san's love...
The sound of the ocean won't go away.
It hurts!
I love Manaka.
Love is...
Love is like the ocean.
Story 25
Love is Like an Ocean