Oh my, that looks delicious.
Miuna-chan!
I-I'm going to go take a bath!
This isn't helping...
The powdered snow falls thick
as these abandoned dreams still
ebb and flow like that day.
I looked at the smile you always had
as the wind that brushed my reddened cheeks
flew high into the sky.
I've always watched you.
So close, yet so far...
Always out of my reach...
"Why?"
I asked with a trembling voice.
The moon that swayed on the rolling waves
said nothing and only watched helplessly.
"Just like me."
My clenched fists hurt.
Story 22
That Which Was Lost
Uroko-sama!
Uroko-sama, where are you?
Are you sure he's on land?
Tsumugu never went into the ocean.
But, he still got cursed with that fish.
That means that Uroko-sama's in Oshioshi somewhere.
But where?
How would I know?
Uroko-sama!
Hey!
Oh come on, he's not like a stray animal.
Man, this is gross!
You don't have to look through it!
Is this going to be enough?
Sayu?
Manaka-san?
Will he really fall for something like this?
Yup, he should.
What are the two of you doing?
We're setting up the adult magazine we found at the beach.
Uroko-sama likes these kinds of things, you see.
Also,
You were making that for Uroko-sama?
Yup.
I made sure to cook the bamboo shoots, carrots and chicken separately!
Let's have a taste.
It's delicious!
My grandmother's is much better, though.
One more!
It turned out nicely.
With both of these, Uroko-sama's sure to turn up!
Yup, he definitely will!
Like I said, he's not some stray animal...
He eats food that's been on the ground like one, though.
What? Really?!
He sounds like one of those sleazy old men with hair growing on their knuckles!
He doesn't have hair growing there,
but he has scales on his chest and arms.
Really? That sure fits for someone who's called "Uroko-sama."
There was something you wanted to tell me after the Sending...
I'll hear you out now.
What was it about?
Is it about Tsumugu?
Huh?
So it's not about him?
What are you talking about?
What are you staring at so casually?
Nothing.
It's snowing.
The sea snow falling from the sky had become a regular sight around here,
and according to the news on TV,
it had started to fall even in towns and cities far from the coast.
Where could he be hiding...
We're getting nowhere without any leads.
Isn't there anything on land that could have some connection to him?
Um, well...
No idea.
What about you, Miuna?
What is it?
Well, I know of an old abandoned temple.
You'll be going back to the university, right?
It's south of the beach.
Is it okay for you to be here?
But it's so run-down and deserted.
Finding Uroko-sama falls into my research too.
That doesn't really have a connection to Uroko-sama, then.
He sounds like he's farting!
Yours did, too.
Remember when you had one on your knee and really hated it?
Yup!
Maybe it's hungry.
I'll go feed it.
It eats food?
Yes. Want to come look?
Yuck.
I wanna see!
Sayu?
Let's take a break.
I'll go make us some tea.
I'll help you.
Wow! It's snowing so heavily!
I wonder if Uroko-sama ate the food we left him...
Um, did you have a fish like that before, too?
Yup! It was so freaky!
Even after it left, you lied and said that it was still there.
Hmm?
Imitating it would be pretty funny!
Oh my god! It ate it!
It's just like a frog.
Here!
Those rice cakes were from a patient I looked after.
This is fun!
Oh? So a present from a man?
Come on, don't put it that way.
You're so popular.
Shut up. He was an old man.
I'm still kinda jealous.
Maybe I should... try and confess again.
Just kidding.
A little while after that,
Mihashi-sensei went back to the university, though a little earlier than planned.
Due to the bad weather,
his investigation was behind schedule,
and with the increasing amount of risk involved, he was asked to return to the university.
You didn't have to come see me off.
This is from Chisaki.
"Please eat it on the train," she said.
Oh my, how nice of her.
Thanks.
I tried telling them that it was all the more important I stayed because of these worsening conditions...
Is the sea snow that much worse than before?
It said on the news that even further inland,
the southern winds were making the snow worse,
even blocking roads and causing power outages.
Are you going to leave too, Tsumugu-kun?
No, I'll be here for a little longer.
Adult
T
H
Child
T
I see.
Well then,
there's still time before the sun sets.
I guess I'll keep looking for Uroko.
I'll come too!
Sayu, let's go with them.
Sure.
Are you staying because of Chisaki?
Yeah.
I thought you'd say it was because of your research or something.
There's no point in that.
I'd like a straight answer, in the end.
Me too.
Don't you think Hikari and Manaka-san have been acting weird lately?
Sayu?
Shiodome. What are you doing?
Nothing much.
Right.
They said that it's going to snow again.
You might want to head home early.
Right. Thanks.
Bye.
Miuna, Minegishi confessed to you, didn't he?
Wh-Why are you asking that all of a sudden?
A confession...
Hi-kun, Hi-kun!
The food and the magazine are gone!
It must have been Uroko-sama.
You can't say that for sure.
Some dirty old man could have taken it.
No, it must have been Uroko-sama.
He is on land!
We'll find him for sure!
Uroko-sama!
Where are you?
He's nowhere to be seen...
I raced against Tsumugu...
Huh?
Then I crashed, and hurt myself.
Ready?
Hi-kun!
You dove straight into that pool for me.
You don't remember that, either...
What else have you forgotten?
Did you only pretend to remember about the fish on your knee?
No, I remember that!
I really do.
But...
But what?
But I don't remember lying about it still being there.
S-Sorry!
I didn't want to make you and everyone else worried!
You don't remember?
Well, but I do remember how we all made the Lady together!
Don't worry about it!
I'm probably still waking up.
The time we...
The time we were told not to go back on land because it was dangerous,
I...
I hugged you.
Or that time we visited Nami Middle before we had to enter cold sleep...
I said...
I said that I loved you.
I don't understand that!
You...
You don't remember any of that?
Hi-kun?
Hey, Octo-head!
You dare crash into a lady and just run off?!
Hikari...
Hey, Miuna?
Miuna!
Where are you going, Hikari?
Hey, Hikari!
Don't follow me!
Huh?
I told you not to follow me!
Hikari!
Ow...
Geez, what are you doing?
Sorry.
Th-Thanks.
What?
There was a shrine around here?
The heck is this?
That's the magazine Sayu had for Uroko-sama...
Unbelievable.
You all must think very poorly of me to try and lure me out using that.
Uroko-sama!
Go and tell Mukaido's grandaughter—
Manaka, wasn't it?
That she's still far from matching the old woman's cooking.
Since when did you become a land dweller?
It is my duty to watch over those from the sea.
However, everyone is asleep at the moment. I've too much time to spare.
So you were watching those of us who had awakened?
You could have shown yourself to us then!
I am but a scale of the Sea God.
I am not as free to do my bidding here as I am at sea.
What a splendid smell.
You smell like a female.
What do you think you're saying?!
I failed to notice the last time,
but your Ena has developed marvellously.
R-Really?
Cut that out, you sleaze!
So? What do you want?
You sought me out to ask me of something, did you not?
Oh yeah. Right.
Uroko-sama, what's happening to the land?
Is the weather going to keep getting worse?
Also, what about everyone at Shishio?
When are they going to wake up?
Is that all you have to ask of me?
Manaka.
What happened to Manaka?
Will she never be able to go back to the ocean?
And...
she's forgotten about so many things that have happened before.
What's happened to her?!
She has become the Lady.
The Lady?
The girl who was sacrificed to the sea god and came to bear his children.
She had left behind her lover back on land.
Unable to leave those memories behind, she fell into despair.
So the Sea God, realizing this,
returned her to the land which she pined for.
But not before she forfeited something in exchange.
I'm well aware of that legend.
The sea god took her Ena, didn't he?
What about it?
The Lady returned to land, and generations passed.
Eventually, the Sea God himself passed away,
and his body effused throughout the ocean waters.
A scale which had separated at that moment came to become me.
To this day, those tiny fragments of the Sea God's emotions are drifting about in the ocean.
Fragments... of his emotions?
Neither of good nor evil—
animosity,
agony,
ecstasy,
and envy.
Uninhibited and sincere emotions.
The spirit flame is also a part of him, but that is more concrete...
it is similar to his consciousness, you could say.
It wishes to supress the calamities that will befall the land and sea.
However, his fragments floating through the sea are sensitive to human emotion,
and at times act on their own,
causing the ocean to react violently.
Manaka was pulled into one of those episodes on that day, and became a human sacrifice.
It seems that the sea god's feelings of longing towards the Lady still remained within those fragments.
Wrapped in a thick blanket of Ena, Manaka lay as the sacrificial girl in the graveyard of Ladies.
Because of that, the sea was calmed,
and the calamity to befall the earth was halted.
The fragments in the sea merged with the spirit flame's consciousness,
achieving absolute harmony.
Unfortunately,
Manaka's innate emotions could not accept her fate as the sacrifice, and she sought freedom.
Those emotions crumbled her Ena, which trickled away,
creating a very faint current.
That current that lead us to Shioshishio?
The tiny grains of Manaka's Ena brushed against each other as they drifted,
creating the sound that the girl from land heard.
So that means...
That sound was Manaka-san's Ena—
no, it was her feelings!
Where are Miuna and Hikari-kun?
They're not back yet.
I wonder what they're up to...
They're not kids anymore.
Stop worrying!
When the three of you came to search for Manaka,
the fragments of the sea god's emotions sensed that he was being robbed of his Lady once again,
so once again, took something away from her in exchange.
Mamaka! Roar!
And at that moment, what was left of Manaka's Ena completely crumbled away.
The sea was calmed because Manaka became the sacrifice.
Since that is no longer the case, I believe the calamity on land will continue, if not accelerate.
What?
Are you telling me that it's Manaka's fault that the land is becoming like this?
Are you saying that it would have been better to just leave her there forever?!
What?
What the hell is that?!
Do not be so distraught.
Even if it were to quicken, the end would not ocurr until generations and generations after you die.
W-Wait!
You said that something was taken from her,
and then what was left of her Ena was destroyed!
So, her Ena wasn't what she forfeited?
Wait...
Then, what exactly did she...
Hikari.
You are in love with Manaka, are you not?
What does that have to do with anything right now?!
Your feelings towards her may never, ever reach her heart.
No—
no one's feelings will.
Are you kidding me?!
Hikari!
For what Manaka forfeited...
was...
Roar! Bang!
That was...
a heart capable of loving again.
All right, how about this?
That won't have any effect on me!
Take this!
Manaka is no longer able to love anyone again.
You got me!
Oh, welcome home, Miuna-chan, Hi-kun.
I play cat's cradle with my silent words
mugon no kotoba de ayatori shite
and tried smiling at my feat.
jouzu ni dekita to waratte miru
The only thing I'm any good at
tokui nano wa dare ni mo kizukarenu you ni
is stifling my heart so no one knows what's in it.
kokoro oshikorosu koto sore hitotsu dake
But this beautiful loop surrounding me
demo torimaku kirei na ruupu wa
very gently winds me in
yowai chikara de taguriyosete kureru kara
and it becomes clear.
azayaka ni
I don't want to let go of these feelings.
musunde kono kimochi goto
Bind them tightly so they can't escape.
hanarenai you ni kataku kataku aa
We are all tied together,
hitomusubi hito wo musunde
heading towards our uncertain future.
kitai no yamanai saki he asu he yukou
Are you doubting Manaka's feelings?!
You can't go and decide it's better not to love at all!
Manaka looks happy enough as she is now.
If you lost the ability to love...
I won't lose it!
Story 23
Whose Feelings
Are These
Story 23
Whose Feelings
Are These
Won't... lose it...