I stepped...
on your shadow!
Now I'm "it!"
Come get me! I'll be the crab!
Step, step on the crab.
Step! Step!
What do we do to help Manaka?!
How do we bring back her ability to love someone?
There's no answer to that.
It may return in due time,
or it may never return.
No way...
Hikari, you should know very well by now.
There are things in this world that you simply can do nothing about.
I've stepped on Hi-kun's shadow!
Step!
Hikari!
Dad wants me to pick up some packages for him.
Can you come to the fishery with me?
Ah, sure.
Want me to come too?
We should be fine.
Instead, could you watch over Akira?
Okay!
'Kay, 'kay!
The powdered snow falls thick
as these abandoned dreams still
ebb and flow like that day.
I looked at the smile you always had
as the wind that brushed my reddened cheeks
flew high into the sky.
I've always watched you.
So close, yet so far...
Always out of my reach...
"Why?"
I asked with a trembling voice.
The moon that swayed on the rolling waves
said nothing and only watched helplessly.
"Just like me."
My clenched fists hurt.
Story 23
Whose Feelings
Are These
Story 23
Whose Feelings
Are These
You don't need to act all mature.
Huh?
I know you noticed and helped me out back there.
So, thanks.
You've been such a crybaby lately.
So I need to be the adult for you.
Shut up.
She said that...
she would tell me something.
She said she would tell me
after the Sending was over.
Oh... I see.
I've been thinking about what it might've been.
Like maybe...
she wanted to talk about confessing to Tsumugu.
Why are you thinking like that?!
Normally, something like that would mean...
Um...
She wanted to confess to...
...me, you're saying?
That wouldn't happen.
What?
Thank You, Namiji Middle School
\/|\/|\/|\/|\/|\/|\/|\/|\/|\/|\/|\/|
No way. I'm certain of that.
You're certain...
Let's talk with everyone
about what Uroko-sama said.
With everyone?
Including Manaka-san.
Manaka too?
Yeah.
After all, this is about her.
If I were Manaka-san, I'd want to know too!
That's the one thing I refuse to let happen.
Is that also "certain"?
A heart capable of loving...
There isn't anything we can do about the sacrifice...
But for Manaka...
We might be able to!
I want all of us to think of something.
Is thinking going to do any good?
We're talking about feelings here.
This is different to trying to look for the village,
or trying to wake up Mukaido.
But still...
We can't leave her like this!
To be honest,
is losing the ability to love someone that bad?
Manaka looks happy enough as she is now.
She doesn't look inconvenienced from what she's lost, either.
That's not the issue here!
What do you think, Chisaki?
Huh?
Well, I think...
If it were me, I might actually feel a little relieved.
Chisaki!
Look, at any rate,
this sort of thing depends on the person.
Unlike before,
this isn't something we can all decide by ourselv—
Don't you decide that!
Sayu?
You can't go and decide it's better not to love at all!
Don't talk for everyone!
You haven't even asked Manaka-san!
Sayu-chan...
What's wrong with you?!
Better not to love? Stop acting so grown-up!
You're still just a kid!
What an idiot!
Sayu!
You know...
The three of you are so distant now.
It's disgusting.
Gosh, he pissed me off there.
Sayu!
He's an idiot!
Love is important!
We need love!
Right, Miuna?
Wait up!
You left everyone?
Yeah, we're done for today.
Geez, that idiot Kaname.
Don't call him an idiot!
But you just called him one.
It's different when I say it!
What?
I'm leaving. I've got homework to do.
Bye-bye.
Talk about a load of nonsense.
Sayu...
There they are!
There!
Akira-kun said he wanted to pick you two up.
I-Is that so?
Danger
Entry Prohibited
planned demolition in a few days
Nyaa...
Nyaa!
Hey, Akira!
This is why we can't go back home quickly when you're with us.
Oh.
Nyaa! Nyaa!
Hey, it's fine once in a while.
Manaka-san?
Over there.
I wonder what that shiny thing is.
Wait here a moment.
A rock.
Isn't this is from a red sea slug?
How rare!
That's right.
I remember telling something to a red sea slug once...
What was it?
Huh? What was it?
I can't recall that part.
Hikari?
Well, this stone y'see,
when you ask a red sea slug about something that's on your mind,
it spits out your fortune.
If it spits out a white stone, your wish will come true.
I think... mine was "true."
It'd spit out a black stone otherwise.
Here, you should keep this.
Huh?
Keep it very, very safe!
O-Okay.
That stone is her fortune.
How are you able to tell?
I just can.
Its color and shape,
how it's pudgy and looks unathletic.
You're saying a stone can be unathletic?
Manaka couldn't remember what she asked the red sea slug.
Yeah.
So what she asked the sea slug
was somehow related to her feeling of love for someone.
I see.
There's no choice but to ask Tsumugu.
Huh?
If it's a feeling so strong that you would ask a red sea slug,
surely she'd be able to remember it.
If the person she loves helps out, surely.
Hikari...
But let's say,
if Manaka's true feelings come back,
and...
And what?
Nothing!
Just, I kind of understand what Chisaki-san and Kaname-san said earlier.
That's all.
Oh, you mean that?
"If you didn't love anyone,
you wouldn't have to be sad."
Right?
Huh?
You said that the other day.
Well, five years ago.
If I didn't love her, I wouldn't have to be sad!
We don't really know what's going to happen.
What Kaname and Chisaki said might be right,
and it might be better without those feelings.
But you know,
I can't agree when I look at your family.
You're the ones who taught me, after all.
Huh?
Because you loved Akari so much,
I'm able to see this happy scene in front of me now.
So, I want Manaka to feel it again.
What it's like to love someone.
Hikari...
Manaka-san,
I just finished bathing.
Ah, okay.
I'll get in a bit later.
Do you feel unwell?
No, I don't.
But I keep hearing the sound of waves deep within my ears.
Sound of waves?
I wonder why Hi-kun wants me to keep this stone safe so badly.
Eh?
Hi-kun looks like he's desperately doing something for me.
But what's making him work so hard?
What if you tried asking him?
If he's keeping it to himself,
it's probably something he doesn't want to say.
This stone is pretty, but I
don't know what to make of it.
It brings confusing feelings.
Manaka-san...
Since Manaka-san's heart
to love someone was taken away,
there's a hole where it used to be,
and it's crying out to her.
Crying, that she's feeling lonely.
Manaka-san, please lend me that stone for a bit.
What? But...
I won't do anything that would ruin it.
I'll make it so you can treasure it more.
Treasure... it more?
Yes!
I swear, on my life!
You're a funny girl, Miuna-chan.
I-I am?
Yup, and adorable.
You haven't changed since you were little.
Hikari's thinking about Manaka-san feelings
more than his own feelings for her.
You're up early.
Good morning.
Exams are soon so I might be coming home late.
I figured I should make more for dinner, too.
I see.
Make sure to eat your vegetables
when you're back at the university.
You forget to eat when
you get caught up in something.
I know.
Make sure to sleep properly, too.
You're not allowed to lie
on the sofa or the floor.
That won't refresh you.
I know.
Are you sure you don't
want to tell everyone?
I'm just returning to the university.
It's not necessary to make a deal out of it.
That's a bit cold.
Can I also ask you something?
What is it?
Why would you feel relieved
if you lost the ability to love someone?
You're skillful with handicrafts, Miuna.
You know, I've been thinking since last night.
About what?
I don't think I'd want to lose
the ability to love someone.
Even if it's unrequited, it's better to have loved.
Sayu...
In these five years, I studied hard and cried at times because of Kaname.
If people stopped being able to love,
life would be a lot easier.
But then I probably wouldn't
be who I am right now.
That's why.
Sayu...
I'm...
I'm going to confess to Kaname.
Con—
I don't care what happens.
We don't have to get together.
As long as I can accept whatever he says.
It's my own problem to settle.
S-Sayu...
I forgot!
I was assigned morning duties!
I need to fill out the log and hand it to the teacher!
My own problem to settle... huh?
Workshop
Miuna-chan!
Manaka-san.
Huh? Where's Hikari and Kaname?
It looks like they left before us.
Is that so?
Right. Here.
Oh, is that the sea slug's?
Wow! It looks beautiful.
It's like Akari-san's pendant.
You know, the one made out of shells.
Yeah.
You helped out to make it with everyone back then.
Oh, that's right.
I'm starting to remember now.
We all made it together.
I'm still far from remembering everything.
I'm really no good.
Hey, how about putting it on?
Emergency
Exit
Here.
It's pretty!
Thank you, Miuna-chan!
I'll really be able to treasure
the stone better like this.
I won't lose this! I'll always have it with me.
Won't... lose it...
M-Miuna-chan, what's wrong?!
I'm sorry. You were just so pretty.
What?!
You're so pretty, and kind,
and fun to be with.
Manaka-san, you have everything.
And for you to lose anything is just...
I-It'll be okay.
I'll make sure to take care of this.
Workshop
I won't lose it, okay?
Okay.
What are you doing?
Ah, bathing it in cold water.
Also these. I was thinking of taking them home.
What do you mean, taking those home?
You're...
There's only so much research
that can be done here.
I'm going back to the university.
Hold on! What about Manaka?!
Huh?
Wait until she gets her feelings back!
She's... in love with you!
I want to do something
that'll help retrieve her feelings!
If you can evoke emotions out of her...
What am I supposed to do
to evoke emotions out of her?
Huh? Uh, I don't know...
Go on a date with her, and...
And kiss her?
And hold her?
Are you some lech?!
Sorry, but I don't feel that way about Mukaido.
You just need to act it out!
It doesn't have to be real!
Is the person Mukaido loves... really me?
Of course it is!
Her face turns red every time she looks at you.
She keeps saying your name
over and over in such a dazed voice.
And that's proof that she's in love with me?
Are you doubting Manaka's feelings?!
You should stop now.
There's a five year difference
between our heights and strengths.
Damn you!
Stop here please!
Give it up, Hikari.
I won't lie to you.
If Mukaido actually loves me,
it'll be pointless.
Why would it be?!
If you tell her you love her back,
Manaka might return to normal!
Regardless of what the situation is,
you should never take it lightly
when you say you love someone.
And also, I love Chisaki.
But, even if you do—
I'm in love with Chisaki.
Chisaki!
Wait!
Tsumugu!
I can't breathe.
But, if I lose her now...
I can hear something.
Like a voice... that I know.
Mukaido's Ena.
No, not just that.
But a countless number of emotions also reside within this ocean.
That idiot.
What's he doing diving
in here without Ena?
Tsumugu!
Hey, Tsumugu!
Hikari.
Y-You... can talk.
I see.
So this is how it feels to have Ena.
I see now.
Tsumugu...
Oh?
The sea.
That fish.
Do me a favor, and let me
go by myself from here.
By yourself?
But you've never even
gone to the sea villa—
I need...
I need to face Chisaki and tell her.
If I don't, I won't be able to move on.
But...
Please.
Tsumugu...
I'm scared.
Scared... of a Shishio where I'm all alone.
Or is it because...
Hm?
Tsu-Tsumugu?
H-How are you in Shishio?!
I chased after you.
That's not what I mean!
Are you able to breathe
down here? Are you okay?
Is that Ena?
My parents hated the sea.
They moved to the city, and left behind my grandpa who refused to leave it.
But, I was in love with the sea.
I wanted to stay by its side.
Tsumugu...
Do you remember?
Five years ago,
when Hikari mistook Egawa
and his friend for vandalizing the Lady.
I do.
Back then, you knew who really
did it and tried to cover for Hikari.
Because if people find out,
Hikari will be the one at fault!
It seemed so pathetic.
I learned that people can become
so unpredictable for someone else's sake.
You're normally so calm and serene,
but at times you're rough, and violent
to the point where no one can stop you.
From that time on I realized
that you're just like the sea I love.
I play cat's cradle with my silent words
mugon no kotoba de ayatori shite
and tried smiling at my feat.
jouzu ni dekita to waratte miru
The only thing I'm any good at
tokui nano wa dare ni mo kizukarenu you ni
is stifling my heart so no one knows what's in it.
kokoro oshikorosu koto sore hitotsu dake
But this beautiful loop surrounding me
demo torimaku kirei na ruupu wa
very gently winds me in
yowai chikara de taguriyosete kureru kara
and it becomes clear.
azayaka ni
I don't want to let go of these feelings.
musunde kono kimochi goto
Bind them tightly so they can't escape.
hanarenai you ni kataku kataku aa
We are all tied together,
hitomusubi hito wo musunde
heading towards our uncertain future.
kitai no yamanai saki he asu he yukou
Hi-kun, who do you love?
Why...
Stop it!
Don't worry about my feelings.
Or, am I wrong?
How is it that in just five years...
Quit sounding like a tragic heroine!
This is a talk between men.
I'm hearing the sound of waves again.
Manaka has nothing to do with this.
It's way too extreme!
The very least I can do...
Story 24
Detritus