I don't know whether he counts as a new student or a returning one,
Sakishima Hikari
but either way, he will be joining our class.
This is Hikari Sakishima-kun.
I'm Sakishima for the second time.
Please look up to me and call me "Senpai."
Well, that's how he is.
Don't worry about being too much for him.
If I hear you talking smack, I'll drag you behind the gym!
The powdered snow falls thick
as these abandoned dreams still
ebb and flow like that day.
I looked at the smile you always had
as the wind that brushed my reddened cheeks
flew high into the sky.
I've always watched you.
So close, yet so far...
Always out of my reach...
"Why?"
I asked with a trembling voice.
The moon that swayed on the rolling waves
said nothing and only watched helplessly.
"Just like me."
My clenched fists hurt.
Story 16
The Murmurs
of Distant Waves
Story 16
The Murmurs
of Distant Waves
Senpai, can we see your Ena?
I wanna see it too!
I remember the Sending!
Happis got super trendy afterwards!
How could happis ever be fashionable?
Tsumugu-senpai was so cool!
This is so weird.
That octopus is in the same class as us.
I haven't heard you call him "octopus" in a long time.
Huh?
Well, he is an octopus.
Not like he's changed at all.
Sorry. You mind if I sit down for a bit?
An old man runs outta energy fast.
The octo-brain's still a little off in the head,
so go easy on him.
I haven't heard that nickname in a while.
You both said the same thing!
Oh, Senpai, aren't you Shiodome's uncle now?
So... Miuna's your niece?
I guess, but you aren't calling me "Uncle."
Hikari was just like before.
At least, he pretended he was just like before.
Since he did, I also acted like nothing happened.
Teach has gotten old and his voice is dry.
Was he any different before?
I think he used to talk a little faster.
How much have you grown?
Huh?
I'm four...
I didn't mean in age.
Your height.
158 centimeters.
Damn, you're outgrowing me!
Huh?! No, I won't!
I'm not going to outgrow you.
Really? But I haven't grown an inch in five years.
I'm gonna be screwed if I don't grow any more than I have.
I'll give you my milk then.
Watch it.
Talk about bad driving.
Wait here a minute.
Minegishi!
What?
Um... Well, you see...
You don't have to explain anything.
I already figured it out.
But I...
I won't tell anyone.
Thank...
Sorry.
You know...
He's in our class, right?
What?
I won't tell your papa.
A-About what?
But you've gotta tell me...
You like him? He going after you?
Well?
Actually, never mind.
I get it all now.
Wh-What is there to "get"?!
I see, I see. He's that kind of guy!
No! You're absolutely wrong!
All right, I see what's goin' on.
You clearly don't!
Welcome back.
I heard you started school again today.
Yep. I'm going again.
I get to be called "Senpai."
Tsumugu-kun brought you his old Hama Middle uniform.
Uniform?
You don't have one, do you?
You can't just wear a plain shirt to school forever.
Hang on, speaking of my uniform,
the guys at the fishery took off my Nami Middle uniform before the Sending...
What happened to it?
Don't ask me.
This one's just for the time being, okay?
He can have it if it fits.
It was from when I graduated, so it may be a little big.
Thanks.
Hey, thanks.
Sure.
It's huge.
Huge!
That guy grows way too fast.
I guess I'll have to adjust it again.
Yeah.
Hey, wait!
Shut it!
Maybe we should just get you a new one.
What? It's fine.
It's no biggie.
It's fine. I'll just wear this.
We can all catch the train together, go to the store, and eat omelet rice afterwards!
Omelet!
Well, he's at least trying to look happy, but still...
It's a guy thing.
Just let him do things his way.
Of course.
Itaru-san, thank you.
Hm?
Thanks for letting Hikari stay here.
Of course I would. He's your brother after all.
Since you have a brother as young
as him, it makes me feel young too.
Itaru-san.
I happen to have the day off tomorrow too,
so let's have some fun with the whole family.
Thank you for working so hard every day for us.
No, no, it's all thanks to my lovely wife.
What's up?
Omelet...
That's tomorrow, silly.
When's tomorrow?
It'll be tomorrow by the time you wake up from bedtime.
Just for today, let's try that again.
We'll go next time, okay?
Next time.
No next time!
Mommy!
Mom?
Could you get me a cold pad?
Sure!
Here. For your uniform.
I can wait until another day.
Nope. You can't.
It's not like I have to get it tailored.
I'll get one from Saya Mart or someth—
We don't have any there.
You know where the tailor is, right?
Yeah.
Ready to go!
See you later.
Take care, okay?
We should get going, too.
We don't want to miss the train.
Can't we just stay here?
Huh? Why?
Why?
Well, I don't really need a brand new uniform anyway.
No.
You need a uniform that fits you.
Now you sound like Akari.
We're going.
On a more important note,
what if one of us gets lost?
There's no way I would get lost!
I meant me.
What?
We can hold hands so we don't get separated.
What, like we're on a date?!
I thought you and that guy from yesterday were together.
No—
How about Sayu, then?
I'll ask Sayu to come with us!
What? Why her?
I'll give her a call!
Wait there a second!
Did you remember to bring one?
A bottle full of seawater?
Oshiohshi Gift Shop
Q
T
G
Why would I bring something like that?
Miuna!
I only did it that once five years ago!
Well, it was just the other day for me.
Oh, come on! I'm not like that anymore.
I've changed a lot!
All right, I get it. You don't have to go on and on about it.
I wasn't!
Sayu!
How did I get here earlier than you?
Sorry!
Whatever.
What do you want to have for lunch?
Omelet rice?
I'm not really hungry yet.
You remember those squid ink-flavored chips?
The black ones?
Yeah, they tasted amazing.
They still sell 'em?
Um, I don't think so. But there's a new squid rice flavor!
Squid rice? Really?
That sounds disgusting.
Space
for Rent
Wow. Everything here is different too.
Space
for Rent
Let's get going.
Wait, did someone just fart?
Huh?
That's not a fart!
Really? Is it a pig then?
No, it's not!
These shoes are just making these sounds—
Yeah, that's Miuna's best pair.
Your best pair makes piggy sounds?
And farting noises?
They must be farting shoes!
Hey! I told you that it's not a fart!
Ow! Stop hitting me, that hurts!
Didn't you have something you needed to do?
Look, now she's upset.
But you were...
Come along now. Don't get left behind.
Please take off your shoes and step onto there.
I need to take your measurements first.
Sure.
It's been a while since I've been asked to make clothes for sea-people.
It would be nice to do business with them again.
Yes, I'm sure it would.
I'll go and bring out some fabrics now.
What am I even doing here?
Lately, there have been less students enrolling even up on land.
Um, could I...
Instead of the Hama Middle uniform, could I...
...So why're you wearing Hama Middle's?!
You don't want Hama Middle's?
Um, actually, Hama Middle's is fine.
No!
He'd like the Nami Middle one.
Please make him the Nami Middle uniform!
Nami Middle?
But wasn't Nami Middle closed down?
Even so, he's a Nami Middle School student!
Er, could you give me a moment, please?
Hey, why...
You wanted Nami Middle's, right?
I'm gonna wait outside.
Don't you think that was a bit awkward for the tailor?
Didn't you hear him?
He said it had been a while since
he'd made clothes for sea-people.
Y-Yeah, but...
Whatever.
Sorry for calling you out all of a sudden.
It's no big deal.
Hey, did you know?
Know what?
Actually, I don't want to tell you anymore.
What is it?
Oh, but I don't want to scare you.
It won't scare me!
Fine, I'll tell you.
Apparently you can't get married to your uncle.
Because you're technically related.
I know that!
But...
I guess that doesn't apply to your uncle-in-law.
Sorry. Maybe I shouldn't have brought it up at all.
Forget what I said.
Why?
Why what?
You were happy for me, weren't you?
You told me that you were happy for me, Sayu!
So why?!
That doesn't have anything to do with this!
Yes, it does!
You're acting weird all of a sudden!
You're the one acting weird!
Why did you ask me to come today?
You could have just come by yourselves!
Did you want to show off how
lovey-dovey the two of you were?
Lovey...
We weren't like that!
Yes, you were!
How can you say that?!
Your loved one came back to you!
It's always you!
You're always the one getting all the luck!
It's not fair!
Why did you have me come today?!
We have to make the pattern for Nami Middle uniforms,
so this may take a little longer than usual.
You don't have to.
Hm?
I don't think I'll be ordering one after all.
I'm sorry for the trouble!
Sayu, you idiot!
You're the idiot!
H-Hey!
Sorry! I'm going home!
Hello. Shiodome residence.
Oh hey, Hikari.
Akira?
Yep, he's got the measles.
The doctor prescribed him some medicine, so he'll be okay now.
I see. That's a relief.
By the way, I got separated from Miuna, and—
Have I heard from her?
No, nothing yet.
Did something happen?
Weren't you together?
Uh, yeah. I'm gonna head home now.
Bye.
Well, this sucks.
I'm sorry...
Well, that's not exactly what I meant.
I was more concerned about what to do until the next train comes.
But it's my fault that you missed it...
Wow, you guys really haven't changed a bit.
Hey now, you can't go making little girls cry.
Always Smiling
Sayama!
Oh, that's quite the shocking tale for an old man like me.
Who are you calling an "old man"?
Stop making yourself out to be so mature.
Oh, come now. I know so much about all kinds of things.
I take it back. You really have become an old man.
So, since our store's been around forever,
we've been able to get some
door-to-door sales going too.
Oh yeah, that shipyard over there...
About three or four years ago, there was talk of demolishing it and making it into a parking lot.
But it's not like there'd be anyone who'd use it, y'know?
Stop here, Sayama.
Huh, here?
Could you take her back home?
Thanks.
Take care on your way back, okay?
No Entry
You haven't grown at all.
Why?
Why would you come after me?
Getting quite cocky there, aren't you?
I'm just here to look for my old uniform that I took off before the Sending.
So I heard you had some kind of argument?
Girls are pretty quick to get into arguments with each other.
They're quick to make up, too.
They're so confusing.
Not this time.
I can't make up with her.
That's not true.
It is!
Y'know, Manaka and Chisaki got into a heap of arguments, too.
Manaka-san and Chisaki-san?
Yep.
It usually ended up with Chisaki giving Manaka the cold shoulder.
And then Manaka would cry.
So how'd they make up with each other?
No idea. How did they?
Kaname might have got them back together.
Okay, fine. I'll play Kaname's role for you.
Hey, um—
Your nose is as red as a red pig's!
You meanie!
Aw, don't get mad at me.
Jerk!
Miu—
Miuna?!
It's so cold.
I can't breathe.
It hurts.
Hikari...
What's this sound?
I can breathe!
Miuna!
The Hikari that I saw underwater
should have been no different from normal,
but he was much brighter.
He was like a different person.
What were you doing?!
I could swim!
I could breathe!
It was beautiful!
The sea was amazing!
Come on, let's go!
H-Hey!
We have to tell Mom about how I swam!
I didn't feel weighed down at all!
Sayu...
I'm so glad you're safe...
I found this on the ground.
Sayu...
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Really?!
Are you keeping a pig in there or something?
No I'm not!
How many do you have in there?
I don't have any!
What kind of pigs are they?
Excuse me...
could you tell me today's date?
I play cat's cradle with my silent words
mugon no kotoba de ayatori shite
and tried smiling at my feat.
jouzu ni dekita to waratte miru
The only thing I'm any good at
tokui nano wa dare ni mo kizukarenu you ni
is stifling my heart so no one knows what's in it.
kokoro oshikorosu koto sore hitotsu dake
But this beautiful loop surrounding me
demo torimaku kirei na ruupu wa
very gently winds me in
yowai chikara de taguriyosete kureru kara
and it becomes clear.
azayaka ni
I don't want to let go of these feelings.
musunde kono kimochi goto
Bind them tightly so they can't escape.
hanarenai you ni kataku kataku aa
We are all tied together,
hitomusubi hito wo musunde
heading towards our uncertain future.
kitai no yamanai saki he asu he yukou
Heya. Morning.
Kaname...
When are you going to go visit Kaname-san?
I'm not going to.
I bet you're surprised at how much things have changed.
Are you... any different?
There's nothing that...
Story 17
The Sick Pair
...would have changed about me.