Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
1st    Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
Inugami Yachiyo, 16 years old.
Despite Inugami being my last name,
I'm all about cats.
What's so great about cats?
Well... I'm the type who prefers to be
disciplined rather than discipline others.
But with your personality,
wouldn't you be all for dogs?
No! See, cats bring out the
masochistic tendencies within me!
What kind of reply is that?
Nekoyama Suzu, 16 years old.
My last name's Nekoyama,
but I'm really a dog person.
Everyone around me says
I'm more of a cat person,
but I don't see that at all.
Chips
You might want to take a look in a mirror.
Nekoyama, this is Inugami-san
from the class next door.
She's like a kitten!
She's like a puppy!
Nice to meet you!
You're not a dog!
Nya!
You're not a cat!
What do you like about dogs, Nekoyama-san?
Well, they're friendly.
You can also play with them and teach them things.
Like "shake hands."
Okay.
Wh-Wh-Why did you give me your hand?
Sorry. A force of habit?
What kind of habit would that be?
Inugami-san and Aki are friends...
They told me they study together
and do a lot of other things tog—
Hold on a sec! Other things?!
What's that supposed to mean?!
Look here...
I can personally teach you
about the changes in your body...
Aki-chan...
What am I thinking?!
The cats outside my place are noisy these days.
I guess you could say they're in heat.
Speaking about being in heat...
Nekoyama-san also being in heat...
My body's burning up—It's unbearable!
Help me, Inugami-san!
Wait, what am I thinking?!
Then again.
Humans are in heat all year round.
Can't be helped.
Inugami-san
&
Nekoyama-san
Inugami-san
&
Nekoyama-san
Huh? My gym clothes are missing.
Really?
I think you might have put
them in your bag accidentally.
Oh, you're right.
That's amazing! How'd you know?
Through your scent!
If it's within a radius of 100 meters,
I'll know it's yours, Nekoyama-san.
She's a pervert.
A genuine pervert.
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
If I recall correctly, you have dogs, right, Inugami?
Yup, three of them.
Wow!
Really?! I'm so jealous!
Would you like to come and see them?
Can I?
Of course. My parents aren't home, either.
This calls for an all-nighter for two!
Dare I ask what that would entail, Miss Dog Owner?
These are my puppies!
So cute! What do I do?!
Really. What am I going to do?
Can I pet them?
Of course you can!
He's so fluffy!
Watching this is so rejuvenating.
I, on the other hand, am feeling restless.
That really tickles!
Hey! Don't lick her!
It's not a problem, really.
Nonsense. You're dirty now.
Let me clean you up.
I feel even dirtier now that you've done that!
Come on!
What is going on?
Is this something I should really keep record of?
I want to stay with them forever...
Do you really? Well...
Then let's get married!
Clearly skipped a few steps!
I decline.
What... How could you?!
I mean...
If I said yes after that,
it'd sound like I did so because of your dogs.
Does that mean what I think it means?!
Quit asking me!
Ask her yourself!
wan wan wan neko ga suki
Woof, woof, woof, I love cats!
muchuu de nani mo mienai
So much so that they're all I see!
nyan nyan nyan inu ga suki
Meow, meow, meow, I love dogs!
sunao ni I love you
But I'll be honest, I love you!
pi pi pi pitto kita no
Pi-pi-pi-pitter patter goes my heart.
anata ni fukujuu shimasu
You know I'll give in to whatever you say!
sore ga futari no
This is how the destiny of our love
ai no destiny
will unfold between us!
Illustration: Namori