Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
2nd    Ushiwaka-san & Nezu-san
Homeroom's about to start.
Guess I should return to my own classroom...
Please be more careful.
Um, pardon me.
Could I ask your name?
That would be Nezu Mikine.
I'm in the seat right behind you, Inugami-san.
What?!
Please forgive me...
N-No, it's fine.
What are you eating?
I'm having my morning fix of cheese.
Cheese is wonderful.
The way it melts...
and the way it tears...
It's so lewd that it makes
the cheese even more delicious.
I think I'll really get along with this girl.
Eating the cheese made me sleepy.
I'm nocturnal, so it's hard for me to stay awake during the day.
That's no good. You need to concentrate during class.
I know that's important, but I need to conserve some stamina for the night, too.
That's what my instincts are telling me.
Romance can happen
at any time, you know.
Definitely gonna get along with her.
You see, I made a new friend earlier!
What's she like?
Her name's Nezu-san.
And we really hit it off!
What do you mean by that?
I'll never forgive you if you leave me for her!
Geez, quit worrying!
My feelings for you will never change, Nekoyama-san!
I didn't mean it like that!
Are you in any clubs, Inugami-san?
Nope, none.
In that case, there's a club I'd like you to join...
A club you'd like me to join?
What kind of club are you talking about?
It's the Assorted Living Beings club.
It's right here.
Alive
-_-_-
The Alive club?
We're registered as the Assorted Living Beings club,
but the students keep calling us Alive for some reason.
Because it's more fitting, or something.
"Fitting"?
Senpai, we have visitors.
Ah, welcome!
Ah!
Ah...
Welcome...
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
Nice to meet you. I'm Ushiwaka Yukiji.
She's also my wife.
Huh? Your wife, as in...
This is Inugami-san and Nekoyama-san.
They came to visit our club.
Why, thank you very much!
All we really do is drink tea and relax, though...
Oh, is that so?
Nekoyama-san, I've really taken to you.
Huh?
Since we're fellow shorties,
we should get along.
You do realize I'm still
taller than you, right?
Then, how about we get along because we're both into tall and lazy types?
Now that's something I can get behind.
So this is Nezu-san?
Yep, yep!
Aki-san, you're in Class B with Nekoyama-san, right?
That's right.
Our class pairings are rather interesting, don't you think?
No, I don't think so...
Actually, if you were to divide the four of us,
it'd be like this.
Aki-chan? Don't tell me that you...
No, not at all.
It's more like...
They'd just make for a really cute idol unit.
I really wanna see that!
wan wan wan neko ga suki
Woof, woof, woof, I love cats!
muchuu de nani mo mienai
So much so that they're all I see!
nyan nyan nyan inu ga suki
Meow, meow, meow, I love dogs!
sunao ni I love you
But I'll be honest, I love you!
pi pi pi pitto kita no
Pi-pi-pi-pitter patter goes my heart.
anata ni fukujuu shimasu
You know I'll give in to whatever you say!
sore ga futari no
This is how the destiny of our love
ai no destiny
will unfold between us!
Illustration: Kurada Uso