Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
7th     Inugami-san & Sarutobi-san
Just so you know, I don't like you, Inugami-san.
Inugami-san
&
Nekoyama-san
Inugami-san
&
Nekoyama-san
Aki-chan, we need to hurry!
We're going to be late!
Huh? It's not even 8 o'clock yet!
I'm on morning duty today!
Why do I have to hurry, too?
Because you're my friend!
It's almost like watching a dog
drag their owner around.
It's only morning and
they're already so lively...
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
Damn it, she's gonna get it later...
That's weird. Our attendance sheets and handouts are missing.
Could this be the work of a fairy?
Are you stupid?
Sarutobi Sora, 16 years old.
I'm in Class A, same as Inugami. Also its class representative.
Due to your lack of punctuality,
I carried out the tasks in your place.
So you must be the fairy!
You really are stupid, aren't you?
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
But yeah, I'm really grateful
for your help, Sarutobi-san!
It's nothing. The class representative
has to make sure that things get done.
Well, I'll make it up to you later!
I'm not asking you to. There isn't anything I want from you either.
Just so you know, I don't like you, Inugami-san.
Um... Have I done something
to make you dislike me?
I see! It's because you're a dog
and you're a monkey.
You're pretty simple-minded, aren't you?
That's not it!
D-Dog and m-monkey...
Don't you go and liken us to animals just because of our surnames!
Well, you see... I'm perfectly fine with being compared to a do—
(The dog's a masochist)
That's just you!
If you keep making animal references with my name, I'll shut you up.
So don't argue with me.
I wonder if she's an idiot or if she just doesn't know what her words will do.
A mouth gag! Wow!
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
Anyway, Inugami-san! You should know you still have morning duty work left!
Don't worry, I'll get to it... eventually.
I want you to finish it while I'm watching you!
I can't possibly get anything done with your eyes all over me!
Stop making everything
sound so lewd all the time!
If you're going to get mad at me,
do it in a way that makes me beg for more!
You're making absolutely no sense! Are you stupid?!
What's that? A new act of sorts?
Sarutobi-san and Inugami-san,
you really live up to your
names with the way you act.
I guess so...
I think otherwise.
Being called a monkey is degrading.
It doesn't change anything even if
they're the smartest animals around.
It's rather unpleasant being called a monkey to your face, you know.
Even if my surname has that word in it.
You don't sound very convincing
with a banana in hand.
Sarutobi-san, do you usually
chit-chat with your friends?
No. I never really bothered with making friends in the first place.
Oh... But I really liked the way
we were talking just now...
Well... I want you to know that...
I want to get more intimate with you!
It didn't even sound romantic.
Inugami-san, you really are a handful.
But I'll retract my statement
that I don't like you.
Huh? What was that?
I couldn't hear that properly!
One more time!
Geez, just forget it!
Why, that...
Nekoyama-san, that hurts...
wan wan wan neko ga suki
Woof, woof, woof, I love cats!
muchuu de nani mo mienai
So much so that they're all I see!
nyan nyan nyan inu ga suki
Meow, meow, meow, I love dogs!
sunao ni I love you
But I'll be honest, I love you!
pi pi pi pitto kita no
Pi-pi-pi-pitter patter goes my heart.
anata ni fukujuu shimasu
You know I'll give in to whatever you say!
sore ga futari no
This is how the destiny of our love
ai no destiny
will unfold between us!
Illustration: Benishake