Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
4th    Nekoyama-san & Glasses
Looks like I didn't pass the eye test...
So you've got bad eyes, Nekoyama.
I'm a bit nearsighted at 0.6 and 0.7,
but it's not like it bothers me in daily life.
Oh well, guess I'll just get
some contacts made later...
You should.
Don't be ridiculous!
This is where you go for glasses, right?!
I'm begging you to get glasses! Please!
Where did you just pop out from?
Well... I wouldn't mind glasses either.
Great!
Let's go get you some glasses then!
You mean today?
As they say, "strike while the iron's hot!"
Let's go together after school—
Actually, wouldn't this be our first afterschool date?
A date?
Please check your enthusiasm.
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
So, where's the optician's?
It's just a short ways from here.
I'm a regular there.
Don't you have perfect eyesight, Inugami?
I do.
Then why are you a regular at an optician?
Welcome!
Because of the pretty young women with glasses working here!
Wow, they have a lot to choose from.
I'll try these.
How are they?
This is bad, really bad!
And yet so terribly good!
Which one is it?
They do feel pretty comfortable,
so I just might go with them.
Nekoyama-san, there's something I'd like to check...
Could you lean forward a bit?
Um... Like this?
Oh, that's good!
That glancing-over-tilted-glasses look is so cu—
Just what are you trying to do?
All right then, I'll have them fit lenses to this frame.
Sure.
Glasses, huh?
As someone with 2.0 perfect vision, I don't really need them...
Aki-chan, glasses make you look kind of old—
But I do think they look good on you, and they bring out your sadi—
That's enough, I'm taking them off.
Just wait a moment!
What?
I want you to act like a sadist for a sec.
Lemme take a pic—
You're so mean, Aki-chan...
Inugami, you should try a frame on, too.
I'll take a picture for you.
I don't look too good in glasses, you see.
They kind of make me look like a klutz.
You say they make you look like a klutz,
but I bet you like that.
Oops!
Hey... What are you two doing?
Thank you very much!
Optician
Oh? You're not wearing
your glasses on the way home?
Huh? Well...
I wanna see you wear them!
I-It's not like I bought them
just to show them off to you...
She says, while taking out her glasses.
Well, I can definitely see better than before...
B-But I feel dizzy.
Whoa?! What's going on?!
This is making me feel
even more dizzy, Inugami-san!
Inugami-san... y-your hand...
Glasses tend to make you feel dizzy
until you get used to wearing them, so...
Thanks...
Don't let her fool you, Nekoyama!
Inugami knew this would happen
when she had you put on your glasses!
Aki-chan, you didn't have to say that!
wan wan wan neko ga suki
Woof, woof, woof, I love cats!
muchuu de nani mo mienai
So much so that they're all I see!
nyan nyan nyan inu ga suki
Meow, meow, meow, I love dogs!
sunao ni I love you
But I'll be honest, I love you!
pi pi pi pitto kita no
Pi-pi-pi-pitter patter goes my heart.
anata ni fukujuu shimasu
You know I'll give in to whatever you say!
sore ga futari no
This is how the destiny of our love
ai no destiny
will unfold between us!
Illustration:
Fujieda Miyabi