Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
5th    Nekoyama-san & Karaoke
I want to go sing karaoke on Sunday!
Not happening.
That was quick...
I've got an away match that day with my club.
No way. Then what about next week?
Hold on...
They've gone to karaoke before?!
Alive
-_-_-
Looks like we're going to
a karaoke box next week...
But I haven't gone to one before.
That's nothing to be worried about.
But...
It's embarrassing to have so many people watching you do something you've never done before.
She honestly doesn't realize that what she said should be more embarrassing. She must have a talent for this.
Would you like to go with me, then?
Huh?
We promised to get along as fellow shorties, right?
I'm indebted to you.
Don't worry, it's my pleasure.
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
"Definite       Declaration Of Obedience"
Lyrics: Kobayashi Tetsuya, Jougasaki Maria/Song Edit: Kobayashi Tetsuya
Uesaka Sumire x Touyama Nao
Takumi (CV: Fukuyama Jun)
"Definite     Declaration Of Obedience"
B
Lyrics: Kobayashi Tetsuya, Jougasaki Maria/Song - Edit: Kobayashi Tetsuya
Uesaka Sumire x Touyama Nao
Takumi (CV: Fukuyama Jun)
"Definite     Declaration Of Obedience"
B
Lyrics: Kobayashi Tetsuya, Jougasaki Maria/Song - Edit: Kobayashi Tetsuya
Uesaka Sumire x Touyama Nao
Takumi (CV: Fukuyama Jun)
"Definite     Declaration Of Obedience"
B
Lyrics: Kobayashi Tetsuya, Jougasaki Maria/Song - Edit: Kobayashi Tetsuya
Uesaka Sumire x Touyama Nao
Takumi (CV: Fukuyama Jun)
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
"Definite     Declaration Of Obedience"
B
Lyrics: Kobayashi Tetsuya, Jougasaki Maria/Song - Edit: Kobayashi Tetsuya
Uesaka Sumire x Touyama Nao
Takumi (CV: Fukuyama Jun)
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
"Definite     Declaration Of Obedience"
B
Lyrics: Kobayashi Tetsuya, Jougasaki Maria/Song - Edit: Kobayashi Tetsuya
Uesaka Sumire x Touyama Nao
Takumi (CV: Fukuyama Jun)
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
"Definite     Declaration Of Obedience"
B
Lyrics: Kobayashi Tetsuya, Jougasaki Maria/Song - Edit: Kobayashi Tetsuya
Uesaka Sumire x Touyama Nao
Takumi (CV: Fukuyama Jun)
"Definite     Declaration Of Obedience"
B
Lyrics: Kobayashi Tetsuya, Jougasaki Maria/Song - Edit: Kobayashi Tetsuya
Uesaka Sumire x Touyama Nao
Takumi (CV: Fukuyama Jun)
You can select songs using this remote here.
Nekoyama-san, what kind of songs do you like?
I'm fine with anything.
Except rock, maybe.
Actually, string instruments in general are no good...
Just the sight of them puts my hairs on end.
You really are a cat.
"Definite         Declaration Of Obedience"
Lyrics: Kobayashi Tetsuya, Jougasaki Maria/Song - Edit: Kobayashi Tetsuya
Uesaka Sumire x Touyama Nao
B
Wow, it has the music video too!
I see. So this is what Nezu-san's into...
Oh, I know this anime song!
You do?
Then let's sing it together.
S-Sure.
Oh my, looks like the batteries in this mic just died.
There we go...
Wh-Wh-What?!
It isn't that bad when I'm singing with someone else.
And Nezu-san's really talented, too.
What's the matter?
You're way too close...
What we're doing is embarrassing enough, so when you come so close...
What's wrong with getting closer?
It makes me uncomfortable!
But if you come here with Inugami-san,
she might want to do something like this.
Dogs are smart, but also impulsive.
Well, I can't deny that...
So...
How about we prepare you for
other things that might happen?
Wh-What?!
Looks like our time's up.
Yes, yes.
Want to call it a day?
Or should we get an extension?
We'd like to have another hour.
Nezu-san, you're crazy!
So where were we, Nekoyama-san?
Singing karaoke, of course!
All right, go ahead.
Okay, I'm fired up!
Chase it all the way, and run until you pass it!
The destination that lies ahead—
Ugh, my throat hurts.
You were particularly loud
during the last hour, after all.
So how did you like your first time?
I-It was fun.
Thank you very much.
Oh no, it was my pleasure.
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
Nezu-san and Nekoyama-san
went to karaoke together?!
Why didn't you take me along?!
She was really cute.
We're going today! Right after school!
wan wan wan neko ga suki
Woof, woof, woof, I love cats!
muchuu de nani mo mienai
So much so that they're all I see!
nyan nyan nyan inu ga suki
Meow, meow, meow, I love dogs!
sunao ni I love you
But I'll be honest, I love you!
pi pi pi pitto kita no
Pi-pi-pi-pitter patter goes my heart.
anata ni fukujuu shimasu
You know I'll give in to whatever you say!
sore ga futari no
This is how the destiny of our love
ai no destiny
will unfold between us!
Illustration: Saburouta