Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
8th     Nekoyama-san & Torikai-san
Who was it that was absent today?
Attendance Log
Why do you ask?
Because I'm on class duty today.
Torikai-san should be the only one.
There's a Torikai-san in our class?
I've never met her before.
Neither have I. I don't think anyone has.
Hold on!
What is this—some creepy school ghost story?
Don't go there.
She's in the hospital a lot,
so she rarely comes to school.
I see.
Now I feel bad for saying that...
It's fine.
I do rarely come to school,
so it's my fault, too.
A-A vengeful spirit!
That was an amusing reaction.
Nice to meet you two. I'm Torikai Hibari.
Even I started to become unsure whether I was a ghost or not.
S-Sorry!
Maybe I don't exist after all?
That's not true! We're able to touch you!
No, it's my fault.
After all, I rarely—
We're really sorry!
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
I'm Hiiragi Aki.
I'm Nekoyama Suzu. Nice to meet you.
Aki-chan and Neko-chan...
So Acchan and Nyan-chan!
Let's get along!
She's gone and given us nicknames?!
That smile... I-It's so radiating!
Inugami-san
&
Nekoyama-san
Inugami-san
&
Nekoyama-san
Oh, I better head to my club.
All right, see you.
See you, Nekoyama.
And Torikai-san, I'll see you tomorrow.
All right, see you.
If I make it to school alive, that is.
One more joke like that one,
and you'll really get to know me.
You're such a nice person, Acchan!
I don't think you heard me.
Nekoyama-san!
Let's head to our club!
Oh? You're with a cute girl I've never met before, Nekoyama-san!
What's going on?
So you're able to notice my presence as well.
At last! A pretty ghost girl only
I can see has appeared before me!
Sorry, she's usually like this.
Is that so...
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
Oh, so that's what it was about?
Yup, that's right.
I'm Inugami Yachiyo from Class A.
Nice to meet you!
So you're the puppy from Class A?
Would you happen to know my friend, then?
Your friend?
She's studious, has brown hair,
wears glasses, and loves bananas—
That last part was unnecessary, Hibari!
That would be her.
Anyway, what are you doing at school?
I felt like coming, so I did.
I told you to let me know beforehand.
We could have come
to school together—
But I did...
My heart cried out to you many, many times...
Like I'd notice!
But using cellphones at the hospital is prohibited.
Of course it is!
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
Sacchan and I have been friends
since elementary school.
I don't think I could go on
if you disappeared, Sacchan.
That's nice to hear, but...
coming from you, those
words weigh heavily on me.
Nothing wrong with heavy love! Welcome it with open arms!
I want you to shut up.
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
It looks like Torikai-san's not here today.
You're right...
But that girl was never in
this class in the first place...
I hope you remember
what I said earlier, Torikai-san.
Yes...
wan wan wan neko ga suki
Woof, woof, woof, I love cats!
muchuu de nani mo mienai
So much so that they're all I see!
nyan nyan nyan inu ga suki
Meow, meow, meow, I love dogs!
sunao ni I love you
But I'll be honest, I love you!
pi pi pi pitto kita no
Pi-pi-pi-pitter patter goes my heart.
anata ni fukujuu shimasu
You know I'll give in to whatever you say!
sore ga futari no
This is how the destiny of our love
ai no destiny
will unfold between us!
Illustration: Arai Cherry