Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
9th  A Lover's Quarrel With Inugami-san
So what is this about?
Hmph!
What is going on here?
Did you two have a fight or something?
Did you break up?
How dare you say that!
This Week's Motto
"Everyone, get along."
So what is it? How did this happen?
It's Inugami-san's fault.
Huh? Aren't you the one at fault, Nekoyama-san?
What?!
What I said was perfectly normal.
Then what I said was normal, too!
Look.
I'm going to hit you two if you were fussing over who's cuter.
We weren't!
Oh, it's the bell.
Aki, let's go.
Huh? Oh, sure.
See you later then, Inugami.
You're leaving me here while you link arms with Nekoyama-san?
Aki-chan, you idiot!
You're directing your anger at the wrong person.
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
Nekoyama-san and Inugami-san got into a fight?
It's the sign of a coming storm.
I'm pretty sure you just said something silly.
It was not!
Even if it would normally be considered silly,
it was still something I had to say!
Looks like we've figured out the problem already.
That settles it.
You're kidding me!
It's about time you give me the full story.
The thing is...
Even I don't know why I got so worked up about it.
But Inugami-san's feelings were all a lie!
Sorry. This just screams "lover's quarrel" so I don't want to hear any more.
You're kidding me!
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
Earlier,
right before you came,
I was talking with Inugami-san.
See, my hair is curly.
It gets worse in the rain and
it's easy for me to get bed hair.
It's a pain to deal with. But when
I mentioned that I might get it straightened...
What did you say?
Wow, it was my first time
seeing Inugami-san look so scary.
Now that I've heard this much, I doubt this will get any better.
Just now... What did you say?
So, like I said... I want to get it straightened.
Are you an idiot or something, Nekoyama-san?!
That was uncalled for, Inugami-san!
But you're saying you want to fix what makes your hair like a cat's fur!
Something like that is... is...
It's like a cup of coffee without the coffee!
So my hair is what makes my identity?!
This Week's Motto
"Treat people kindly."
What is this? You like curly hair?
So you wouldn't be interested
in me if my hair was straight?
Don't try to change the topic!
Inugami-san?
Of course, straight hair has things going for it, but it isn't the same!
All I'm trying to say is that I like how curly your hair is, Nekoyama-san!
And you still have the nerve to want to straighten it after hearing that?
You're such a bother...
At any rate, I won't forgive you.
What?!
What I do with my hair is my business.
You keep nitpicking the things that I do,
but you're not even my lover, Inugami-san!
Even I won't be able to
shrug off that harsh rejection!
I'm having trouble
shrugging off that statement!
And that's what it was about.
I think I might have gotten too emotional.
What do you think, Aki?
So it was a lover's quarrel after all.
This Week's Motto
"Be nice to cats."
wan wan wan neko ga suki
Woof, woof, woof, I love cats!
muchuu de nani mo mienai
So much so that they're all I see!
nyan nyan nyan inu ga suki
Meow, meow, meow, I love dogs!
sunao ni I love you
But I'll be honest, I love you!
pi pi pi pitto kita no
Pi-pi-pi-pitter patter goes my heart.
anata ni fukujuu shimasu
You know I'll give in to whatever you say!
sore ga futari no
This is how the destiny of our love
ai no destiny
will unfold between us!
Illustration: Kawai Roh