Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
3rd    Nekoyama-san & Catnip Tea
You sure are in a good mood this morning, Inugami.
Ta-da!
Catnip tea!
I can see where this is going, and it won't be pretty.
I might as well ask. What are you bringing that for?
Well that would be...
To make Nekoyama-san drink it, of course.
I knew it already, but she looks absolutely evil.
This will be my plan.
Stage One, I'll be on standby until noon.
Stage Two, I'll swap Nekoyama-san's tea with this catnip tea.
Stage Three, Nekoyama-san will start to feel tipsy.
Then I'll endlessly pamper her!
Justice!
What do you think of this flawless plan?
Doesn't she realize that I'm going to try and stop her?
Nekoyama-san!
Good morning!
What's with Inugami-san today?
Nothing at all.
But just in case, I'll lend you my fencing stick.
What's going on?
Hmm? Won't you take a hint and leave, Aki-chan?
You're one to talk about taking hints.
You're not considering stopping me, are you?
Aren't we friends?
I'm doing this because we're friends.
Why do I feel like they're
flirting behind my back?
Hey!
Is there something you
two are hiding from me?
No, that's not it, Nekoyama.
Then what is it?
Wha—
I'm sorry, Nekoyama!
Are you okay, Nekoyama-san?!
N-Nekoyama-san... ?
What an odd smell. Is this alcohol?
Huh? Er, well...
Oh? Inugami-san, what were you thinking bringing all this alcohol here?
Hey, answer me.
Inugami-san.
So this is what Nekoyama-san is like when she's drunk.
Hey, this is your fault. Do something about it.
Inugami-san, lick me where I'm wet.
I-If I may...
Inugami's obeying her...?!
They're gonna change our airing time!
What? You'll lick me too, Aki?
Like hell I would!
Of course you wouldn't.
Licking is a dog's specialty, after all.
Inugami!
How am I supposed to deal with this?
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
I was so surprised today.
It's your fault, you know.
It was different from what I expected.
But...
Oh gosh, I could get addicted to it!
So I'd like my catnip tea back, please!
Wh-What was that just now...
I think I'm going to die if I think any further about it.
wan wan wan neko ga suki
Woof, woof, woof, I love cats!
muchuu de nani mo mienai
So much so that they're all I see!
nyan nyan nyan inu ga suki
Meow, meow, meow, I love dogs!
sunao ni I love you
But I'll be honest, I love you!
pi pi pi pitto kita no
Pi-pi-pi-pitter patter goes my heart.
anata ni fukujuu shimasu
You know I'll give in to whatever you say!
sore ga futari no
This is how the destiny of our love
ai no destiny
will unfold between us!
Illustration:
Sukeno Yoshiaki