Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
13th     A Hot Springs Trip with Nekoyama-san
Hey, Nekoyama-san.
Why are you trying to cover yourself?
B-Because... it's embarrassing...
"It's embarrassing"? You're saying that now?
And besides,
how am I supposed to wash you if you keep yourself covered?!
I don't understand how that's your concern!
This may seem out of the blue, but we're visiting a hot spring.
I won tickets for two at a lottery drawing held at my shopping district.
So, I invited Nekoyama
to come along with me, but...
Why are you here, Inugami?
That's cruel, Aki-chan!
I mean, how could you?!
Why did you go and leave me out?!
I wasn't trying to leave you out.
When I thought of who to invite,
Nekoyama was the only one who came to mind.
That doesn't mean you shouldn't consider me at all!
Besides, what's the deal? You wanted
a hot springs trip with just the two of you?!
You're definitely planning on
taking advantage of her!
So let me join you!
This is exactly why I didn't want you to join us.
Come on you guys.
We're taking a trip together,
so let's make the most of it.
Okay?
Hmph.
Sorry.
You're right about making the most of it.
That's why I brought this video camera—
Aki-chan! Don't!
That cost a fortune! I'm serious!
That's nice.
I'm truly sorry for my actions.
Right.
I just let myself go.
And I couldn't control myself.
Right.
And I wanted to see
how much I could get away—
We're getting out.
R-Right.
Stargazing
Bath
Geez,
why did they have to be so mean?
Listen, Aki-chan! Nekoyama-san!
Just what was that about?!
This is so good!
This one too.
You're right!
Why are you two being
so clingy with each other?!
We're not being clingy at all.
I just left you behind so I could
have dinner with Nekoyama.
Didn't I say to stop leaving me without a thought?!
I mean, we're at a hot spring.
Let's all try to have more fun together!
What are you even saying?
Did you honestly think I'd allow you to
stay longer than 4 minutes with us unclothed?!
What are you even saying?
What's wrong, Nekoyama?
I was just thinking about how I finished my sashimi with that last piece.
I see.
I'll give you mine, then.
Really?
It's delicious!
Want me to feed you some more?
Just why are you two flirting
and leaving me out of it?!
Why would you?
Is this what I think it is?
Nekoyama-san, do you like Aki-chan?!
Well yeah, I like her.
Who wouldn't?
From now, I'll use this trip to mend my heart.
What's that supposed to mean?
I mean, you two are deeply
in love with each other!
No, that's not how I meant it.
I like you too, Inugami-san... I think.
I'm falling into deeper despair.
Doesn't "I think" mean you don't really like me?
Th-That's not...
Um, see...
I'm okay saying it to Aki.
But saying it to you makes me blush.
Sh-She's so cute.
Now that I think about it,
you're pretty quiet today, aren't you?
Well, you see...
It's my first time going on a trip with friends,
so I'm not sure how to show my excitement.
She's so cute.
I see now.
So it's not like you were getting bored.
Right.
And it's not like you started disliking me.
As for my approach
in the hot springs—
No. That, I minded.
That hurts.
Give up.
Good night.
Inugami-san, good—
Good night to you, too.
You... Did you really have to?
Well, I just couldn't.
So what?
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
This was pretty fun.
That's good.
It'd be nice if I can go on
a trip with you guys again.
The next time we do,
we'll leave Aki-chan out.
That's my line.
Nekoyama-san, where would you like to go next?
Let's see...
A "next time" will probably
depend on everyone's support.
End.
.
wan wan wan neko ga suki
Woof, woof, woof, I love cats!
muchuu de nani mo mienai
So much so that they're all I see!
nyan nyan nyan inu ga suki
Meow, meow, meow, I love dogs!
sunao ni I love you
But I'll be honest, I love you!
pi pi pi pitto kita no
Pi-pi-pi-pitter patter goes my heart.
anata ni fukujuu shimasu
You know I'll give in to whatever you say!
sore ga futari no
This is how the destiny of our love
ai no destiny
will unfold between us!