Man, I wish I had a girlfriend...
Sorry, Kagura!
Geez, Yomi! You're late!
I'm really sorry!
I was out on duty earlier.
Well, you could've texted me at least.
Kagura.
Could we make up with this?
Please?
Fine...
Merry Christmas.
Let's go, Yomi.
Okay.
Someone once said:
There are but two ways to live one's life.
Either live life not believing for a
second that miracles could ever exist,
or live life as if every moment is a miracle.
Give me a situation report!
Yes, sir!
Captain!
What the hell is that?
Reporting in!
The situation's dire!
The National Diet has—
The National Diet Building
has been seized!!
A previous report presented
the following news:
The National Diet Building
has been seized!!
Changes in Train Line Schedules
The National Diet Building
has been seized!!
The National Diet Building has been seized by a group of armed supernatural power users.
The National Diet Building
has been seized!!
Currently, the building is suspended in mid-air and moving across the city skyline.
Due to the hazards—
Merry Christmas, dear ladies and gentlemen.
From today onwards, we espers will be ruling over Tokyo.
Unless you submit to us,
your lives will end here.
This is not negotiable.
TOKYO ESP
Stop right there!
Stop, or we'll shoot!
Lulled by the peace, you have grown complacent in your ignorance.
For the longest time,
I have turned a blind eye to your folly.
But I will no longer stand idly by
for your insolent reign.
What?!
I'm over here.
Over here.
You will all be held hostage
until humanity finally accepts the arrival of their new rulers.
Don't panic!
Stay calm and evacuate in an orderly manner!
What a mess. No way I'll get anywhere in this.
What a mess, indeed.
Th-Thank you...
There's been an explosion in front of Yotsuya Station.
We need an ambulance immedi—
The helicopters aren't ready yet?!
They should be ready in about 30 minutes...
This is terrible!
There are explosions
going off all over the city!
Seriously?
The Roppongi Hills area was also hit? Are you sure?
Ministry of Defense
What now?
A frontal assault is out of the question. There are hostages!
Ministry of Defense
I've ordered a dispatch of emergency units for now.
Our forces are spread thin with all the explosions going off everywhere!
Are the armed forces even doing anything?!
What's the status on them?
Dispatch the Supernatural Disaster Countermeasures Division.
Squad One is armed and ready to go.
Mobilize Squad Four as well!
Right now, numerous explosions believed to be
caused by ESP users are occurring across the city.
The armed forces are on the
ground at the areas in question.
It is strongly suspected that the perpetrators are connected to the National Diet Building incident.
Changes in Train Line Schedules
The perpetrators are also suspected to have had some part in the Tokyo Tower Incident last June.
Citizens should follow the evacuation orders and relocate to safe-zones until the situation subsides.
Strike three! Humanity's out!
As we look down below, we can see the current situation in Tokyo.
ESP users are targeting a number of areas through explosions, fires, and other destructive acts.
Another explosion!
Don't panic!
Don't panic, and follow
the evacuation guidelines!
The Diet is held in the air!
Terrorist attacks in Tokyo
Changes in Train Line Schedules
Is there nothing we can do against their power?
Is it too late to hope for saviors like the girl
with the white hair and her group to appear?
"The girl with the white hair"?
Was there someone like that?
They were a group of espers, but they disappeared.
Look at this!
A helicopter is approaching
the National Diet Building!
I can't identify it, but it might be our white-haired savior or her allies!
We will fast-rope into the building and rescue the hostages inside.
Remember, we're dealing with ESP users here.
They're no ordinary humans, so stay aler—
Captain!
I guess she's not here.
Don't move!
What are you doing here with those weapons?
Stop right there!
You bitch...
You're nothing but target practice when you're wide open like that!
This is Special Unit 7-7.
We've encountered an ESP user.
Special Unit 7-7, this is Mission Control.
All ESP users you come across are to be eliminated.
You also have permission to use lethal force.
Fire at will.
Weapons free, huh.
Special Unit 7-7, this is Special Unit 5-5.
This is Special Unit 7-7.
What is it, Masahi?
That girl in front of you appears to have some connection with that stuff on the news.
Think you can capture her?
We're dealing with a Teleporter here,
so I can't make any promises.
Natsuki!
Drive your bike straight at that girl on my signal.
But I doubt that'd be effective against someone like her.
I'm counting on you!
Now, Natsuki!
Did we get her?
I told you to capture her...
My faith in you, Amida Buddha.
My bike...
Sorry. I'll make it up to you.
Come back, Minami.
There's no need for impatience. The girl will come in due time.
Understood.
What is that?
It disappeared?
TOKYO ESP
The White Haired Girl
These guys look like trouble...
Attention to all ESP users and anyone involved.
Lay down your weapons and release the hostages.
Any refusal to comply will be answered with lethal force.
We repeat:
Lay down your weapons and release the hostages.
All law-breakers and ESP users are to—
Humanity is finally showing signs of life.
Damn those espers...
Hey, when is the girl
with the white hair coming?
A girl with white hair?
Yup.
See?
Oh, her.
In times like these, she comes and saves people, right?
Was the girl with the white hair...
She's some kind of hero, right?
The white-haired girl...
An old friend of mine was saved by her once.
Really?
Like hell she'd come and save us!
She's just another esper, like those criminals causing this mayhem!
Espers are humans, just like us.
There's all kinds of them out there.
If she were here, she'd help us escape
even if she wound up bruised and broken.
Onii-chan, are you friends with the girl with the white hair?
You brat... You think you've
got it all figured out, huh?
And like she'd be able to help this situation all on her own, anyway!
But she's not alone.
Murasaki!
Ayumu-kun!
You came all the way out here?
Yeah.
It just didn't feel right to sit tight and wait.
Have you heard anything about Rinka yet?
But I can't imagine that she
would do nothing about this!
She'll come back!
You're right.
I can use this to see what
those attackers are planning.
With your power of Psychometry...
I figured out Peggi was safe
the same way through these.
Wait, these—You went to other areas under fire?!
Yup.
Don't give me that!
What if something happened to you out there?
But there isn't much else I can do to help.
I want to do the best with what I have.
What's wrong?
They're planning to drop the
National Diet Building somewhere!
Ayumu-kun!
My mother is still there!
Onii-chan!
You're the girl from before...
I have something
I want your friend to know!
I want to thank her
for saving me!
Oh, aren't you enjoying yourselves?
I hope none of you are hurt.
My, they're still alive!
That calls for a reward, I guess.
This place will blow up in exactly five minutes!
Mama!
That woman...
Stop it!
Huh?
No can do!
You can't step beyond this line!
Mama! Mama!
Nana-chan, run! Don't come closer!
My, this is bringing tears to my eyes!
Little girl, your mother's about to become one with the stars.
She's going to twinkle like a little star!
Stop messing with us!
Come on! Remove this barrier and let them go!
I'll remove it when it
hits the last five seconds.
Otherwise I'd be a goner, too!
Onii-chan!
Mama is in there...
Mama!
Please! Take her and get away from here!
Hurry and run!
No!
Mama!
Murasaki...
We can't give up yet!
It's not too late! It never is!
You're wasting your time!
You'll never tear my barrier of air down if you're this weak.
Really now?
Huh?
How 'bout a taste of my brute strength
when I pound that barrier right into you?
Kobushi-san, I managed to defuse the bomb.
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
A mere pistol won't be enough
to take any of us down.
You're all espers?
I'll have you know that
not all espers are criminals.
There's definitely one person
who comes to mind.
When scum like you tried
causing a ruckus before,
that idiot threw herself right at 'em.
Retreat! Retreat!
Skull-Smashing Kick!
That girl with the white hair is finally here.
Urushiba!
araburu tamashii e shukufuku no kuchizuke wo
A savage soul is saved by a kiss
ame ni yaburarete tsukurareta hiji no
and sheltered from the relentless rain.
furueteta sono mune no naraku e to maboroshi ga
Its heart trembles from the secrets held
surinukeru
in its flickering visions of Hell.
ano me no yoku ni
Are you drawn to the greed
sono hitomi wa hikareteru ka
that gleams in its eyes?
takanaru mune mo
Feel the panic rise up in your chest!
sou yo shin wa shinseigi ka
Is this the truth that will change the world?
kotoba wo hanate
Set your words free!
kurushiku daketemo tanoshii ne
Joy can still be found outside of that embrace
kowareru tabi ni kiku to omou
that we have every time we break down.
idonde wa yabure karada wa
We will push until our bodies break
barairo ni nijinde saku
and you bloom deep red.
ai ga kimi no chi wo
Let my love become your blood
hi ni somare
and set your feelings aflame.
araburi tsuki wa yoru ni
The crimson moon lashes out,
tozasare maboroshi ni ochita
only to be locked away, trapped in its own illusion.
TOKYO ESP
Girl Meets Boy