Who are you?
People refer me as "Professor."
Now then, let the lesson begin.
nan byaku nan sen nen mo
No matter the hundreds and
thousands of years between us
iroasenai telepathy
this unbreakable telepathy we share
douka tsunagatte
will keep us connected.
our bond glows strong
Our bond glows strong.
TOKYO ESP
hanpirei suru yume semete agaite
We struggle to close the distance our dreams have put between us.
TOKYO ESP
zero hearts
Zero Hearts!
kodou no pulse wo compass ni shite
Let my beating heart guide you back towards me.
zero hearts
Zero Hearts!
reincarnation nazeka kamisama wa konna kotoba sae
Why would the gods let the word "reincarnation" remain
gense ni nokoshi
in the world that we live in?
biru no mashita kaze no zankyou no naka de
Under these buildings in the howling winds,
kibou no hikari sagasu te ni wa
our hope shines towards our dreams.
juuryoku sae mo chigiri keshite mada tsuyoku
We'll tear away from the gravity that binds us and grow stronger!
aa zero ni naru shinka wo
Even if you hit rock bottom,
osorezu ni tondeyuke
don't be afraid to take flight and find another way.
kokoro wo gyutto tashikameatta kizuna to iu na no tsubasa
This connection we found with our hearts will become our wings.
nanajuuoku bun no ichi
No matter what comes my way,
yuzurenai jibun no iro de
not even a fraction of it will prevent me
kimi wo mamorasete
from protecting you.
never forget zero hearts
Never forget, Zero Hearts!
Wh-What is this?
It's an illusion.
My ESP ability allows me to project images inside a person's mind,
causing them to hallucinate.
The touch,
taste, and even smell may seem real,
but not a single thing actually is.
That stone—
Like both of your own powers,
all of this was made possible by these shining fish.
Oops.
Oh, that's right.
You have a Collector on your side.
Just what are you planning?!
Is Peggi this Collector
you're referring to?
This is a fragment of a legendary lithograph.
It has the ability to awaken the hidden powers sealed within a living being.
To us, those abilities appear like shining fish.
I'd say it's the biggest discovery I've
come across throughout my research.
Rinka-san! I've seen this person before.
Huh?
He's the one who spread the shining fish all across Tokyo!
Really?!
Where did you see him?
It was in the memories of the fish that swam into her.
You see, in these past three months,
I've been releasing these fish outside regularly.
I knew that soon enough a Collector would appear to recover the fish.
I'm guessing it acts as a population control.
Although, I wasn't able to hypothesize
who the fish would swim into.
Why are you releasing all those fish?
Consider this question in response.
Why are you fighting?
Is it for those petty ideals of justice and peace?
Or... is it due to the love you have for Kyoutarou?
A-Azuma-san has nothing to do with it.
Regardless of your reasons,
I've taken great interest in your activities.
So what do you say?
Will you join me in creating a new world?
What do you mean, "creating a new world"?
In one week, a miracle will occur in this metropolis.
Bear witness then and reconsider my invitation.
You are the ones who have been chosen.
The time has come for you to know why.
A dream...
Is something wrong?
P-Professor?
That's what he called himself?
Yeah.
He gave me the chills...
I didn't see anything from the second floor.
Are you saying the illusion was cast on only the two of you?
I think so.
I think I know that man.
Azuma Hokusai.
He took me in and raised me.
I dropped by where Azuma
and his friends are staying.
Oh, did you bring them here?
Don't assume things.
I had a chat with the white-haired girl, that's all.
She's very much piqued my interest.
Ow.
So you're Kyoutarou-kun?
I was a friend of your mother and father.
Come with me back to Japan.
From now on, you will be attending the middle school nearby.
If you have any questions, just ask Minami.
N-Nice to meet you.
Hey, foreigner.
Is it really true you're living
together with Azuma Minami?
You're doing her, right?
What's she sound like?
Hey, call her out to the gym storage room.
What?
We're tellin' you to let us have a go at her!
Senpai!
Why you...
Can you stand?
This town is full of people like them.
Despite the apparent tranquility, it has fallen far into ruin,
but we've no other choice but to stay here.
If only this town would cease to exist.
Your voice.
Huh?
This is the first time I've heard you speak, Minami.
Jeez.
Finals are coming up,
but there's no way I can study now.
Are you still thinking about what the Professor said to you?
Yeah.
In one week, a miracle will occur in this metropolis.
My dad said to stay out of it no matter what happens,
but I can't help worrying about it.
Um, I'm sorry!
Huh?
You're probably even more worried.
No, it's all right.
If anything, I just don't want to see you get hurt.
I figured something like this might happen anyway.
Huh?
My parents were scientists
on the Professor's research team.
When I was a kid, they took me with them overseas
to where they were excavating some ancient ruins.
They told me about amazing miracles,
legendary history, and unexplored myths.
That could be the reason though.
When I gained these abilities, I felt it had something to do with my parents' work.
In fact, it's possible that my parents' deaths
and even the civil war were
connected to the Professor's research.
Anyway, if it turns out that
Minami's being controlled by him,
there's no way I'd just "stay out of it."
What's with me lately?
A lot of crazy things have been happening,
but when I'm with Azuma-san, I feel at ease.
Why are you fighting?
Is it for those petty ideals of justice and peace?
Or... is it due to the love you have for Kyoutarou?
Wait, Minami!
I wonder what I am to Azuma-san.
There hasn't been anything big on the news so far...
Miracle?
Take me with you if anything happens.
Huh?
I could be able to help you with my ESP abilities!
Thanks, but it'll be too dangerous if a fight breaks out.
And nothing could end up—
Excuse me.
I'm Nabeshima from Ueno's First Investigation Division.
We'd like to ask a few questions regarding the white-haired girl incidents.
Metropolitan
Police Department
Kagura Soba
You will return with us to the police station.
You people sure are making a lot of racket this morning.
Dad!
Urushiba-san...
How did I guess that she'd be your daughter?
Long time no see, Nabeshima.
Merayama from the Hotokeda clan told us everything he knew.
Now, why don't you tell us
about these supernatural powers of yours?
Nabeshima-san, it's an emergency!
We've received a message from headquarters, and—
What's going on?
An earthquake?
That's...
What is that?
Just what on earth...
are you going to do with that, Professor?!
Now then, let the fun begin.
TOKYO ESP
The Encounter, The Illusion And The Girl
The birth of the new world begins here.
Yo, Azuma, you free right now?
Kobushi-chan?
This is their work, right?
Yeah.
I'd say so.
Sounds like fun.
So, what d'you say we get on that thing?
What?! A tanker is floating through the sky?
Yes, and it's heading slowly towards the city center.
Unbelievable.
Hey, don't you dare stick your head into this.
O-Okay, I got it already.
Rinka-san.
Don't mind us and go!
But...
if I escape with my ESP powers, you two will—
It's fine.
I'm not alone anymore, remember?
Murasaki-chan...
Hm? Hey, Rinka—
Dad, I'm sorry!
Get back here, Rinka!
Mom used to sing that song a lot.
Yes, and today marks the anniversary of her passing.
The white-haired girl is on her way here.
Why did you try to make her join us?
She doesn't look like she'd be of very much use to us.
You'll see why soon enough.
Guide to Shibuya
My, isn't this just the most fabulous city?
Looks like it's the real deal.
Yeah.
Let's look around and see if anybody's inside.
We're leaving as soon as I get my hands on that stone.
What?!
Kobushi-chan, that's a bit—
To the one flying this ship,
change your course immediately!
I repeat! To the one flying this ship—
Azuma!
Can you breathe?!
Hey!
It has been a very long time, Kyoutarou.
You know,
you were sprawled on the ground like that in our first encounter too.
Professor...
You're not playing fair, Onee-sama.
Seriously.
You're weaker, less pretty,
and clearly the inferior thief,
yet you've taken on the name, "Black Fist"?
Don't you think you're a bit full of yourself?
I really don't have the time to deal with you, Kozuki!
Kozuki, this power...
It's all thanks to the shining fish.
Annoying pricks of a feather flock together, don't they?
What a shame.
It seems that no one understands.
Understand what?
Would you please die, Onee-sama?
Kobushi-chan!
Now then, is that injury...
even real?
It's futile.
I can change every destination you picture teleporting to.
Even if you know they're only illusions, you can't break free.
I've even hidden my true face from you since we first met.
Behold, Kyoutarou.
This is how it really looks.
This is my true face.
No way...
Don't be fooled, Azuma!
This is obviously just another of his illusions!
I don't need to put up with a petty thief.
Minami.
Understood.
Stop, Minami!
Azuma-san!
We can't get any closer than this!
Orders are to pull back.
Please wait!
What's going on with those people on deck?
It's no use.
I can't make it budge.
Forget about me.
Go on. Take Kobushi-chan and get out of here.
She was shot in the shoulder, and—
So you're finally here,
Urushiba Rinka.
Just what do you intend on doing by levitating this ship?!
What if I said
I'm going to drop it?
There's nothing any of you can do to stop me.
I won't let you.
I definitely won't let you!
You sure talk like some kind of idealistic hero.
You're nothing but a spineless, soft-hearted imbecile though...
and you don't even know to pick your fights.
Seeing you walk around like you own the place
is becoming an eyesore.
Stop it, Minami!
You've got to break free from the Professor's control and come back to your senses!
"His control?"
I'm—
I'm here by my own will.
This is all for the sake of creating a new world, Kyoutarou.
And in order to do so,
one must begin by purging all existing ideals.
The time has come for the superior
beings to seize control from humanity!
This is a message to all of humanity.
We are espers.
The tanker ship you're all seeing at this very moment is not an illusion.
We have thrown off the shackles of mankind's expectations of society and science...
Where did this video come from?
and have come here to call upon our fellow brethren.
What? From an external source?!
It stopped?!
And now,
as recognition of our superiority,
we hereby demand the establishment of a special esper zone in Tokyo.
Rinka-san!
The ship!
What the hell are they trying to do?
Kyoutarou, I hope it's very clear to you now.
As weak as you are, you will only know defeat if you attempt to stop us.
Give up, Kyoutarou.
Rinka-san!
araburu tamashii wa shukufuku no kuchizuke wo
A blessed kiss is granted to my unbridled soul.
annei yaburarete tsukurareta hinichijou
Severed from the peace I once knew, my life tumults into chaos
urotaeta sono mune no naraku e to maboroshi ga surinukeru
and apparitions slip into the dark depths of my restless heart.
onore no yoku ni
Have you been blinded
sono hitomi wa kegaretieru ka
by the greed that resides inside?
takanaru mune no
Feel your quickening heartbeat.
sono ishi wa shin ni seigi ka
Is your resolve what you believe to be real and true?
kotoba wo hanate
I'll set my words free!
kobushi kudaketemo tamashii ga
No matter how many times I'm crushed,
kowarenu kagiri ikudo mo
if my spirit stays strong, I won't be broken.
idonde wa yabure karada wa
My body bursts into a splash of red
barairo ni nijinde saku
but that won't stop my assault.
akeki inochi yo gin ni somare
My blood-red life will be bathed in silver.
araburi tsuki wa yoru ni
The savage moon lashes out,
tokasare maboroshi ni ochita
only to melt away into its own illusion.
TOKYO ESP
Each Girl, Each Affection