That bastard Hotokeda.
How dare he kidnap the Miss!
Ready your weapons! This is war!
Calm down.
I'm going alone first.
I don't care what he's become.
I'm going to settle this.
This is my responsibility.
Boss...
Murasaki.
nan byaku nan sen nen mo
No matter the hundreds
and thousands of years between us
iroasenai telepathy
this unbreakable telepathy we share
douka tsunagatte
will keep us connected.
our bond glows strong
Our bond glows strong.
TOKYO ESP
hanpirei suru yume semete agaite
We struggle to close the distance our dreams have put between us.
TOKYO ESP
zero hearts
Zero Hearts!
kodou no pulse wo compass ni shite
Let my beating heart guide you back towards me.
zero hearts
Zero Hearts!
reincarnation nazeka kamisama wa konna kotoba sae
Why would the gods let the word "reincarnation" remain
gense ni nokoshi
in the world that we live in?
biru no mashita kaze no zankyou no naka de
Under these buildings in the howling winds,
kibou no hikari sagasu te ni wa
our hope shines towards our dreams.
juuryoku sae mo chigiri keshite mada tsuyoku
We'll tear away from the gravity that binds us and grow stronger!
aa zero ni naru shinka wo
Even if you hit rock bottom,
osorezu ni tondeyuke
don't be afraid to take flight and find another way.
kokoro wo gyutto tashikameatta kizuna to iu na no tsubasa
This connection we found with our hearts will become our wings.
nanajuuoku bun no ichi
No matter what comes my way,
yuzurenai jibun no iro de
not even a fraction of it will prevent me
kimi wo mamorasete
from protecting you.
never forget zero hearts
Never forget, Zero Hearts!
What's going on?
Who the hell are you?!
You bitch!
You're strong.
What were those moves?
It's Kali, a martial art.
My dad taught me when he was still a police officer.
You ain't human. That's for sure.
Anyone else'd be on a hospital bed with those injuries.
Where's the girl you kidnapped?
She's in that room over there.
If you want to take her home, she's yours.
Thievery is more my forte, anyway.
And I've had my eyes on something
worth more than these pathetic thugs.
What do you think you're doing?
I'll be taking this with me.
What? Weren't they working together?
Rinka-san.
This is our chance to rescue Murasaki-chan.
Right.
Murasaki-chan!
Just what're ya think ya doin'?!
Damn it!
My body is enveloped in a psychokinetic barrier.
If you're serious on taking me out,
you better have brought a nuke!
Wh-What?!
Did it just... eat that shining fish?!
You bastards!
What did you two do to me?!
Rinka-san!
A stone that lures those shining fish, huh?
That's a hell of a score!
Stop right there, young lady.
That stone has value beyond your comprehension.
Give it up.
Huh? The hell are you?
Damn it, that Rinka.
Huh?
He's strong.
Is he with that guy in the warrior getup?
This looks bad.
Young lady, are you all right?
I don't know what happened, but it looks pretty serious.
Y-Yeah...
Hand over that girl.
You're a determined creep, aren't you?
Looks like I'll have to take you seriously.
That hurts!
It worked?!
Azuma-san! Take Murasaki-chan!
Got it!
Skull-Smashing...
Psy-Kick!
Hm?
Murasaki!
I'm here to rescue you!
Thank goodness, you're safe.
You're really amazing.
But at any rate,
why did your attack work on him this time?
I wonder if it's because Peggi ate that shining fish earlier.
Hey, Rinka!
Are you all right?
Dad!
Eh?!
Wait, you're—
Well, well.
And here I told you to stay out of this.
You're being very difficult.
Just who are you?
You never told me I'd lose my powers like this.
You said someday I'd rule the world.
That's why I agreed to spread those shining fish!
Clearly, you were never cut out for it.
Well, I suppose we'll settle for
confirming the existence of a Collector.
So you're free to go.
Who exactly are you?!
For now, simply think of me—
as a herald of catastrophe.
It can't be!
We will bring change to this world.
Abandon your cheap ideals
of justice and join me at my side,
Kyoutarou.
Minami.
Why?
Why are you doing this?!
Wait, you bastard!
Whatever your decision,
do not interfere any further,
or I shall strike you down
the next time we cross paths.
Wait, Minami!
What just happened?
No way...
Why would Minami...
Why?
Really now...
I'm fine with letting you stay
until you find a new home but...
Thanks for the food.
Is this girl a friend of yours?
I'm her life-long rival!
What does that even mean?
Why are you still with us, anyway?
Until I hear from Azuma about
who exactly that girl is,
I ain't leavin'.
You say that, but...
I haven't heard from him since then,
and he won't even pick up his phone...
Thanks, that really helped.
Rinka,
I ran a background check on Azuma.
Huh?
He was just a child when his parents died on foreign soil,
and was left behind in the midst of a civil war.
Kyoutarou!
Lignier!
Lignier... not you, too.
Damn it. You brats—
Huh?
Where are you,
Minami?
Rinka-chan!
Take this coffee to Table 1.
Okay!
Huh?!
You're hanging around here too?!
Graduation Album
Gomuri Middle School
I thought I'd show this to you.
Graduation Album
Gomuri Middle School
I did some of my own research off of Mister's findings.
Hosogu  Masami
Taniya Ryouko
Mister?
A-Anyway, it turns out
Ishida Kenta
Hiroda Takeshi
Azuma Minami
that girl is his foster sister.
She's the daughter of the man who adopted him.
Currently, their whereabouts are unknown,
and any data on the father has been wiped clean
so any record of him comes up blank.
So what does that mean?
It means they've been planning something.
I'll bet you,
Azuma's probably catching up with them right about now.
That can't be true!
Well, they're family, after all.
That's why it's our duty to uphold justice!
Only those with a power like this can do anything about it.
TOKYO ESP
The Rain, The Ring And The Girl
Where have you gone, Azuma-san?
Minami...
So that's where you were, you damn crow!
You're—
Now tell me where that girl and Rindou are!
What do you want with them?!
I'm going to burn them to a crisp!
I found you!
You—
Take this!
What?!
What were you doing, Azuma-san?
Sorry.
The last time I saw her was about two years ago.
She and her father disappeared after that.
It's just... on that last day I saw her...
She was crying.
I'm guessing that...
something was already
going on with her at that point.
Do you think it was related
to these supernatural powers?
Probably.
Though, she wasn't the type
of girl to turn to crime.
That's why I wanted to find her and ask her what's going on.
You're right.
I'll help you look for her, too.
Huh?
It'd be too dangerous
if I let you go alone.
A miracle!
You really are my hero after all!
What?
You really don't remember?
About half a year ago?
I was attacked by a group of delinquents,
but no one would try to get close and
walked by like nothing was happening.
I never could stand people like that.
These are bad guys, right?
Yeah.
That's good, then!
At the time, you ignored the danger you were putting yourself into
and saved me out there.
Your heroic appearance was like a miracle!
I'm not a hero at all, really.
But if something were to happen...
Does this mean you're thinking
seriously about becoming a superhero?
Huh?
It's a miracle!
I'm sure you'll become the strongest hero out there!
There's one thing I want you to promise me.
No matter what happens next,
don't leave me behind.
Of course!
Great!
I'll take you out on a theme park date then!
Huh?! Y-You don't have to...
This blows.
I finally found him, but it looks like I wasted my time.
Built by Toshima Ward
East Ikebukuro Central Park
What?!
You came into contact with those shining fish, too?
Yeah.
I get strange visions whenever I touch things.
Hm... She might have psychometry.
It's the ability to see the history of an object.
H-Hold on.
Do supernatural powers even exist in the first place?
Yes.
The truth is, we have them, too.
We're espers.
U-Unbelievable!
Are you two even human?!
That's a rude thing to say to them!
I mean, it was our conflict
that forced them to get involved.
You both came to save me
even though you were injured badly.
If my own family chooses to treat you like monsters,
then I don't want to go back home!
Murasaki!
Her hairstyle's not the only thing that's changed about her, huh?
I'm leaving home.
Really now...
It's nice to have all this company,
but should I be expecting more of you?
Well, leaving them out didn't seem right.
I'll definitely repay you for your kindness someday.
You ran away from home?
I used to do a lot of that.
I'm doing it right now, actually.
I'm right there with you.
Um...who is this person?
A strange and self-centered girl.
Just eat up, for now.
Humans can do anything as long
as they've got their stomach filled.
Thank you.
Murasaki-chan, hang in there!
I-I'm okay.
We should have you practice ways to control your power.
Our powers can trigger on
their own if we don't watch out.
Okay.
How pathetic.
You won't survive on your own that way.
She's not alone.
Murasaki-chan has us!
You're too naive.
You were brought up with love and care from a wonderful man like this,
so you wouldn't know how tough it can get in the real world.
What do your parents do for a living?
I never met them, and I was raised
by my grandma, so I wouldn't know.
I never met my mom, either.
Huh?
She died soon after giving birth to me.
Well, I'm not going to tell you how to live your life,
but I won't sit and watch you commit crimes.
They'll limit what you can do in life and cage you until the very end.
I...
want to become strong like Rinka-san!
Huh?
So, please, teach me!
I'll learn everything that I have to.
With this power, I wouldn't even be able to protect myself.
Murasaki-chan...
I know you've no intent
of coming back any time soon,
but I brought a few things
that I thought you might need.
There's also this.
This belonged to your mother.
I'm sorry.
I always felt terrible about our family life.
I wasn't able to manage being both a father and a Boss,
and I couldn't do enough for you.
If you really do have the ability to see the past,
I'd want you to know her warmth from that ring.
What the hell?
She has a family that actually wants to come and see her.
I leave my daughter in your care.
Of course.
Hey, Mister.
What is it?
If I were your daughter, would you have raised me with love like that?
Of course.
I'd do everything I could to take care of you,
so I wouldn't have any regrets.
itsu no ma ni ka wasureteita
Before I knew it, I had already forgotten.
hitori datte kimetsukete
I made myself believe I was all alone.
zutto koko ni nokotteiru tashikana kioku
These memories will always lie here waiting
kizuku sono toki made
for you to find them.
Murasaki-chan.
I wonder if this is what you'd call a miracle.
fureru you ni tsutawattano
Your warm and gentle affection
Huh?
It was like I met my mom—
No,
my family, for the very first time.
atatakai yasashisa ga
feels so real to me now.
yubisaki kara kokoro wo kumou
Your love travels from your fingertips
We all meet through a series of coincidences.
And with small bits of courage, we are brought closer together.
tsutsumu ai
and caresses my heart.
Most people wouldn't be able to understand our lives,
but I felt that this moment was truly wonderful.
A miracle, huh?
Psychometry, was it?
You've awakened to a very interesting power.
Wh-Who are you?
People refer me as "Professor."
Now then, let the lesson begin.
TOKYO ESP
The Encounter, The
Illusion And The Girl