Minami.
Leave the unimportant ones to me.
As you will.
Urushiba!
Rinka...
It's him!
He's the levitator controlling the National Diet Building!
Fire!
What?!
I'm the one who trained Minami and our men over the past few years.
To try and take me down with those
is laughable!
Is this guy a Qigong master?!
nan byaku nan sen nen mo
No matter the hundreds and
thousands of years between us
iroasenai telepathy
this unbreakable telepathy we share
douka tsunagatte
will keep us connected.
our bond glows strong
Our bond glows strong.
TOKYO ESP
hanpirei suru yume semete agaite
We struggle to close the distance our dreams have put between us.
TOKYO ESP
zero hearts
Zero Hearts!
kodou no pulse wo compass ni shite
Let my beating heart guide you back towards me.
zero hearts
Zero Hearts!
reincarnation nazeka kamisama wa konna kotoba sae
Why would the gods let the word "reincarnation" remain
gense ni nokoshi
in the world that we live in?
biru no mashita kaze no zankyou no naka de
Under these buildings in the howling winds,
kibou no hikari sagasu te ni wa
our hope shines towards our dreams.
juuryoku sae mo chigiri keshite mada tsuyoku
We'll tear away from the gravity that binds us and grow stronger!
aa zero ni naru shinka wo
Even if you hit rock bottom,
osorezu ni tondeyuke
don't be afraid to take flight and find another way.
kokoro wo gyutto tashikameatta kizuna to iu na no tsubasa
This connection we found with our hearts will become our wings.
nanajuuoku bun no ichi
No matter what comes my way,
yuzurenai jibun no iro de
not even a fraction of it will prevent me
kimi wo mamorasete
from protecting you.
never forget zero hearts
Never forget, Zero Hearts!
Die, Urushiba!
Where's Azuma-san?!
Bring him back!
That's impossible.
He's dead.
I killed him myself.
You're lying!
You two were family! There's no way you would!
What do you know?!
You selfishly dragged him into this fight for your own goals!
Don't talk like you know everything!
Especially about him.
You don't know anything about us...
You don't know anything at all!
As if...
As if you'd know anything
about my Kyoutarou.
This world...
I'll wipe clean this world of humans.
You can't do that.
You can resent someone,
want to hurt them, and fight them.
You can even love them.
Don't you see that espers feel the same things humans do?!
Nothing will change.
Even if you replace the current world order with your new rules,
nothing will change!
That's why Azuma-san didn't
want you to be a part of this fight!
Why couldn't you believe in him?!
If...
If only all of you believed in him...
Things could've turned out differently between espers and humans.
If you're not willing to fight,
you can mark your grave here!
I won't lose him to you!
I don't care how many I need to kill.
I'm going to bring him with me into the new world!
He's alive.
I knew it. Azuma-san is still...
Why, you—
Skull-Smashing Psy-Kick!
Skull-Smashing
Psy-Kick!!
Are you two all right?!
Regent!
We've come so far only to meet our end here?
Stop, Peggi!
That's not all.
That's not all I had, Afro.
Ayumu-kun!
This isn't an afro.
These are natural curls!
Run!
This one is too strong for any of you!
You don't say?
Well, I ain't been holin' myself up somewhere for the past few months for nothin'.
Guess this shows my training's paid off.
Now, stay down!
Everyone, grab on to something!
The National Diet Building is going to fall!
Dad!
Stop!
It stopped.
Are we going to make it out of here, then?
Miracle.
His wounds need to be tended to!
Understood!
Ayumu!
Mom!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Ayumu.
Thanks, Mom.
Wasn't this...
what that enemy was using earlier...?
Hey, Rinka!
Sage!
You're all right!
Sage, where are the Professor and his group?
Not anywhere close.
It appears they made their escape
before the National Diet Building fell.
I see.
Rinka-san!
It's not over yet!
Eh?
This was just a decoy!
The Professor is planning to spread the shining fish all over Tokyo through electromagnetic waves!
His true target was that place all along!
That place...?
Tokyo Sky Tree!
Wh-What's happening to the sky?
We've been had.
The biggest disadvantage the Professor had were his small numbers,
but he's turned the tables on us now.
It's spiraled far beyond any kind of control the government can have over him.
The true birth of the new race, "Esper", is going to take place here in Tokyo.
This is our victory.
Now, this city will belong to us espers.
You won't be able to do a thing.
Minami!
Rinka-san!
Peggi, I need your help.
You have to stop.
You've been fighting since we left the facility,
and in your current condition, your body can't take it.
I can keep on going.
I can!
Hey now.
You're not thinkin' of goin' in there like
it's the bottom of the bucket list, are you?
Wh-When did you—
If you went and died,
Mister's gonna be sick with grief.
Kobushi-chan...
Are you saying that you'll fight together with me?
Don't be dumb.
Just make sure you tell him
how cool I was after we get out.
Sure.
What's going on?
We're surrounded by the shining fish.
Azuma-san would definitely...
keep forging ahead with all his strength!
He'd absolutely keep forging ahead!
Evacuation Orders For
City Center Residents
Tonight Snowing In Kanto Region
Watch Your Step
Foreign Social Security Force
Random Acts of Terrorism On
Programs
New Message Recieved
We've received our orders.
It looks like they've found the location of the Ark.
You know, you shouldn't eat before work,
Sister.
Here I was planning to find
an opportunity to steal the Ark,
but it looks like I'm in
for more than I bargained for.
I'm terribly sorry.
That's fine.
You've done more than enough.
With our plans coming to fruition, it's dangerous for us to stay here.
You two leave first.
What about you, Father?
I have to stay here,
and wait for someone.
I've found you!
I will be your opponent.
Urushiba Rinka.
You've surpassed all of my expectations of you.
Now then,
which is the real me?
Where do you think you're going?
There's no place to hide here!
Kobushi-chan, now!
Kobushi-chan!
Even if you hide yourself from my sight,
it's pointless if you can't
hide your malicious intent.
It looks like this is the best you can do,
white-haired girl.
Just a little more...
It was just a little more...
Just a little more, and I would've been with Azuma-san.
After all it took to get here...
Azuma... san...
Kyoutarou?!
Your illusions can be easily nullified by someone who holds the same powers as yourself.
I knew it.
You've been fighting
and running yourself ragged.
This is amazing.
As I thought, your strings of fate connect you to me.
Minami,
finish off Kyoutarou.
This time... where I can see it.
Kyoutarou won't be able
to lift a hand against you.
Oh my.
Why?
Why does it have to be her?!
Minami...
Thank you, Minami.
I'm grateful from the bottom of
my heart that you treasure me so,
but that day...
when you left me without a trace,
I was a little sad.
That was...
It wasn't because I was left behind.
It was because I couldn't do anything for you,
and I realized afterwards how helpless I was.
Rinka-san saved someone like me.
She believed in my words and actions.
That's why I was able to believe in her in return.
Back then, if you—
No,
if I had believed in you,
then I would've wanted you to let me protect you.
Kozuki-kun,
take the Ark and Minami with you.
I can't let them have it just yet.
"Them"?
Now, go!
Minami!
Kyoutarou...
Kyoutarou!
I-I'm not the one to blame!
Now, Kyoutarou,
if you want to kill me,
this is the best chance you'll ever get.
Why...
Why, of all people,
do you refrain from killing me?
You had countless opportunities to kill me!
Was your reason for saving me that day
that you wanted someone to stop you?!
You're wrong.
It was because sensed a miracle within you.
This is all part of a greater plan.
Azuma-san.
Professor!
Looks like they've finally taken the bait.
Leave, Kyoutarou!
This is the path I've chosen.
Go on and live.
Become a hero.
Hey, what the hell is that?!
Happy New Year
Thunder Gate
It's been but seven days since then.
The city has turned to anarchy.
Crime is on the rise overall,
and it is because of the sudden increase in unchecked esper activities.
What's going to happen to this city?
I don't know.
For now, we keep our heads low.
I'd rather not get ourselves caught in some mess again.
Damn it!
Not even risking our lives
was enough to save the world.
In the end,
we weren't able to do anything.
It's not over.
It's not over just yet.
The situation might've gotten worse,
but our ideas of justice haven't changed!
Rinka-san.
What we need to do
should still be the same, so...
Let's do it, Azuma-san!
Only those with a power like this can do anything about it, right?
Yeah.
I put a lot into today's breakfast.
You're not eating today either?
Goodness.
It's the New Year today, too.
Oh?
Burglary Takes Place Right
In Front Of Cameras
Live From Taito Ward
I'm at a robbery.
In front of our cameras, there's—
A little girl!
Wait, you fiend!
Call me "Crow Head"!
I am a Defender of Justice!
They're here!
Our heroes, the white-haired girl and Crow Head
Goodness, heroes?
along with their friends!
They're easygoing, aren't they?
A hero.
Die, you costumed bastard!
I know the meaning of "justice"
depends on each person's perspective,
and I now know my motivations, my fears, and my limitations.
Despite that,
if the person I love feels
that same love towards me,
and if I can become a light for someone else,
TOKYO ESP
there's a reason for me to fight!
Tokyo ESP Girl