I wonder how my husband
and I ended up tying the knot.
Maybe because we knew each other's faults?
I won't be able to make you happy.
Because there's no gap
between our ideals and reality?
Well, I'm in this dress,
so as a woman, I guess that's
enough to make me happy.
Or maybe because we were able
to fall in love in spite of all that.
I can make myself happy,
so try to do the same for yourself.
Love sure takes many forms...
There's nothing to do here but swim.
I don't want to get sunburnt.
I wanted to see you in a bikini...
Well, if it's in the room...
They promptly fucked like rabbits.
THEY
PROMPTLY
FUCKED
LIKE
RABBITS.
l
All in all, it was a pretty boring honeymoon,
but I was strangely satisfied.
I can't understand what my husband is saying.
j
,
How I Got Into Hobbies
I Don't Understand
My husband is two years younger than me.
He's what you'd call an otaku,
so he's the type of organism
that lives and dies over anime.
I never understood that kind of stuff...
Is it interesting?
"Interesting"?
Mashiro-tan is mai waifu!
I'm your wife!
I Can't Understand What My Husband Is Saying
My husband scrapes out a living
as what they call a "blogger".
It's impressive that you can
make a living off of that.
I'm not about to work myself
to death like everybody else.
You really do hate working, don't you?
To work is to die!
I'd sooner drop dead than effort!
How are we going to survive?
I Can't Understand What My Husband Is Saying
You work, you lose. I think.
Get these things out of the living room!
You're bringing shame upon your family!
Whoopsies! I forgot to put
them away after I used them.
"Used"? Not "read"?
There's nothing but boobs in this thing!
Do all guys have nothing
but tits on the brain?
Damn straight.
I...
We are titties!
What the hell do you mean, "we"?!
I Can't Understand What My Husband Is Saying
Titties!
So moe...
He really likes that... Like this?
Moe sensors...
Engaged!
I Can't Understand What My Husband Is Saying
Business
Smile
It's our day off, so let's go out somewhere.
I couldn't go to sleep.
I was caught up in a flame war.
Did you put it out?
If you insist...
Make me feel moe!
Meow.
I'm guessing you want
to see something animated.
Well, I'd like to write
a review for my blog, so...
After
The
Movie
That was pretty fun.
The whole setting was completely cliché and bereft of originality.
The MC disappeared out of nowhere,
and the subplot was especially sluggish.
The flashy effects, composition,
and the overall appeal to kids is all fine and dandy,
but that ultimately subdues the idea that adults will enjoy it too.
It felt like a cash-grab and I quickly lost interest.
Well, I'm sorry I didn't take
all that into consideration.
I Can't Understand What My Husband Is Saying
Let's head home.
No, let's hit that up first.
Um...
Ah...
Whatever.
Get your shit together~
Get
your
shit
together~
Won't you please, my love~
Won't
you
please,
my
love~
Living with you is fun.
Living
with
you
is
fun.
Being together fills me with joy.
Being
together
fills
me
with
joy.
Hell if I know why, but it makes me happy~
Hell
if
I
know
why,
but
it
makes
me
happy~