Kame Soba Closing Hours
New orders came in!
Two sobas and one soki.
Niina?
What are you doing?
I tried making some food as well.
How's that?
Can I add it to the menu?
Not a chance!
Why not? I put a lot of effort into it...
The soba's ready.
Okay!
Niina, please don't serve that soba to a customer.
Nanafa, one bowl of soki ready to be served!
Thanks, Niina!
Sorry for the wait!
Who might you be?
Thank you for the meal.
Plain...
Lamentable...
This is unworthy of being called Okinawan soba!
As punishment, I will condemn you with a curse that will dry up the restaurant.
A water spirit?
I heard that she's a spirit who loves soba
so much that she always eats it while on her travels.
Without water,
we can't open the restaurant anymore.
Oh well, no use crying over spilled milk.
Let's go watch some fireworks!
Right, there's a fireworks festival today.
I wonder what will happen to the restaurant.
If only you'd noticed you served that dish beforehand...
It's my fault?!
How so?
First of all,
it's your fault for being such a prankster!
I guess I'll go back into the banyan tree.
The one who made the water spirit angry is me, after all.
If I'm gone, then...
Wait, Niina, where are you go—
Niina...