Hello.
Okinawa, here we come!
Another school trip in town!
Cheese! Yay!
Okinawa
So big!
Delicious!
Hello
Nanafa
A warm welcome to the students on their school trip.
Where are you girls from?
Tokyo.
We're here on a school trip.
Ah, right.
We want to experience things that most tourists wouldn't know about.
Is there anything interesting around here that only the locals are familiar with?
If that's what you're after, how about beach volleyball?
Beach volleyball?
Sounds like fun!
There they are!
They already look like roasted pig's trotters.
How long have you been here?
We've been here... since we left the restaurant.
People only play beach volleyball after the sun has gone down.
The only thing you'll find here in the afternoon is a barbecue.
We're already barbecued...
Listen up, girls.
Yes...?
When you go to the Okinawan seas, you'll be in grave danger if you don't cover your body like this.
You're the only one dressed like that, Grams.
Thanks for waiting. I brought the fish.
There's enough for everyone.
These fishes... don't seem to have eyeballs.
We wood spirits' favorite food is eyeballs, after all.
Want a bite?
N-N-No thanks!
City-folk sure are strange...
tichi taachi miichi no majimun to
1, 2, 3!  With demons
yuuchi ichichi no sanshimai
4, 5! And three sisters
muuchi nanaachi niji no hashi
6, 7! A rainbow bridge
sora kara shichisei futte kuru
drops from the Big Dipper in the sky.
tokidoki samishiku naru to
Sometimes when I feel lonely,
osora wo miageru no
I look up to the sky.
agijabi yo!
"Amazing!"
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
nan kuruu nai sa
Someday your day will come.
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
yasashii ano ko no egao ga ukande kuru
Envisioning that sweet smile of hers.
(hai hai hai!)
(Yeah yeah yeah!)
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
haato ga tokun
My heart is beating...
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
hibiku yo
...really fast!
kokoro de tsunagaru yuimaaru waarudo
It's a supporting world where hearts connect together.
Please tune
in again
next time!
Please tune
in again
next time!
Please tune
in again
next time!
Illustration: Poyoyon♡Rock
Please tune in again next time!