Hello!
In a street called Wakamichi,
she's bound to appear.
Once there was a neurotic man who had a wife so beautiful to the point that it drove him mad.
In order to relieve her husband of this stress, the wife cut off her own nose.
However, the husband began to despise his wife who had lost her beauty and tried to kill her.
He even drove nails into her feet so that she couldn't separate herself from him.
But his wife was so grieved and mortified that she left him nonetheless.
As she couldn't walk due to the nails in her feet, she walked away on her hands.
Look, the handstand ghost...
...is behind you right now!
Hello
Nanafa
Okinawan Ghost Stories.
The ear-cutting monk?
Once there was an ear-cutting monk called Ufumura Udun, who stood beside an old mansion.
He wielded a sickle and a small katana.
If he noticed a crying child, he'd take them by their ear
...and cut it off in the blink of an eye!
Look, he's preparing his tools right behind you!
You're all a bunch of scaredy-cats for being spirits yourselves.
But you know...
That ear-cutting monk might be here somewhere...
There's no way.
It's true!
I can even hear the scratching sounds sometimes!
It's the sound of him sharpening his sickle!
Wait a second.
Do you guys hear that?
Kame Soba
Hmm?
tichi taachi miichi no majimun to
1, 2, 3!  With demons
yuuchi ichichi no sanshimai
4, 5! And three sisters
muuchi nanaachi niji no hashi
6, 7! A rainbow bridge
sora kara shichisei futte kuru
drops from the Big Dipper in the sky.
tokidoki samishiku naru to
Sometimes when I feel lonely,
osora wo miageru no
I look up to the sky.
agijabi yo!
"Amazing!"
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
nan kuruu nai sa
Someday your day will come.
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
yasashii ano ko no egao ga ukande kuru
Envisioning that sweet smile of hers.
(hai hai hai!)
(Yeah yeah yeah!)
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
haato ga tokun
My heart is beating...
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
hibiku yo
...really fast!
kokoro de tsunagaru yuimaaru waarudo
It's a supporting world where hearts connect together.