Oh, hello!
Why's no one around?
There's no way people would leave home right now.
There's a baseball team representing Okinawa at the Koushien Stadium today.
Hang that up!
Who in the world would think of
calling in the middle of a match?!
Is baseball really that interesting?
Of course it is!
Hello
Nanafa
Do islanders really love baseball that much?
Without further ado, let's play some baseball too!
Yeah!
Why did I have to come too?
Niina-chan, go for it!
Prepare yourself, Niina!
Oriental Hyper Spin!
Raana went down in one hit...
Baseball is such a fearsome sport.
The child's play ends right here!
Howdy!
It's "Hello" for a girl like you!
H-Hello.
Long time no see, Niina.
She's a friend of yours?
Nope.
As a noble lion and the guardian spirit of the Kyan family,
I'm bound to be the rival of a wood spirit like you.
I will definitely not allow you to say you do not recognize me anymore!
Hmm? Cha' say somethin'?
Believe me when I say I'll make you eat your words!
Yeah right.
Here I go!
Take this!
Niina!
Spinning Fire Tornado—
SNAP
It sounds like something broke...
Fool!
tichi taachi miichi no majimun to
1, 2, 3!  With demons
yuuchi ichichi no sanshimai
4, 5! And three sisters
muuchi nanaachi niji no hashi
6, 7! A rainbow bridge
sora kara shichisei futte kuru
drops from the Big Dipper in the sky.
tokidoki samishiku naru to
Sometimes when I feel lonely,
osora wo miageru no
I look up to the sky.
agijabi yo!
"Amazing!"
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
nan kuruu nai sa
Someday your day will come.
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
yasashii ano ko no egao ga ukande kuru
Envisioning that sweet smile of hers.
(hai hai hai!)
(Yeah yeah yeah!)
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
haato ga tokun
My heart is beating...
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
hibiku yo
...really fast!
kokoro de tsunagaru yuimaaru waarudo
It's a supporting world where hearts connect together.
Please tune
in again
next time!
Please tune
in again
next time!
Please tune
in again
next time!
Illustration: Poyoyon♡Rock
Please tune in again next time!