Hello
Nanafa 5
Ah, hello.
Raana-chan, take this!
What are you doing?
Home run!
You don't hit home runs in badminton!
But hitting a home run feels a lot better!
Let's have another go.
Come on...
Kokona-chan!
Hello!
Rock
Hello
Nanafa
Kokona and her friend's mysterious powers?
Mimi-chan, Mimi-chan!
Say "Ouch" when you get hurt.
Grandpa told me that.
Come on, say "Ouch"!
Ouch!
Say it louder.
Hello there, Gramps!
Hmm? You can see our grandfather, Mimi-chan?
Yeah, I can see him!
My grandmother is a shaman, so she taught me lots of magic spells.
Wow!
I'll show them to you, Kokona-chan.
Sari sari sari, atotu utotu...
O Okinawan gods, please ease the pain of those who are suffering.
Mimi, what kind of prayer was that?
Well, I'm told it's a prayer that will discipline bullies.
I-I wasn't bullying anyone...
You just smashed away my badminton birdie!
Niina, you ate my ice cream, didn't you?
That was the last one too!
I'm so—
Wait, what's wrong with them?
Mimi-chan's prayer is super awesome!
tichi taachi miichi no majimun to
1, 2, 3!  With demons
yuuchi ichichi no sanshimai
4, 5! And three sisters
muuchi nanaachi niji no hashi
6, 7! A rainbow bridge
sora kara shichisei futte kuru
drops from the Big Dipper in the sky.
tokidoki samishiku naru to
Sometimes when I feel lonely,
osora wo miageru no
I look up to the sky.
agijabi yo!
"Amazing!"
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
nan kuruu nai sa
Someday your day will come.
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
yasashii ano ko no egao ga ukande kuru
Envisioning that sweet smile of hers.
(hai hai hai!)
(Yeah yeah yeah!)
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
haato ga tokun
My heart is beating...
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
hibiku yo
...really fast!
kokoro de tsunagaru yuimaaru waarudo
It's a supporting world where hearts connect together.
Please tune
in again
next time!
Please tune
in again
next time!
Please tune
in again
next time!
Illustration: Poyoyon♡Rock
Please tune in again next time!