Oh, hello.
So cool!
I wanna play on a taiko drum too.
Awesome.
Only men can play taiko drums a at traditional Eisa.
...or not.
The women are the dancers.
Why? Nao has her own taiko drum.
I see...
So women can play as well if it's not a traditional Eisa.
Hello
My sister is super popular!
Nanafa
Nao-senpai!
Nao is really cool!
Can I shake your hand?
And popular to boot.
Nao.
Nao!
Miyazato
Yuina
Tenth Grader
You really are the best taiko drummer!
I just love the way your beats hit my soul.
I'm really touched!
So please have this.
I put my whole heart into making these.
You stand out too much!
You're the reason I've come this far in life.
You cheater!
If you're gonna pick a fight, then beat it!
Raana
Thanks, Yuina.
What in the world?
My sister's fans usually give her presents like sweets.
What's wrong?
I can't seem to find Yuina's present.
I guess I'm better off without it, though.
Yuina has developed a very special talent...
Hogging all the sweets for herself...
Nao is quite the mean girl, isn't she?
I wouldn't have stolen them if she'd
actually given me some in the first place.
Happiness should be shared with everyone.
Don't you agree, Niina-dono?
tichi taachi miichi no majimun to
1, 2, 3!  With demons
yuuchi ichichi no sanshimai
4, 5! And three sisters
muuchi nanaachi niji no hashi
6, 7! A rainbow bridge
sora kara shichisei futte kuru
drops from the Big Dipper in the sky.
tokidoki samishiku naru to
Sometimes when I feel lonely,
osora wo miageru no
I look up to the sky.
agijabi yo!
"Amazing!"
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
nan kuruu nai sa
Someday your day will come.
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
yasashii ano ko no egao ga ukande kuru
Envisioning that sweet smile of hers.
(hai hai hai!)
(Yeah yeah yeah!)
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
haato ga tokun
My heart is beating...
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
hibiku yo
...really fast!
kokoro de tsunagaru yuimaaru waarudo
It's a supporting world where hearts connect together.
Please tune
in again
next time!
Please tune
in again
next time!
Please tune
in again
next time!
Illustration: Poyoyon♡Rock
Please tune in again next time!