Hello!
How is she holding up?
Maybe she hasn't worshiped the gods lately.
Grandpa says she's been praying all the time.
To be expected...
Hello
Nanafa
How can we cure Nanafa's cold?
What in the world are they doing?
It seems like a prayer for Nanafa.
Is there anything you want?
Something Nanafa...
...would want?
That's cold.
Aloe is the best cure for everything!
Doesn't seem to work for colds, though.
Aww...
It feels really refreshing, though.
Thanks, Kokona.
Here, Nanafa. I bought everything you might want.
Candy, fruit, and ice cream.
You should be able to find something you like.
Don't worry about me. Are you all right?
Grams, is that eyeball soup?
As if.
I hope she can at least drink this.
Oh, it's bonito soup!
Smells good.
Was this the thing...
...you wanted?
Yep.
tichi taachi miichi no majimun to
1, 2, 3!  With demons
yuuchi ichichi no sanshimai
4, 5! And three sisters
muuchi nanaachi niji no hashi
6, 7! A rainbow bridge
sora kara shichisei futte kuru
drops from the Big Dipper in the sky.
tokidoki samishiku naru to
Sometimes when I feel lonely,
osora wo miageru no
I look up to the sky.
agijabi yo!
"Amazing!"
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
nan kuruu nai sa
Someday your day will come.
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
yasashii ano ko no egao ga ukande kuru
Envisioning that sweet smile of hers.
(hai hai hai!)
(Yeah yeah yeah!)
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
haato ga tokun
My heart is beating...
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
hibiku yo
...really fast!
kokoro de tsunagaru yuimaaru waarudo
It's a supporting world where hearts connect together.