Closed today
as well
-Kame Grandma
A sudden farewell
to the wood spirits?!
When we first met, I thought
you were just some strange kid.
But before I knew it, you were almost like a part of the family.
With you, Raana, and Iina...
If only I could keep on living together with you guys,
that alone would be enough for me.
Let me have a taste.
How about adding some more bonito flakes?
Let's make something delicious together
and use it to get that water spirit to forgive us.
We apologize for what happened the other day.
Please give this a try.
Thank you for the meal.
Brown...
If this is considered Okinawan soba,
I'd praise it worthy no matter where it's served.
A perfect dish!
Well done, Nanafa.
You too, Niina.
This is my appreciation for serving such delicious soba.
A seasonal octopus.
Huh?
What's wrong?
Wood spirits can't handle octopuses at all.
sora kara shichisei futte kuru
drops from the Big Dipper in the sky.
tokidoki samishiku naru to
Sometimes when I feel lonely,
osora wo miageru no
I look up to the sky.
agijabi yo!
"Amazing!"
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
nan kuruu nai sa
Someday your day will come.
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
yasashii ano ko no egao ga ukande kuru
Envisioning that sweet smile of hers.
(hai hai hai!)
(Yeah yeah yeah!)
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
haato ga tokun
My heart is beating...
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
hibiku yo
...really fast!
kokoro de tsunagaru yuimaaru waarudo
It's a supporting world where hearts connect together.