Hello!
I'm blasting off again!
Hello
Nanafa
Rush! A battle for the toilet!
Kame
Soba
Whoa, it's crowded as hell.
That's to be expected.
The restaurant's toilet is broken, after all.
Out of order
as long as it
can't flush!
Grandma
Oh my, you have a horrible look on your face.
Silence! Hurry up and switch places with me!
No can do. It's first come, first served!
No, I'm leaking!
I'll just go and stand he—
Don't you even think about cutting in line.
Let me go!
All done.
Nanafa, you go first!
Thanks, Sis!
To stop a troubled wood spirit from using the bathroom...
You've fallen pretty low.
I wonder what your fans will think when they see you shivering like that.
Th-That has nothing to do with this.
Sis, it's all yours.
You shall not pass!
I will surely pass!
The restaurant's toilet has been fixed.
Ah, the long and painful battle finally comes to an end...
Grandma, why are you here?!
Well, now that it's fixed,
I have to give the god of the toilet my thanks.
I can't...
...hold it in anymore.
tichi taachi miichi no majimun to
1, 2, 3!  With demons
yuuchi ichichi no sanshimai
4, 5! And three sisters
muuchi nanaachi niji no hashi
6, 7! A rainbow bridge
sora kara shichisei futte kuru
drops from the Big Dipper in the sky.
tokidoki samishiku naru to
Sometimes when I feel lonely,
osora wo miageru no
I look up to the sky.
agijabi yo!
"Amazing!"
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
nan kuruu nai sa
Someday your day will come.
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
yasashii ano ko no egao ga ukande kuru
Envisioning that sweet smile of hers.
(hai hai hai!)
(Yeah yeah yeah!)
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
haato ga tokun
My heart is beating...
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
hibiku yo
...really fast!
kokoro de tsunagaru yuimaaru waarudo
It's a supporting world where hearts connect together.