Here's your soki soba.
Kyan
Nanafa
Ninth Grader
Kame
Soba
How much longer, Nanafa-chan?
You should help me out, Nao!
I'm busy right now.
Kyan
Nao
Twelfth
Grader
I'm back!
Kokona!
Kyan
Kokona
Fourth
Grader
Do you think you could help me out?
What?
Please?
Hello
Nanafa
Hello! Wood spirits?!
What?
The nail is...
Because the nail stuck into the banyan tree was removed,
this wood spirit appeared.
Really?
Where am I?
Kame Soba!
I'm Nanafa Kyan.
Hey, what's your name?
My name's Niina!
How ya doin'?
A little girl shouldn't be saying something like that!
How you do—
Say it properly!
Huh?
What's it matter to you?
You're just a hard-headed old granny.
What'd ya say?
You makin' fun of Grams?
What?
You wanna fight or something?
Knock it off, you two!
That hurt. What was that for?
Now you've done it!
What do you think you're doing?
That nail...
Could you remove it for me?
Pretty please?
I'd like to be with Niina.
I don't want any more fighting!
Why would you smash it further in?!
tichi taachi miichi no majimun to
1, 2, 3!  With demons
yuuchi ichichi no sanshimai
4, 5! And three sisters
muuchi nanaachi niji no hashi
6, 7! A rainbow bridge
sora kara shichisei futte kuru
drops from the Big Dipper in the sky.
tokidoki samishiku naru to
Sometimes when I feel lonely,
osora wo miageru no
I look up to the sky.
agijabi yo!
"Amazing!"
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
nan kuruu nai sa
Someday your day will come.
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
yasashii ano ko no egao ga ukande kuru
Envisioning that sweet smile of hers.
(hai hai hai!)
(Yeah yeah yeah!)
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
haato ga tokun
My heart is beating...
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
hibiku yo
...really fast!
kokoro de tsunagaru yuimaaru waarudo
It's a supporting world where hearts connect together.
Please tune
in again
next time!
Please tune
in again
next time!
Please tune
in again
next time!
Illustration: Poyoyon♡Rock
Please tune in again next time!