Oh, hello!
Raana-san!
The flowers I planted here have finally bloomed!
How beautiful!
To think Raana would appear as well...
Hello
Nanafa
Wood spirits are lazy beings!
If you're going to live here,
I'll have you work for us as well.
I'll pass on that.
All right! I'm up for it!
Didn't ya hear what Grams said?!
Slacking off and lazing around is what we wood spirits do.
That's... no different from being a NEET.
Raana-chan, could you please wash the bean sprouts?
Leave it to me!
You should be thankful that we're even lazing around here.
Since we grant blessings.
"Blessings"?
For example, Raana grants the blessing of "a great harvest."
Whenever she touches any kind of food, it grows endlessly.
What in the world?!
I see. This is what ya meant.
Hey, do you grant some kind of blessing too, Niina?
Well...
"Well"?
What was it again?
What's with that?
It's huge!
Hey, who's there?
My name is Iina.
I'm the lion that protects this house!
I won't let the likes of you do as you please!
What's a banana peel doing in a place like this?
tichi taachi miichi no majimun to
1, 2, 3!  With demons
yuuchi ichichi no sanshimai
4, 5! And three sisters
muuchi nanaachi niji no hashi
6, 7! A rainbow bridge
sora kara shichisei futte kuru
drops from the Big Dipper in the sky.
tokidoki samishiku naru to
Sometimes when I feel lonely,
osora wo miageru no
I look up to the sky.
agijabi yo!
"Amazing!"
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
nan kuruu nai sa
Someday your day will come.
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
yasashii ano ko no egao ga ukande kuru
Envisioning that sweet smile of hers.
(hai hai hai!)
(Yeah yeah yeah!)
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
haato ga tokun
My heart is beating...
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
hibiku yo
...really fast!
kokoro de tsunagaru yuimaaru waarudo
It's a supporting world where hearts connect together.
Please tune
in again
next time!
Please tune
in again
next time!
Please tune
in again
next time!
Illustration: Poyoyon♡Rock
Please tune in again next time!