Come on, stop blabbering.
Why on earth do I have to go to an elementary school just for this?
Great Sports Festival
Hello
Nanafa
Heating up! A tug-of-war!
Niina, are you okay?
There's no love or place for us.
Hey, Sis, listen!
I'm participating in the footrace, creative dance, and tug-of-war.
So don't forget to cheer me on!
Tug-of-war, huh?
Do your best, Kokona.
I will!
Are you Kokona-chan's mama?
She's so young.
Oh, so that's what makes her so cool.
Uh, I-I'm not her mo—
It's fine, it's fine.
We still have a delicious lunch box.
Just let it be for now, okay, Mama?
Quit that. It's embarrassing...
Go get them, Kokona!
Mer
Wood Spirit...
ci
less
Evil
Demon
Tornado!
Merciless Evil Demon
The Majestic Wrath of the
Resting Big Dipper Stream
What a dreadful thing to do to little kids...
Hold it right there, Niina!
I'm not just going to sit here
and let you do as you please!
The Chain of
Guardian Lion...
Evil Death Threats
Crash!
Don't shoot!
The Chain of Evil Death Threats
Scarlet Silk of Suffering
Stop it, you two!
Now that the nuisance has been taken care of,
let's have a one-on-one battle!
I accept your challenge.
Advanced...
Fruitful Attack!
Fruitful
Attack
Eat this!
And this!
And that!
Why me?!
Cut the crap already.
tichi taachi miichi no majimun to
1, 2, 3!  With demons
yuuchi ichichi no sanshimai
4, 5! And three sisters
muuchi nanaachi niji no hashi
6, 7! A rainbow bridge
sora kara shichisei futte kuru
drops from the Big Dipper in the sky.
tokidoki samishiku naru to
Sometimes when I feel lonely,
osora wo miageru no
I look up to the sky.
agijabi yo!
"Amazing!"
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
nan kuruu nai sa
Someday your day will come.
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
yasashii ano ko no egao ga ukande kuru
Envisioning that sweet smile of hers.
(hai hai hai!)
(Yeah yeah yeah!)
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
haato ga tokun
My heart is beating...
haitai (haitai!)
Hello! (Hello!)
hibiku yo
...really fast!
kokoro de tsunagaru yuimaaru waarudo
It's a supporting world where hearts connect together.