Don't go too far ahead!
Onii-chan, wait up!
Okikura Kakeru
Fukami Touko
Shirosaki Hiro
Imi Yukinari
Takayama Yanagi
Nagamiya Sachi
Episode 1
Fireworks
mune no naka de zawameiteru nami no hontou no imi wo
I pondered over the sound of waves astir in my heart
hizashi ni saegirarete watashi wa mada shiranai
though the rays of the sun blinded me from the truth.
ano koro egaita enikki mitai
Just like the pictures I drew in my diary as a child,
subete ga irozuki hajimeru hora
everything around us is being immersed in color.
manatsu no sora to umi no aosa ni
I try to close my eyes and hide
mabushikute me wo tojite mo
from the brilliant blue sea and sky,
watashi no kokoro no hashikko wo
but your voice always finds its way
tsukande hanasanai kimi no koe wa
right into the corners of my heart and holds on tight.
kore ga koi kana
I guess I'm in love.
You got it!
Nice going!
I give everything my best shot.
Oh? What's this?
Huh? Lemme see!
Oh, these things are pretty advanced now.
The ones I had as a kid weren't nearly as...
I finally found you.
What's up?
Nothing.
You think I can bring this back as Sacchan's gift?
Might be pushing it a little.
Just a little.
Not to mention, I was the one who—
One of these, please!
Whoa, you're gonna drop them.
Dude, you think I'm that uncoordinated?
Well, whatever. You break 'em, you're buying more.
What, even after I went to all
that trouble to split the cost exactly?
Y'know, I came here every day when
I had my high school entrance exams.
Huh? Isn't this kinda far
from your house, Yuki-kun?
Like distance matters. This guy only looks alive when he's out running anyway.
What do you mean, "only"?
This is our last chance
to hang out here together, huh?
Why are you being so negative?
We can always come back.
Yeah, next year, and the year after that...
We'll be friends forever!
"Forever"?
You can't be so sure about the future.
What, so we're gonna stop
being friends after graduation?
No way!
Well, no. I just meant that we
don't know what could happen.
They say wishes only come true when you make them come true yourself.
So instead of saying "this is our last chance", why don't we say "until next time"?
By "they", you mean Sachi, right?
Well, yeah. So?
All right, then!
I hope that I'll be able to handle
whatever the future has in store for me!
Thank you for waiting.
Not at all.
Two iced coffees.
Thank you, dear.
Yukki, gimme a hand over here.
Sure.
When did he become "Yukki"?
He's really made an impression!
Here's your side of toast.
He's just focused on the bottom line.
Gramps is only ever nice around Yukinari.
Makes me wonder which of you is the real grandson here.
Yuki-kun's really popular, I guess.
He's just good with seniors.
What're you talking about?
Something about Grandpa?
Eating out makes everything
taste so much better!
And I told myself I wasn't
gonna drink any ramune, too.
I feel for you. Watching your weight must be tough.
Don't call it that.
Here. Take a look at this.
Wow, it's all sparkly.
The fireworks sure were amazing, huh?
They were like, whoosh! Bang!
Man, the festival's almost over.
Hinode
Bridge
I'm back!
Welcome back.
Welcome home.
Thanks!
What would you like for dinner?
Stew!
Not in this heat.
Hm, what should it be?
You're always like this, Mom.
Why'd you bother asking?
I'm off!
Hold on, Hina! What would you like for dinner?
There's some cabbage left over.
Oh, that's my Hina!
Look! All three of us have matching bells!
Oh, sorry. I didn't bring mine.
Wow, how thoughtful of you.
Shush!
It's hanging on your door, right?
If you saw it there,
why didn't you bring it for me?
Because you always go off
at me when I touch your things.
Wait, who said you could go in my room?
I seem to recall someone asking me to bring her textbook to her.
Exile and the Kingdom
The Descent
Camus
Exile and the Kingdom
The Descent
Camus
Exile and the Kingdom
The Descent
Camus
Exile and the Kingdom
The Descent
Camus
Exile and the Kingdom
The Descent
Camus
Exile and the Kingdom
The Descent
Camus
Exile and the Kingdom
The Descent
Camus
Exile and the Kingdom
The Descent
Camus
Exile and the Kingdom
The Descent
Camus
Exile and the Kingdom
The Descent
Camus
Exile and the Kingdom
The Descent
Camus
Exile and the Kingdom
The Descent
Camus
Exile and the Kingdom
The Descent
Camus
Exile and the Kingdom
The Descent
Camus
Exile and the Kingdom
The Descent
Camus
Exile and the Kingdom
The Descent
Camus
Exile and the Kingdom
The Descent
Camus
Exile and the Kingdom
The Descent
Camus
Exile and the Kingdom
The Descent
Camus
So it was you.
David!
"David"?
Hey, you forgot this.
I thought you'd already left without it.
Thank you.
Switching schools is such a pain.
Which year are you in?
Third year.
Oh, so am I.
It must be tough, changing schools in your third year.
And you are?
What's your name?
Fukami Touko.
Touko.
Just "Touko"?
I saw you at the fireworks display the other day.
You were buying a bell.
Stay still, Jonathan.
Jonathan?
That's the chicken's name.
The others are called Husserl, Confucius, Roger, and Marx.
Technically they belong to the school, but our ethics teacher's the one who really takes care of them.
Jonathan's from someone else, though.
So that's why they're ignoring him, huh?
They have free roam of the school,
so it's hard to sketch them.
Why don't you put them in a coop, then?
I'd feel bad locking them up
just so I could draw them.
How come Jonathan isn't running away from you? That's so cool!
You'd feel bad?
Isn't it better to let them
roam wherever they want?
That's just your own point of view.
Really? I mean...
No animal would actually
choose to be caged, right?
They can't make that kind
of choice in the first place.
Huh?
This is a port town, so there are lots of cats around.
There's a good chance they'll end up as some cat's dinner.
The cats are all full on fish! It'll be fine!
I hope...
Besides, I haven't heard of
any cats attacking them before!
What about things other than cats?
Jonathan will fly awa—
Run away!
What's your problem?!
"Fly away", you said?
What do you make of me? Friend or foe?
Fine! I'll protect him!
Please think about it!
I can't just...
Please!
Hey!
How did I get dragged into this?
Over here!
I'll fill you in on the details later.
Did Yana-chan give the okay?
Yeah, she's fine with it.
She's not that mean.
Thank you so much, Momo-san!
Sure. No problem.
Heya.
She just got her license, so she's been itching to give someone a ride.
Tee-hee.
Man, what'd I do to deserve—
Hey! Why is there a bird in my room?!
Didn't you get my text?
We can't leave them outside. Too dangerous.
Then put both birds in your room!
And didn't I tell you that I can't use my phone during lessons?
Cut the poor things some slack.
They're in an unfamiliar environment.
And for your information, these aren't just "birds". They're chickens.
This was Touko's idea, wasn't it?
I bet you'd just roll over and
give her anything she wanted.
N-Not exactly.
I haven't had ramune in so long!
Open it for me.
Open it yourself.
Do what Touko's doing.
Just do it!
I've... always wanted to keep chickens.
Yuki.
If Touko told you to go kill yourself,
would you?
Touko wouldn't say that.
I know that much.
Oh, I know! Let's have hot pot tonight!
Hot pot in summer is the best!
Jonathan, are you happy right now?
What do you want to do?
Am I keeping you safe?
Onee-chan, dinner!
C-Coming!
Why are we having chicken hot pot in the middle of summer?
What happened to it being too hot?
I just had an urge to, y'know?
It looks delicious.
Touko, come and sit down.
Thanks for the food!
Onee-chan, why'd you bring a chicken home?
Well...
I brought him here on the spur of the moment,
but now I'm not so sure about it.
I got everyone else involved, too.
And it didn't really resolve anything, either.
I mean, what's the difference between keeping them in a coop and keeping them in a room?
I wonder how Jonathan feels about all this.
Come to think of it, I just assumed
I knew what was best for him.
We managed to get ourselves some quality chicken tonight.
What?
Talking about chickens makes me
remember my first date with your father.
Huh? What happened?
He was late for our first date, you see.
Say what? I seem to remember you
being the one who was late.
By over two hours, to boot.
Huh? I asked you if you'd been waiting long, and you said, "I just got here."
W-Well, that was...
So how does the chicken come into this?
Well, you see, I was copying a Jakuchuu chicken painting and lost track of time.
Why were you drawing a chicken before your first date, of all things?
That should've been
the last thing on your mind!
Oh, Hina, you're so sweet.
Does this mean that you care more about chickens than you do about Dad?
Oh my.
We should go somewhere
that Sachi's okay with next time.
Yeah!
We went hiking last year, after all.
What do you say?
Okay.
We can't let the festival end here!
You're still saying that?
One soda water.
We won't have enough time today, so how about tomorrow?
As eager as ever, huh?
The next time you ask me to keep your chickens, you're getting a big fat "no", okay?
N-O. Got it?
I can't believe you did that!
Sorry.
Hey, they were cute at least, right?
If we hadn't stepped in, they might've been attacked by a ferocious raccoon dog!
Oh? How many raccoon dogs
do you think are around here?
I... don't know.
Anyway, this is all your fault for putting one in my room.
You didn't even know what they were called until I told you.
What? Of course I did!
You sure about that?
Welcome!
Chickens really do crow at dawn, don't they?
They didn't lay any eggs.
Do you think animals in zoos are happy?
Anyway,
what made you suddenly want to do something like that?
Um, there's this transfer student, you see.
He's in our grade, and he's kinda like David.
You talking about me?
That gave me a start!
I'll introduce him to you guys!
His name is um...
Okikura.
Okikura... David?
I thought I knew what
was right for Jonathan—
Hey.
So who are you?
I figured there would
be boys here too, but...
What?
Touko. I saw the same thing you did that day.
katachi no nai sekai ni iki wo fukikomu
Take a deep breath and shape this world
mata atashi ga umareru
and bring me back to life again.
barabara ni chirakashita
Hearts are fragile like glass
kokoro wa waremono dakara
and shatter into pieces when they're broken.
sotto tsutsunde kimi ni okurou
I gingerly wrapped those of mine and sent them to you.
hitotsu dake erande misete
Let me know which shard you've kept close.
nande mo nai you na hibi no kakera
Memories of our days together calmly pass us by.
wasurarenu mono to tsui ni aru no wa
There's rarely ever a day we wouldn't look back on.
nando mo daitatte itsu no ma ni ka
And before we knew it,
surinukete shimau mono da
all our moments together had long slipped into the past.
toumei na garasu no mukou bon'yari to
The scenery I caught but a glimpse of
sukashite mieta keshiki wa mada
when I peered through the looking glass
atashi mo shiranai kimi mo shiranai sekai kana
was of a world yet unknown to both you and me
kira hikari wo sorashita
that shined ever so brightly out of our reach.
I think I'll ask him out.
Did he do anything weird to you?
Weird?!
Like what?
I don't really get what you mean.
I hereby lift the ban
on relationships!
Episode 2
Bench