Touko. I saw the same thing you did that day.
"The same thing"?
You. Who are you to Touko?
Hold on.
Did you come here to see her?
Yeah.
That all?
How did you know to find her here?
Kazemichi
This is where you guys hang out, isn't it?
Yes...
Kazemichi
I'll be waiting for you at the Kirinkan
Observation Platform tomorrow at eleven.
Huh?
H-Hey!
mune no naka de zawameiteru nami no hontou no imi wo
I pondered over the sound of waves astir in my heart
hizashi ni saegirarete watashi wa mada shiranai
though the rays of the sun blinded me from the truth.
ano koro egaita enikki mitai
Just like the pictures I drew in my diary as a child,
subete ga irozuki hajimeru hora
everything around us is being immersed in color.
manatsu no sora to umi no aosa ni
I try to close my eyes and hide
mabushikute me wo tojite mo
from the brilliant blue sea and sky,
watashi no kokoro no hashikko wo
but your voice always finds its way
tsukande hanasanai kimi no koe wa
right into the corners of my heart and holds on tight.
kore ga koi kana
I guess I'm in love.
Listen. You don't have
to go if you don't want to.
Who put you in charge?
I was surprised at how straightforward he was.
So, what's going on between
you and that David guy?
Um... We met and talked
about chickens at school?
What?
How did you go from that
to meeting up tomorrow?
Well...
I guess he was pretty easy on the eyes, though.
That had nothing to do with it!
If you wanna go, then go.
I'm more into personality than looks, though.
Like I said, that has nothing to do with this!
Is there something you're worried about?
All right. I'll come with you.
Sacchan?!
He didn't say that you had to come alone.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Then how about we all go?
That would be very insensitive.
You don't know a thing
about how girls feel, do you?
What makes you say that?!
Episode 2
Bench
How do girls feel, anyway?
Would you like me to tell you?
I told you to knock before coming in!
I thought you might need me.
Well, you obviously thought wrong.
The kind of guy who understands how girls feel...
is tall, rich, and intelligent.
But actually, he'd know by now that none of what I said is true.
Good luck!
I gotta concentrate.
Have you found your fragments?
I was too careless.
Sorry, I wasn't able to finish your room in time.
I'll get it done this week.
It's okay. I'm quite fond of what I have right now.
You mean sleeping outside in that tent?
As your father, I can't let that go on much longer.
Thanks.
Oh, right.
I'm about to head out now,
so I won't be needing lunch.
Got a date or something?
Yeah.
It's beautiful.
I sorta messed up along the way and had to fix it up a bit.
It doesn't look that way at all.
I'd like you to have it.
Can I really?
It's a thank-you gift for coming with me today.
Thanks.
Is that...
It's the very first piece
that you made for me!
Do these sparkly things have something to do with why you came today?
Hey.
Morning.
Oh, you were at the cafe yesterday.
My name's Nagamiya.
Did you come because you were
worried about Touko, Nagamiya?
What would I have to do to earn your trust?
Stay away from Touko-chan.
That's a tough ask.
What if I were to tell you that I could
sort out one of the things on her mind?
Touko, you can see visions under certain conditions, right?
Sacchan.
I'd like to talk with Okikura-kun.
But...
Sorry.
So you can help her?
Most likely.
I'll be waiting downstairs.
Thanks.
By the way, our group has a no-dating policy.
What?
I really doubt a policy
like that would last very long.
Touko, how do you feel
about that ability of yours?
My ability?
It wouldn't be wrong to call it your power.
I'm talking about those
visions that you have.
Um...
Would you like to go outside?
It's so hot.
There are a couple of things I should apologize for, too.
Huh?
Oh yeah, why'd you just tell me to come out here?
What would you have done if I didn't show up?
I'd have figured out some other way to see you.
I wasn't concentrating very well today,
so I heard your voice again.
Sorry.
Um, I don't quite follow.
I ended up eavesdropping on
something you'll say in the future.
Something I'll say in the future?
Yes.
You want to apologize...
because you heard me singing alone in the bath,
or did you overhear me mumbling about my test results?
No, nothing like that.
Oh, thank goodness.
Are they that bad?
Huh?
Your test scores.
A gentleman wouldn't ask, you know!
So you believe me?
If you tell me you're joking
right now, I'll forget it happened.
You know, like the three-second rule.
I wasn't joking.
The other day, at the festival, was the first time
I saw an image alongside the vocal fragments I hear.
"Fragments"?
I've finally found you.
That was the first time I'd heard a voice.
I call the voices I hear from the future "fragments of the future".
Fragments of the future?
It's no different to the visions that you've had.
You're telling me that I can see the future?
Most likely.
But how?
There's something that acts as a trigger for your visions, isn't there?
Right.
That should make the fragments easier to see.
It works with glass?
Yup.
Anything that sparkles, but glass in particular.
That will do, then.
Focus your mind on the glass.
I want to see the future too.
Was that me?
That confirms it.
When I'm with you,
I can see those visions too.
I've never been able to see them this clearly before.
I could hear voices, too.
But what makes you so sure
that they're visions of the future?
They all came true for me.
When we're together, I can see images alongside the voices.
So what are you gonna do now?
Take this for now. It's my number.
Wait, this is your home phone!
I don't think he's shady,
but I can't bring myself to like him.
Did he do anything weird to you?
Of course not!
That's good to hear.
I can't imagine what I'd do to anyone who would try to hurt you, Touko-chan.
These could be our last moments together.
I've gotta tell her!
Confession
It's what a man would do!
Oh?
Confession
Who's a man?
Okay, screw the knocking, but would it kill you to show a little tact?
Oh yeah, I saw her the other day.
That girl you're into.
Don't say that!
She was at the hospital. Is she unwell?
She has to go for regular checkups.
Oh, a fragile, unfortunate little girl?
Sounds like just your type.
Don't go slapping labels on her!
Hey. We met yesterday, didn't we?
Hi.
I'm Imi Yukinari.
I'm Okikura Kakeru.
Back already?!
Hey, did you pace yourself properly?
Here. Drink up.
Don't ignore me!
You're only just starting to get better again.
You've gotta pace yourself.
Oh, and Hiro sent us all a text
a little while ago, so take a look at it.
What's with you?
I ran into David.
Davi—
Oh, the guy from yesterday?
And?
I won't lose to him.
What? I didn't catch what you said.
Hello?
Touko, it's me.
Yes? What's up, Yana-chan?
I just wanted your advice on something.
Sure.
Well, I'm thinking of asking him out.
Oh? Right!
You know who I'm talking about, right?
Um...
Right?
Yuki-kun?
So you knew about him.
I've always thought that the two of you are so cute together!
But I think he already likes someone.
That someone's gotta be you, Yana-chan!
You should get ready for him to ask you!
What do you mean, "get ready"? How?
W-Well...
Besides, I don't even know whether he likes me.
No, I'm sure he does!
If it doesn't work out, I...
can't be with you guys anymore.
That won't happen!
I'm not so sure.
I'm telling you, it'll be fine!
Just put some thought into it, okay?
You're amazing, Yana-chan!
I'll be right behind you!
All right. Thanks, Touko.
Hey. You can get in the bath now.
Bath?
No way. They wouldn't get in together, would they?
But how does one get ready to be asked out?
Onee-chan, dinner!
Coming!
Get ready...
Thanks for the food!
Oh, fried chicken tonight?
I had a sudden craving, y'see.
The refrigerator is stuffed with all that chicken you bought.
Onee-chan, you went to the Kirinkan, right?
How was it?
Hmm... I wish there was an air conditioner on the balcony!
What?
Speaking of which, that's a very
special place for us, isn't it, Mari?
Yup.
It would have been about twenty years ago.
Mari was copying a piece of artwork on display that was so breathtaking
that she ended up fainting. That's where yours truly swooped in for the rescue.
I don't get it.
She woke up in my arms and exclaimed, "You ran all the way up here for me?"
To which I replied, "Solely for the
reason of carrying you back down."
Wow, this is a little embarrassing.
Mom, did that really happen?
No clue. Don't remember.
What?!
Hey, Hina-chan,
if—just if—you could see the future, what would you do?
That was random.
Hm...
I'd make a killing at the boat races!
What?
Most people would wanna find out where they'd end up, or who they'd marry, or whatever.
Yeah, but that'd be so boring!
Well, at least wait until
you're old enough to gamble.
She says she can't make it today.
Her lessons are running a little behind schedule.
How did it go yesterday, Sacchan?
It didn't seem like there was anything going on
between them compared to the other day.
I think they just talked.
What do you mean, "I think"?
I gave them some privacy.
You left the two of them alone?!
Sorry I took so long!
Huh? What happened?
Anyways, like I mentioned in my text,
we're going hiking tomorrow!
Firstly, let's set a time to meet up.
But before we get into that,
I'd like to make an announcement!
Please do.
I hereby lift the ban on relationships!
Wait, what? We weren't allowed to date before?
Yup! But from now on—
Hold on a sec!
Actually, on second thought...
Yuki-kun.
All right, I'm ready too!
Welcome!
Oh?
Yanagi-san.
The others went home already.
I see.
I finished earlier than I thought,
so I figured I'd drop by just in case.
I guess I'll take a rest while I'm here.
Get Yukinari to fill you in on tomorrow's plans, all right?
Sure, thanks.
What would you like?
An apple tea, thanks.
Coming right up.
Oh, and I have an announcement from Touko-san.
Hm?
The ban on relationships has been lifted.
Sorry! I just remembered
something I had to do!
Wha—
Okay, see you later, Yuki-kun!
Right.
Touko!
Yes?
Um... Got a minute?
Huh?
It's really hot today, isn't it?
Yeah, it is.
Oh, sorry. So what's up?
Um, well...
Yesterday, you and David...
Yesterday?
Oh, so it ended up happening?
What? What ended up happening?
Oh, uh, just advice, you know?
Advice?
Yeah.
I mean, you're actually pretty shy,
so you're probably not that good at treating girls well, and...
Nah, you're a really nice guy, but if you don't put your feelings into words, no one'll ever know!
I guess not, huh?
Why don't you try telling the people you love how you really feel?
You're right.
I should tell people
how I really feel.
Yup!
I...
Touko, I—
Whoa, hang on, why are you telling me?
Touko!
Yessir!
I... love you, Touko.
I—
I love you, Touko!
Th-Thanks.
U-Um...
Thanks!
Yuki!
What's up with you
and that dumbstruck face?
What are you doing here?
Huh? What are you on about?
I'm on my way home.
Oh.
I see.
Sorry.
You weirdo.
Come on, let's go home.
What do I do? What do I do?
I have to do something.
Oh, I know!
Hello, Okikura residence.
Um, I, er, I'm Fukami,
from the same school as...
Oh. It's me.
Right. Okikura-kun, I...
I want to see the future!
I want to see the future too.
katachi no nai sekai ni iki wo fukikomu
Take a deep breath and shape this world
mata atashi ga umareru
and bring me back to life again.
barabara ni chirakashita
Hearts are fragile like glass
kokoro wa waremono dakara
and shatter into pieces when they're broken.
sotto tsutsunde kimi ni okurou
I gingerly wrapped those of mine and sent them to you.
hitotsu dake erande misete
Let me know which shard you've kept close.
nande mo nai you na hibi no kakera
Memories of our days together calmly pass us by.
wasurarenu mono to tsui ni aru no wa
There's rarely ever a day we wouldn't look back on.
nando mo daitatte itsu no ma ni ka
And before we knew it,
surinukete shimau mono da
all our moments together had long slipped into the past.
toumei na garasu no mukou bon'yari to
The scenery I caught but a glimpse of
sukashite mieta keshiki wa mada
when I peered through the looking glass
atashi mo shiranai kimi mo shiranai sekai kana
was of a world yet unknown to both you and me
kira hikari wo sorashita
that shined ever so brightly out of our reach.
Yana-chan, actually—
It's a sign of our friendship.
Really?
Yes, but I love them.
Everyone, get back!
Episode 3
Plastic Tank