I've never had to move before.
Dad said he wanted to open his own studio away from the city,
so we ended up leaving Tokyo.
I had to change schools, too.
I hope I'll be able to manage in a completely new environment.
Episode 12
Fireworks (Again)
mune no naka de zawameiteru nami no hontou no imi wo
I pondered over the sound of waves astir in my heart
hizashi ni saegirarete watashi wa mada shiranai
though the rays of the sun blinded me from the truth.
ano koro egaita enikki mitai
Just like the pictures I drew in my diary as a child,
subete ga irozuki hajimeru hora
everything around us is being immersed in color.
manatsu no sora to umi no aosa ni
I try to close my eyes and hide
mabushikute me wo tojite mo
from the brilliant blue sea and sky,
watashi no kokoro no hashikko wo
but your voice always finds its way
tsukande hanasanai kimi no koe wa
right into the corners of my heart and holds on tight.
kore ga koi kana
I guess I'm in love.
It's so cold—
Are you all right?
Y-Yes, I'm fine.
Thank you very much.
No problem.
Bye.
Oh, wait!
Hinode Beach Harbor Station
Okay, it's this way.
Wow, it's the harbor!
My name's Fukami Touko.
I'm Okikura Kakeru.
Thank you again for earlier.
The fireworks?
Huh?
You're here for the fireworks, aren't you?
It's not that bad at the moment,
but there'll be a lot more people—
I just moved here.
Eh?
There's a fireworks display today?
Yeah.
Oh, I didn't know.
On the right side of the harbor,
there's a beach and a breakwater.
That's where they'll light the fireworks.
What's taking Kakeru so long?
I bet his tent got buried under the snow or something.
What, he's still living in that tent in his backyard?
It's been snowing a lot lately.
I don't think he is.
All right, if you say so, Sacchan!
What's that supposed to mean?
Hey.
Here's your hot orange juice.
I'm Fukami Touko. Pleased to meet you.
Guys, introduce yourselves too.
Oh yeah, sorry.
I'm Shirosaki Hiro.
My name's Takayama Yanagi.
I'm, uh, Imi Yukinari.
What's this? You fall for Fukami-san or something?
Well, Yukinari falls for just about anyone.
Hey...
In any case, I'm going to show her around Hinode Beach.
Oh, ain't that a shame, Yuki?
I'm Nagamiya Sachi. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too!
My dad decided to set up
his workshop around here, so...
Workshop?
Yup!
He's an artisan who makes handicrafts and vases and stuff out of glass.
Wow, that's pretty cool.
It's less fun than it sounds,
though, because of the heat.
You're going to see the fireworks, right?
The ones they have here are really something!
Um, well...
Huh?
Apparently she didn't know about tonight's fireworks display.
Really?
Each year, the five of us meet up at Hinode Beach Shrine to watch the fireworks.
It's been a long run.
Ever since grade school, right?
As I recall, at first they told us to always travel in groups of three or more,
and we've been stuck together ever since.
Now we just meet up each year
without anyone even arranging it.
Yup.
You should come too!
It'll be super fun!
Can I really?
Of course!
Right, Yuki?
Yeah.
All right, then.
Thanks!
You're not used to this snow?
Nope.
It didn't fall very often where I grew up.
Try to keep a high center of gravity, and take small steps.
Thanks.
From that balcony on the fourth floor, you can see all of Hinode Beach.
Wanna take a look?
I can't wait for the fireworks.
You don't often hear about
fireworks in the winter, do you?
Nope.
I wonder what they look like amongst all the snow.
I doubt you'd be able to see them anywhere but here.
We're all looking forward to
seeing them with you, Touko.
Just "Touko"?
Touko, will you be transferring in to
Hinode Beach High School as a third-year?
Oh, yeah, I will be.
It must be tough, changing schools in your third year.
I want to major in fine arts, so I guess it's more about practical skills than study for me.
I see.
Are you going to follow in your father's footsteps?
Well, I haven't thought that far ahead yet, but...
I've never been outside this town before, so I wouldn't know,
but how's it feel to be in a new town?
It's really exciting.
I'd love to explore the town until the fireworks start.
Shall I be your guide?
Huh?
Thanks!
But I think I'd prefer it alone.
I see. Of course.
It's not that big of a town,
and the people here are very kind.
What's this? I heard there was a new girl.
Look, your lack of knocking aside,
when you come into a boy's room,
you should give some kind of advance warning!
Why's that?
"Why?"
Obviously 'cos it's kinda risky if you don't.
So, how was she?
Eh, pretty average, I guess.
No match for the fragile glasses-girl, huh?
If that's all you're here for, then kindly leave, Sis!
Yeah, yeah.
Tee-hee!
Hey!
Shiomi Ryouza
Don't overdo it just because you're feeling fine.
I know.
If I hurt myself, it'd defeat the purpose.
Hurry up. I'm freezing out here.
Twelve seconds left.
Yes, yes, "It's important to
keep a daily routine," right?
That girl from earlier...
Fukami-san?
Yeah?
She was cute, wasn't she?
Man, it's cold.
Jeez, where is he?
I thought he said he'd be taking the short route.
I'm back.
Oh, welcome home.
Same as every year with your friends at the fireworks, I assume?
Yeah, that's the plan.
You guys?
Same as every year for us too, on the rooftop.
Oh, and we'll be inviting Fukami-san's family too.
Fukami-san?
They told us that they have two girls in middle and high school.
Oh, didn't I tell you?
They'll be running a glass workshop around here.
Isn't this wonderful?
It turns out that they're fans of my music, too.
I'll be meeting up with the older girl later at Hinode Beach Shrine.
Eh?!
Things turned out that way.
Amongst all those people?
It's her first time here in Hinode Beach, isn't it?
What if you can't find each other?
Oh, yeah.
Maybe I should go and pick her up.
Oh, looks like they're here already.
She sent me a text saying that she wanted to look around town before coming home.
I see.
Would you like Touko's phone number?
Yes, please.
Wow, Onee-chan's been busy.
Yes, she has. And do you know who's just like her?
She's come down with a fever.
But please do come inside.
Pardon the intrusion.
Sacchan, how are you feeling?
Well? Think you can make it?
Sorry.
This isn't good.
I don't have my phone on me either.
Wow...
My, how beautiful.
All right, I'll be at the neighborhood association.
All right.
Don't stay out too late, okay?
Of course.
Sorry, and thank you for looking after Sachi.
Not at all! She's safe with me!
Yuki, you idiot.
It's already started.
Um, excuse me—
Hey, don't go off by yourself.
What? You're the one being slow.
Huh?
Excuse me!
Yes?
Huh?
Can we help you?
Um, I...
What's wrong? Do you need something?
Huh? You don't remember me?
But we met just a little while ago!
Are they faking it?
Is this a prank?
Wait, really?
You really don't remember me?
Oh, no, it's nothing. Thanks.
You sure?
Yes, I'm fine.
That was weird.
Yeah.
Hina, you wanted to go with Kakeru-kun too, didn't you?
Nope.
I don't like crowds of people.
Is that so?
I wonder how Onee-chan's doing.
Tamaya!
Oh, Hina-chan, it seems you're familiar with those traditional expressions.
Wow, they're amazing this year too!
Sorry about that.
Oh, it's okay.
I finally found you.
Hurry up!
Wait for me!
I thought I never would.
U-Um, you can see me?
Oh, never mind.
I couldn't reach your cell either, so I was getting worried.
Huh?
Oh, it's out of battery.
The others aren't here yet?
They're over there—
But it's kind of weird.
Almost as if they can't see me.
The fireworks have started already.
It's a little hard for me right now.
Wanna watch from here, then?
The others will be waiting
for us at the shrine, won't they?
Can't hurt to change it up.
I guess we won't be going to the shrine this year.
Yeah, sorry.
It's okay.
This year can be a special exception.
It's one of those, uh...
"Special moments."
Yup, that!
It can be a special moment.
It's beautiful.
Sachi, gimme a look too.
I'm next in line!
Dude, you're so obvious.
Huh? What is?
Okay, fine, you can go next.
I don't think that'll count as an indirect kiss, though.
Wh-What do you mean, indirect...
Here you go.
Is this the world I've been seeing in my fragments of the future?
Seems that way.
So, are you the Kakeru-kun that I imagine?
Yes, but I'm different from the
Kakeru from just a minute ago.
If anything, I'm like a projection of the "me" in your real world.
So you're just a Kakeru-kun from my imaginary world?
Yes, that's correct.
What about the guys over there, then?
They're also not real, but not in the same way.
"Not real?"
It appears that something happened.
They didn't meet up here after all.
Eh?
Are you real?
Yes, I am.
And the loneliness I felt earlier...
Right now, during this fireworks display,
the Yana-chan, Sacchan, Yuki-kun,
and Hiro-kun from this world can't see me.
That must mean that I don't yet have an
unforgettable place I share with everyone.
Isn't that right,
Kakeru-kun?
It's... It's nothing.
katachi no nai sekai ni iki wo fukikomu
Take a deep breath and shape this world
mata atashi ga umareru
and bring me back to life again.
barabara ni chirakashita
Hearts are fragile like glass
kokoro wa waremono dakara
and shatter into pieces when they're broken.
sotto tsutsunde kimi ni okurou
I gingerly wrapped those of mine and sent them to you.
hitotsu dake erande misete
Let me know which shard you've kept close.
nande mo nai you na hibi no kakera
Memories of our days together calmly pass us by.
wasurarenu mono to tsui ni aru no wa
There's rarely ever a day we wouldn't look back on.
nando mo daitatte itsu no ma ni ka
And before we knew it,
surinukete shimau mono da
all our moments together had long slipped into the past.
toumei na garasu no mukou bon'yari to
The scenery I caught but a glimpse of
sukashite mieta keshiki wa mada
when I peered through the looking glass
atashi mo shiranai kimi mo shiranai sekai kana
was of a world yet unknown to both you and me
kira hikari wo sorashita
that shined ever so brightly out of our reach.
I think "Touko" is a beautiful name.
You can tell me later.
I'm calling in your promise.
Have you changed?
It's all my fault.
Final Episode
Shooting Star
Don't go.