Hello, Okikura residence.
Um, I, er, I'm Fukami,
from the same school as...
Oh. It's me.
Right. Okikura-kun, I...
I want to see the future!
I want to see the future too.
mune no naka de zawameiteru nami no hontou no imi wo
I pondered over the sound of waves astir in my heart
hizashi ni saegirarete watashi wa mada shiranai
though the rays of the sun blinded me from the truth.
ano koro egaita enikki mitai
Just like the pictures I drew in my diary as a child,
subete ga irozuki hajimeru hora
everything around us is being immersed in color.
manatsu no sora to umi no aosa ni
I try to close my eyes and hide
mabushikute me wo tojite mo
from the brilliant blue sea and sky,
watashi no kokoro no hashikko wo
but your voice always finds its way
tsukande hanasanai kimi no koe wa
right into the corners of my heart and holds on tight.
kore ga koi kana
I guess I'm in love.
Oh, just then...
Episode 3
Plastic Tank
Yeah. It happened just now, didn't it?
Yup, it did.
We should meet up and talk.
I'll come over to your place.
Huh?
If I don't leave now, I'll get home late.
Oh, you don't have to.
We can do this another time.
I'll head over after I finish what I'm doing.
I've got a very important guest—
I mean, I'm going to be working on something, so don't come into the studio, okay?
Oh?
Sure, as long as you can still make it to dinner.
Okay!
You're such a hard worker, Touko.
Yana-chan isn't the one that Yuki-kun loves.
And now Okikura-kun's coming over here.
All right...
Both Yuki-kun and Yana-chan are dear to me.
That's how I feel, and it won't ever change.
But even if my feelings don't change,
there's no guarantee that our
relationships will always be the same.
Yana-chan's crying.
Glassblowing Workshop
For Cups and Single-Flower Vases
I'm going to make Yana-chan cry.
You had another vision?
Yeah.
I see.
So this is why your trigger ended up being glass.
I guess so.
We've got a customer?
Good evening!
Hey! We're in the middle
of a conversation!
Thanks for putting up with my sister.
I'll go make some tea—
It's fine! Okikura-kun was just about to leave.
K-Keep this a secret from Mom and Dad, okay?
We're having pork cutlets for dinner tonight.
See ya!
Sorry to send you home right after you came here to see me.
Don't worry about it.
I was hoping I could see how Yana-chan and Yuki-kun were doing in the future.
Let me guess. Did Imi Yukinari confess to you?
H-How did you know?!
Yana-chan came to me for advice because
she felt that Yuki-kun had his eye on someone.
You were probably the only one who hadn't already realized.
What?
So what were you intending to do after you'd seen their future?
I wanted to think of a way
to keep us from drifting apart.
Well, whether you succeed or not,
I like that you're trying so hard.
I'll be fine from here. Thanks.
Our group is going hiking tomorrow!
Would you like to join us?
Why would I?
Um...
You just moved here a few days ago,
so I thought you might not have many friends yet.
I only go hiking on my own.
Well, bye.
Was I really the only one who didn't know?
That can't be true.
If they arrive right this minute,
we'll still be good for time, but...
Feeling sleepy?
Yeah. Just a bit.
This is crazy, any way you slice it.
Maybe we should just—
I told you, a girl can't live without one!
And why exactly can't you live without your hairdryer on a hiking trip?
How am I supposed to fix my hair otherwise?
You won't have anywhere to plug it in, anyway!
I have a battery-powered one, duh.
Yo.
Morning.
Glad the two of you could make it.
Morning!
All right, let's climb this thing!
Sorry I'm late!
What took you so long, Sis?!
Sorry, sorry.
I made a wrong turn somewhere.
Tee-hee.
Are you really, really sure about this?
Of course! Have some faith in
your older sister, my dear brother.
If you feel at all uncomfortable, call me right away. Got it?
Right! See you at the top!
Everyone, get back!
Y'know, I think I've seen you a
couple of times before, Sacchan.
Oh, you don't mind me
calling you "Sacchan", do you?
No, it's okay.
Anyway, when people around here talk about going to the hospital,
they're all only talking about one hospital, right?
Whoa there.
Oh, that pendant is so cute!
Where'd you get it from?
It was a gift.
Oh, really? Whoever picked it had great taste.
Lemme guess, your boyfriend?
Not quite.
But I love them all the same.
No way! What a lucky guy!
Yeah, so my kid brother is totally clueless when it comes to girls,
and he's all self-conscious about his height and other pointless stuff,
but he's a good kid at heart.
Right.
I really hope you two get along!
Thanks.
Too excited to sleep before the big day, I take it?
Well, Okikura-kun came over yesterday, and—
Okikura-kun? He's that new boy at school, right?
Maybe we should have invited him. He seems like the hiking type.
Actually, I did invite him,
but he said he'd rather hike alone.
A lone wolf, huh?
I'm the opposite. It's no fun unless I'm with you guys.
Anyway, let's press on!
Only half an hour 'til the top!
Hey!
How are you feeling?
Fine, thanks.
I had a fun ride.
"Fun"?
I've never been on one before, but I imagine that's what riding a rollercoaster feels like.
A rollercoaster...
Right, then. I'll come pick you up when you're done.
Sure, thanks.
Take care on your way...
She's as free as the wind, huh?
She's more like a typhoon at home, though.
We're here!
Look at all the mountains!
Oh, and there's the ocean!
We just came up a mountain too, y'know.
Huh? What is it?
This is so refreshing!
Yup.
Hey, look! That mountain still has snow on it!
That's Mt. Hinode, isn't it?
Anything I can do to help?
You could fill this up with water for me.
Got it!
Now, where to find water...
I'll go with you!
You probably shouldn't, Sachi.
Yeah, I agree.
We can't have you lugging
a heavy tank of water back.
I'll go instead.
Oh? I'll come too, then.
You're in charge of the tent, Yukinari!
What? I am?
Let's go, Yana-chan.
Bet you we'll end up searching
far and wide for a river,
then we'll find out there's actually some water right nearby.
Yana-chan, I—
I want to talk to you about something, Touko.
Huh?
Oh, I spy a creek!
Wow, it's pretty!
Are you dating Yuki?
What?!
Geez, what are you doing?
S-Sorry.
Hey, actually—
I put down a blanket, so you can read here.
Good luck, buddy.
Where are you off to?
I'm gonna go look for those two.
Right. They have been gone a while.
Did they get lost looking for water?
There's a tap right over there.
I didn't know he could be this considerate.
Do you like yakisoba?
I like it with lots of red ginger.
Okay.
We should be okay over here.
Yana-chan, you're so daring.
And whose fault is it
that I'm being so daring?
Well?
Sorry.
I guess I could have picked a better time, though.
Yana-chan...
Touko, how did you feel about Yuki after that happened?
To be honest, I was too surprised to feel anything.
Yeah, I guess so.
Being confessed to does tend to throw people off.
I didn't say anything about confessing—
Wait, how did you know?!
I... happened to see it all.
Touko, are you going to start dating him now?
No, I won't.
Yuki-kun's great, but my boyfriend alarm didn't go off at all.
What's that supposed to be?
I didn't know you even had one.
Well, sorry. I don't get to use it often.
So you're not going out, huh?
I guess if you did have a thing for Yuki...
Well, it'd probably be more obvious.
Huh?
I said that I'd support you, you know.
I'm not gonna give up.
No Service
How does one even get lost around here?
The hell are you guys doing?!
Why did you scream?!
Get out of here!
Also, you're on water duty now and forever!
Whenever I catch sight of you reading your books, your beauty is such
that the image of a graceful doll rises unbidden in my mind—
That's lovely.
Is it a poem you wrote?
Nah.
Ok, time for the noodles.
Here you go.
Thanks—
Ow!
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
We need some water.
Here it is.
Where do you need it?
On Hiro-kun.
Over his head?
I'll pour it over your head.
Man, he completely freaked me out!
Thanks for the food!
Man, this is good!
I know, right? Enjoy.
Huh?
A token of our friendship.
You really outdid yourself with this one.
Okay. I guess I'll eat it, then.
You think so? Help yourself, then.
Great!
No, really. This is amazing.
What?!
Stop with the compliments.
You're creepin' me out here.
Friendship.
Are you calling me creepy?
Actually, I was thinking of putting this on our new menu at Kazemichi.
Hey, that's an awesome idea!
If you end up doing that,
I'll be sure to come 'round sometime.
Sure!
All right, good luck.
The image of a graceful doll rises unbidden in my mind,
but then, I realize something.
Sacchan!
How's your hand?
Oh, it's fine. I didn't get burnt or anything.
Here.
As thanks for looking after me all the time.
Um, sure. Thank you too for—
You can read it now, if you'd like.
Sacchan, I...
Um...
I...
Sachi! I love...
the name "Sachi".
I thought I should tell you, Yuki-kun.
I think that there's someone
better for you than me!
Do you already have a guy you like?
No, I don't.
Then we—
We can't!
Why not?
Because you're too good of a friend to me.
I see.
Sorry for all this, again.
Don't worry about it! Hop in.
Thanks.
Oh yeah! On the way here, I saw a wild boar!
What?!
They're pretty ferocious. I don't think even playing dead would save you!
That's something you do for bears, isn't it?
Sorry!
Oh, is it?
I let you guys do all the packing.
It didn't take long, so it's no biggie.
Sis, I'm done!
She's taking you all the way home, right?
Yup.
Then I'll see you next at the cafe?
Touko-chan, thank you so much for today.
All right! We're heading off!
Be careful on your way back, okay, Sis?
Yeah, yeah.
Sacchan, are you feeling all right—
Right, then!
Let's head back down
before we run into any boars!
Fun fact: more accidents occur
on the way down than up, so—
Okay! We get it!
You think we'll make it
down in one piece?
Touko, we're leaving now.
Oh, okay. Thanks.
I'll be at the front this time.
Don't fall behind!
Roger!
Yeah, whatever.
Hinode
Bridge
Sacchan
New Message
Unlock
Touko-chan,
Fire Hydrant
thanks so much for today.
I'll call you soon.
Welcome back.
Evening!
Hina-chan, what would you do if
a best friend's crush confessed to you?
Did that happen to you?
Hey, stop that!
What would you do?
Why do you even need to ask?
Do you like them too, or not?
That's about all there is to it.
That's just what I
expected you to say.
Aw, come on! Stop it!
By the way, did you end up going hiking together with that guy from yesterday?
I did not!
katachi no nai sekai ni iki wo fukikomu
Take a deep breath and shape this world
mata atashi ga umareru
and bring me back to life again.
barabara ni chirakashita
Hearts are fragile like glass
kokoro wa waremono dakara
and shatter into pieces when they're broken.
sotto tsutsunde kimi ni okurou
I gingerly wrapped those of mine and sent them to you.
hitotsu dake erande misete
Let me know which shard you've kept close.
nande mo nai you na hibi no kakera
Memories of our days together calmly pass us by.
wasurarenu mono to tsui ni aru no wa
There's rarely ever a day we wouldn't look back on.
nando mo daitatte itsu no ma ni ka
And before we knew it,
surinukete shimau mono da
all our moments together had long slipped into the past.
toumei na garasu no mukou bon'yari to
The scenery I caught but a glimpse of
sukashite mieta keshiki wa mada
when I peered through the looking glass
atashi mo shiranai kimi mo shiranai sekai kana
was of a world yet unknown to both you and me
kira hikari wo sorashita
that shined ever so brightly out of our reach.
Kakeru's such a weird name.
Yanagi's such a beautiful name.
He's kinda cool, though,
don't you think?
You think so?
Do you like him?
Episode 4
Hill
He's a bit guarded, don't you think?