Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
6th    Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san On Break
I'm home.
Welcome back.
What were you up to yesterday?
Yeah, about that...
I don't remember anything at all.
My memories start with sitting on the train again.
Who was I with? And what was I doing?
Doesn't that scare you?
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
At any rate, my hangover is killing me.
Go buy me some sports drinks and grapefruits.
Why those two?
Oh, here.
They're supposed to be good for curing hangovers.
But it's not even 11 o'clock yet.
I'd rather go in the evening if I have to.
Why's that?
Because that's when dogs are taken out for walkies.
You really like dogs, don't you?
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
Onee-chan gets to do whatever she pleases.
She's always being treated when she goes out.
And she's with a different person every time I see her.
I'm simply taking it as it comes.
I wonder why that is...
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
What? You want me to go shopping with you?
I'll pass.
I'm babysitting my little sisters, and you're just going to the supermarket anyway, right?
And now the doorbell's going off, too.
Coming!
I'm busy, so I'm hanging up.
I came anyway!
They're so cute!
Back home with you!
I wanted to take it easy since I finally had a day off from club activities...
Sorry...
But I love it when Aki-chan's spending time with me.
There's kids around, so watch your words.
Huh?
We'll be waiting here for you!
I'll stay too, then.
You can't! You have go shopping too, Onee-chan.
Or Yacchan will get lost in there!
You don't have to be so hard on me, Kiri-chan.
Milk and dog food...
Just buy the things you need.
You know, when we're like this...
We're not.
But I haven't said anything.
Still, we're not.
All I wanted to say is that we're like newlyweds.
And I keep telling you, we're not.
Sorry for the wait.
We bought ice cream!
Onee-chan, Yacchan!
Welcome back!
Why are you here?
Um... Just coincidence.
So they were your dogs, Inugami-san.
No wonder it felt like I'd seen them before.
And these two are Aki's younger sisters.
I can see the resemblance, but they were so cute I didn't notice at first.
Well, I'm sorry for not being cute.
By the way, why didn't you two invite me?
Well, it's your day off.
And I didn't want to bother you by dragging you around.
Hey!
So you're the kind of woman who let's people take advantage of you, Onee-chan.
Where did you learn to say such a thing...
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
Inugami-san.
Y-Yes?
U-Um...
What is it?
Let me take your dogs' leashes!
It's a dream come true!
I'm sure you'll be fine.
But they tend to stray off when something catches their attention, so you better be careful...
Inugami-san?!
I can't believe you're such a two-timer!
I don't get to be together
with them, so it's hard to resist!
But just because we're always together,
it doesn't mean I'm okay with that! Geez!
How did we end up having this conversation?
wan wan wan neko ga suki
Woof, woof, woof, I love cats!
muchuu de nani mo mienai
So much so that they're all I see!
nyan nyan nyan inu ga suki
Meow, meow, meow, I love dogs!
sunao ni I love you
But I'll be honest, I love you!
pi pi pi pitto kita no
Pi-pi-pi-pitter patter goes my heart.
anata ni fukujuu shimasu
You know I'll give in to whatever you say!
sore ga futari no
This is how the destiny of our love
ai no destiny
will unfold between us!
Illustration:
Hara Yuuya