Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
10th     Nekoyama-san At The Pool
Today's the day the pool opens!
Hey, Inugami! No jumping into the pool!
What an idiot...
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
Plunging into the pool like that—
Are you a moron or what?!
That's right. What if you injured someone?
You need to learn to control yourself, Inugami-san.
No idea who you're talking about...
Were you even listening?!
Well, we're wearing swimsuits!
Of course we'd be wearing school swimsuits!
That's right! School swimsuits!
Out of all outfits you can wear on school grounds, swimsuits expose the most!
I'd be a fool to let such a view go to waste.
I'll happily be a fool, then.
Come to think of it, high school swimsuits don't come with name tags.
You're right.
Fine by me. They were pretty embarrassing anyway.
What? But...
I think it'd be really nice
to have them sometimes.
Like, what if Nekoyama-san forgot
to write her name on her name tag?
Spare me the details.
It's such a hassle to undress again, but I guess I have to...
Just let me do the writing...
Or something like that...
You're a perv.
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
Nyan-chan, what are you doing?
I'm watching water striders.
So you just do what you like, too.
What about you, Torikai-san?
I'm only here to watch.
Chlorine isn't good for me.
It kinda makes me think I'm melting.
It makes me think my skin is breaking down.
Then it's my face, and finally, I don't have any other choice but to drown in this pool.
That's scary.
Nyan-chan, you're not going to swim?
No, I'm not.
You see, I'm really bad with water.
Water can be scary.
You can drown in it,
or you get swallowed into it.
Is that what happens to people
who drift off into red-light districts?
That's a good observation, Nyan-chan!
At any rate, Inugami-san would come
right after me as soon as I enter the pool...
Nekoyama-san!
What do you want, Inugami-san?
Don't give me that!
Come and swim with me!
I don't like water,
so that's not going to happen.
What?!
What if I say pretty please
with a cherry on top?
I can't means I can't.
So cold!
Come on, what's up with that?
It's my first request of the year, you know!
That doesn't mean anything!
Actually...
This angle is kind of hot.
No, I really shouldn't be...
Hey, Nekoyama-san.
Are you listening?
Huh, what?
I was saying I really want to see
a completely drenched Nekoyama-sa—
That's not something
I want to hear you say!
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
I wonder if Nekoyama-san got mad...
Wouldn't that be a rather
normal reaction coming from her?
You think so, huh...
I'm getting this feeling that I'm missing out
on something really good right now...
Nekoyama, do you feel ill?
I'm feeling kind of hazy.
Really? What's wrong?
I wouldn't be having
such a hard time if I knew myself.
Whatever, I'm sleepy anyway...
I blame the pool.
But you barely did any swimming!
wan wan wan neko ga suki
Woof, woof, woof, I love cats!
muchuu de nani mo mienai
So much so that they're all I see!
nyan nyan nyan inu ga suki
Meow, meow, meow, I love dogs!
sunao ni I love you
But I'll be honest, I love you!
pi pi pi pitto kita no
Pi-pi-pi-pitter patter goes my heart.
anata ni fukujuu shimasu
You know I'll give in to whatever you say!
sore ga futari no
This is how the destiny of our love
ai no destiny
will unfold between us!
Illustration:
Minamoto Hisanari