Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
12th
at the Summer Festival
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
Why aren't you in a yukata?
Go back and change!
Go and change what?
I came here straight from my club, so I didn't
have the time to change into a yukata.
Wait, so this is what
you usually wear?
Yeah, it is...
Huh? What is it?
I think this could work.
I think it's really out of
place at a summer festival.
I mean, it's a chinese dress.
You're making me
feel uncomfortable.
By the way,
who helped you two
put on your yukatas?
Onee-chan helped me put mine on.
What about you, Inugami?
I don't need anyone's help!
To think you'd know
anything about being a girl...
Oh yeah, Onee-chan said
I should learn to do it myself.
"We wouldn't want you unable to put it
back on after slipping out of it, right?"
That statement doesn't
sound quite right to me...
Oh, Nezu-san!
If it isn't Inugami-san and company.
Nezu-san.
Ushiwaka-senpai as well?
Why, good evening.
I wonder if it's because
Nezu-san looks really young,
or because Ushiwaka-san
just looks really motherly...
What's that supposed to mean?
Hm...
Oh, is that Blue Hawaiian
flavored shaved ice?
That's right.
I buy it every time
I come to this festival.
It makes your tongue go blue!
Yes, it does.
Well...
Let's take it off, shall we?
Um, you didn't have to.
Is that so?
What even...
You know, it's probably because we didn't go far,
but there's a ton people from school here.
I even spotted some of our teachers.
I wonder if Torikai-san
and them are here, too.
Oh, I don't know about that.
Knowing her, I bet she's got
heatstroke or something.
You think so?
Sorry about this, Sacchan.
It's fine. I knew what I'd be in for.
Over here!
Look, I got a yo-yo balloon!
What are you, twelve?
Uh, I have no idea how to stop this.
Do you like them?
Well it's not that I like them,
but ever since I was a kid,
I've always been curious
about how they taste.
It doesn't look like there's
much to feast on, though.
Oh, I guess so.
There's nothing to guess about it.
It's starting to get crowded.
It's almost time for the fireworks.
I wonder if there's a
better place to watch them.
Well actually, I know
a nice spot over there.
But not many people know of it, so you never know just what might happen.
What are you thinking
of doing to us there, Senpai?
Hm?
wan wan wan neko ga suki
Woof, woof, woof, I love cats!
muchuu de nani mo mienai
So much so that they're all I see!
nyan nyan nyan inu ga suki
Meow, meow, meow, I love dogs!
sunao ni I love you
But I'll be honest, I love you!
pi pi pi pitto kita no
Pi-pi-pi-pitter patter goes my heart.
anata ni fukujuu shimasu
You know I'll give in to whatever you say!
sore ga futari no
This is how the destiny of our love
ai no destiny
will unfold between us!
Good god...
What am I going
to do with these two?
Illustration: Kuzushiro