Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
11th     Nekoyama-san's Sick Day
Suzu, it's morning. Wake up.
Wake up, please.
Please. Wake. Up.
I'm up, Onee-chan!
Good morning, my little sister.
What are you doing at—
Suzu, your face is flushed!
Are you all right?
You're a little hot...
All I did was nibble
your ear a little.
I doubt that's the reason.
You better stay home today.
I'll make the call for you.
Are there any friends I should...
Actually, just tell me your school's number.
I can make the call myself,
and I do have friends, so—
Inugami-san
&
Nekoyama-san
Inugami-san
&
Nekoyama-san
What's wrong?
Nekoyama's running a fever
and can't come to school today.
Why did I even bother
coming to school today?
Well I'm here to learn.
Guess I have to get through this dull day
at school before I can go visit her...
I'll let you in on something
that'll cheer you up, then.
Nothing can cheer me up at this point...
Let me tell you,
a girl with a cold is thirty
percent cuter than average!
No way! You've got my attention now!
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
My fever's at 39 degrees...
Any higher than this and
I might start seeing things—
Inugami-san?!
I was worried about you,
so I skipped class and came here.
That makes me happy, but you
shouldn't have. You could catch my cold...
It's fine if I do.
They say you get better if you pass your cold
to someone else. Someone like me, for example.
You're acting kinda weird...
I'm acting like always, you know.
You're kind of close, too...
Am I?
But that's fine, isn't it?
I'm more likely to catch
your cold this way. Actually...
maybe I should close our distance to zero.
I took your first!
M-My first—
How can you be so carefree about that?!
And what's with the pandas?!
It was a dream.
I-I can't believe it!
Not even a fever can
excuse that kind of dream...
I'm so embarrassed!
Come on, you're just really tired, that's all.
But I can fix that for you, if you want.
Just what are you—
I-I must still be dreaming!
Nekoyama, you're up?
Aki.
School's over, so we dropped by
to see how you were doing.
So it's this late already, huh...
Also, you kept tossing
and turning... Are you okay?
No, I don't think I'm okay at all.
I think I'll just stay in bed
for the next six months.
What on earth happened?
Really, though, if you stay here—
Don't worry about it!
I totally wouldn't mind catching your cold.
They say you get better if you
pass your cold to someone else, so...
W-Wait—Inugami-san?!
Oh no, it's like the dream all over again!
Here, pass it on!
Don't just go and
hug a sick person!
Inugami-san & Nekoyama-san
All right then, make sure to take it easy.
But we still haven't wiped her body, or helped her eat porridge, or—
Just shut it!
Thank you. And see you!
Actually, how did those two even get in?
So you really do have friends...
Oh, so it was you.
wan wan wan neko ga suki
Woof, woof, woof, I love cats!
muchuu de nani mo mienai
So much so that they're all I see!
nyan nyan nyan inu ga suki
Meow, meow, meow, I love dogs!
sunao ni I love you
But I'll be honest, I love you!
pi pi pi pitto kita no
Pi-pi-pi-pitter patter goes my heart.
anata ni fukujuu shimasu
You know I'll give in to whatever you say!
sore ga futari no
This is how the destiny of our love
ai no destiny
will unfold between us!
Illustration:
Takenashi Eri