No Flirting
We had a certain rule.
No Running
PDAs Prohibited
Student ID
Fujimiya-san.
You dropped this.
Student ID
If looks could kill...
I'm not allowed to talk
to her in the classroom.
Not even to say hello.
I'm sorry about earlier, Hase-kun!
Nah, it's my fault for
starting the conversation.
Only being able to talk to you
on the roof kinda sucks, though.
But then you'll get wrapped up
in all the rumors, too...
I mean...
I'm doing this by choice.
Besides, I'm happy that I've met
someone who I can be normal with.
W-Well, hopefully you'll make even more friends like that.
You're right.
In all honesty, I was happy
to be someone special to her.
I thought following those rules
was just a part of being her friend.
Well, until she arrived.
Found you.
So this is where you've been?
ashita mo kou shite kimi no soba ni ite
Tomorrow, I want to be with you,
onaji toki wo sugoshite itai na
so we can enjoy the same things we did today.
yukkuri peeji wo mekuru you ni mata
So once again, as we slowly flip these pages,
fuyashite yukou kimi to no shirushi
let's fill them with symbols of what we've done.
kotoba ni dekinai koto oshiyosete kitemo
I 'm overcoming that which I can't put into words,
daijoubu kowagaranakute ii yo
but it's okay - don't be afraid, please.
kimi wo tsuresari ni yuku yo
I 'll take you with me,
hateshinai ano sora e to
to this boundless sky we'll never forget.
kanjiru mama ni egakou
So while these feelings remain,
ashita to iu niji no hashi wo
let's draw the rainbow bridge we call tomorrow.
kimi ga otoshita wasuremono
If you ever lose something dear,
boku ga kitto sagashidasu yo
I 'll try my best to find it for you,
nandodemo aitai kara
because seeing that smile on your face
taisetsu na kagayaku egao ni
is worth the world to me.
#5 - a new friend
All right, we'll stop here.
Don't forget your homework.
Hase, come to the office.
Huh?
Why?
Take a wild guess.
We're going to have a nice, long chat
about your grades and your future.
I really want to have lunch,
but it looks like I'll be late!
I'm sorry!
Are you okay?
Hase-kun?
Hello there, Fujimiya-san.
We're in the same class, right?
My name's Yamagishi Saki.
I've followed you here because there's something I want to talk to you about.
There's something...?
You see...
If you don't mind,
would you please be my friend?
Wh-Why?
Because I want to be friends.
Well, honestly I'd rather you
be my older sister, but...
Oh, you as my mom works too.
But I think I'd rather
have you as my sister...
One that's two years
older than me, perhaps?
E-Excuse me?
I've always looked up to you.
Fujimiya-san, you're always so mature.
You can do everything by yourself.
I wish I could be more like you,
but it'd be great if you
would look after me, too.
Are you against the idea of becoming friends?
N-Not exactly...
Oh, good!
Then let's be good friends, Fujimiya-san.
H-Hase-kun!
There's someone who
looks like she fits right in.
Hello.
Um, you're Yamagishi-san, right?
Why are you here?
She asked to be my friend.
Excuse me, but could I get
the names of these two gentlemen?
I'm Hase, and he's Kiryuu.
Wait, hold on.
Aren't we in the same class?
You don't know our names?
Hase-kun and Kiryuu-kun.
So you two are her friends?
Yep.
But technically, I'm her only friend.
Well, starting today, Fujimiya-san
officially has two friends, including me.
But I've got other friends too,
so I won't be able to eat here every day.
Oh yeah, about that.
I can only act like this on the roof,
so I'd prefer that you didn't talk to me in the classroom.
Why not?
It's kind of complicated.
I don't really understand, but I got it.
I'll see you later, Fujimiya-san.
What should I do, Hase-kun?
Let's just wait and see what happens.
We don't know what she's like, anyway.
next day
Morning, Fujimiya-san.
It's me. Did I surprise you?
Y-Yamagishi-san...
You smell nice.
What shampoo do you use?
J-Just a normal one...
Morning, Saki!
Maiko-chan. Ai-chan.
Something happen with her?
We were just chatting. Right?
Huh?
She just chatted her up like it was normal...
Wait up, Fujimiya-san.
We have the same elective class, right?
Let's go together.
Um, Yamagishi-san.
I believe I asked you to not
talk to me in the classroom.
Oh, did you?
Why?
You don't remember?
I mean, it sounds plausible.
Why can't I talk to you in class?
Do you hate me?
That's not...
So I can talk to you, right?
Come on, let's go.
Wait...
She's really assertive.
Hey, Fujimiya-san.
I don't get this part of our math homework.
Can you help me?
Where are you going?
Fujimiya-san...
Huh?
Where'd you go?
You're being way too loud.
There you are.
Wait!
Hold on, Yamagishi-san!
I-Inoue-sensei!
No running in the hallways.
S-Sorry.
You okay?
Yeah.
Yamagishi-san...
She's got her own tempo or something.
She can be a bit pushy, too.
But she's bright and cheerful.
I think it'd be fun to be friends...
Huh? You want to?
But if we become friends, I'll forget about her.
That's why I've avoided talking to people.
Why not break that rule?
I'm really grateful that we became friends.
Finding the courage to talk to you was worth it.
It was scary, and I was nervous in the beginning,
but it definitely worked out for the better.
I'm sure Yamagishi-san's
waiting for you to talk to her.
Thank you, Hase-kun.
Fujimiya-san.
Need something?
Y-Yamagishi-san!
Can I speak with you for a second?
Your memories of friends reset every week?
Yeah. I'm sorry for springing this on you.
It's okay if you don't believe me.
It's not that I don't believe you.
It's just kinda hard to grasp.
What do you mean by "memories of friends"?
What does resetting them mean?
Can you explain?
Let's see...
I basically forget my friends.
You forget them?
Correct. Every Monday.
So you're like me, then.
I'm really forgetful, too.
I forget people's names left and right...
And I forget if I've talked to someone, too.
That isn't really the same...
Nah, it is.
But you know when you're
going to forget things, right?
You're better off than me,
since I don't know when I'll forget things!
You're kind of amazing, Yamagishi-san.
Huh? Amazing?
I've never thought about it that way before.
You're probably just overthinking it.
You've gotta relax a little and enjoy life.
People are willing to help forgetters like us.
Of course, people also say that I always
run away from my problems, but...
I think you're fine the way you are.
Fujimiya-san, you're cute when you laugh, too!
Hey, I'm gonna call you "Kaori-chan" from now on,
so you should call me by my first name, too!
S-Saki-chan?
There you go!
I'm so happy we're using our first names!
I'm just happy that we're friends.
I wonder if Fujimiya-san was able to talk to her...
I'd be more worried about yourself.
She's eating your lunch.
I'm digging in.
No!
Thanks for the food.
N-Not even a crumb left...
Yamagishi-san, you eat too fast...
I'm sorry, Hase-kun.
She said she wanted a taste, so...
It was so good, I gobbled it all up.
Kaori-chan, you're really good at cooking.
Thank you, Saki-chan.
When'd you start using first names?
And we've got a date
tomorrow after school, right?
Y-Yeah.
A d-date...
friday
Kaori-chan.
Thanks for waiting.
No problem... We really should've met at the station, though.
Why?
If people see us together,
they'll start talking about you.
Hey, let's go.
W-Wait, your hand—
It'll be fine.
Oh yeah, I was thinking of going somewhere!
Wanna come along?
You're gonna tail them?
Well, aren't you curious?
It's two girls going on a date!
Okay, but we've gotta see
how well they get along together!
Well, you have fun with that. I'm going home.
Don't leave me!
What if Fujimiya-san finds out,
and treats me like a weirdo?
Trust me, you're already one. Now let me go.
I'll buy you an eggie roll! C'mon!
I've been wanting to try the crepes here.
Me too.
Me three!
Why am I here...
Apparently I came here with Hase-kun before.
But that time, the shop was closed,
so we couldn't eat the crepes.
We won't have that problem today!
Sorry, Hase-kun...
Delish!
It really is.
Hey, give me a bite of yours.
Don't get jealous of a girl.
You can have a bit of mine, Kaori-chan.
What's wrong?
I'm just really happy.
Friends share food a lot, right?
I've seen it happen in manga,
so I've always wanted to experience it.
Delicious!
Yup. Be it food or fun,
friends share everything.
I've wanted to go shopping with friends, too!
Go to a nice store, and check out nice clothes...
Hey, Kaori-chan...
How do I look?
It looks really cute!
You should try one on too.
Ready?
Yeah...
That's so cute!
It's kind of embarrassing, though...
Those aren't clothes.
Those are animal costumes.
Fujimiya-san's rocking hers...
Where to next?
There's so many options...
A short tea break would work...
Karaoke would be fun too!
What else...
There's so many things
I've wanted to do with a friend.
I always thought you were a bit
more quiet and mature, Kaori-chan.
Disappointed?
Nope. I'm really happy I get
to see the different sides of you.
Thank you.
Fujimiya-san seems like she's having fun.
At least, more than she had with me.
Today was a lot of fun.
What are you doing?
I'm writing down everything
that happened today in this dairy.
It's so I can at least leave records behind.
But we had so much fun!
I'm sure that when Monday rolls around,
you won't forget a thing.
That would be nice.
But I don't think I'll recognize you at school.
Really?
Thank you, Saki-chan.
I never imagined that I'd
make friends like everyone else.
Likewise.
I wonder what they're talking about.
Who knows?
Yamagishi-san seems like
a nice and cheery girl.
Yep. She's changed a lot.
We were in the same elementary school class.
Really? Why didn't you say something?
'Cause it's effort.
Besides, she doesn't even remember my name.
Back then, she was really out of it,
always forgetting things.
People would always make fun of her.
She was bullied.
She was crying all the time,
and coming to school was tough for her.
I see...
But you know, things are different now.
I've got friends now, so I'm not alone.
I became friends with you too, Kaori-chan,
so things will be even more fun!
Yep.
Better be heading back.
Yeah.
See you on Monday, okay?
Kaori-chan!
Goodbye!
Fujimiya-san...
monday
There she is.
Good morning!
Good morning.
Excuse me, but who are you?
Wow.
You really did! You really did forget!
It's me. Yamagishi Saki.
Saki-chan?
Yup. We ate crepes, went shopping,
and talked a lot, right?
We shared the crepes...
Yeah, yeah!
Hey, Saki.
Introduce us to her, too!
Sure.
Watch out, though.
She's more forgetful than I am.
Seriously? That's impossible!
You're the queen of forgetting things.
Nobody can top you.
Just the other day, you forgot
to bring your bag to school, right?
You remembered to bring your lunch though!
Did that happen?
Oh yeah, Kaori-chan...
She's really cute when she laughs.
Don't be a sourpuss.
Laugh more!
The rule that bound our conversations
seemed to have disappeared.
And then...
Seems like those two will get along.
Yup.
W-Was that...
She definitely noticed you.
And it's a Monday, too.
It felt like we were making progress.
Slowly but surely.
kaisatsu no mae tsunagu te to te
We're at the gate, holding hands.
itsumo no zawameki atarashii kaze
There's the usual bustle, but yet a new wind blows.
akaruku miokuru hazudatta no ni
I was supposed to see you off with a smile,
umaku waraezu ni kimi wo miteita
but here I stand, watching you and trying to hold back my tears.
kimi ga otona ni natteku sono kisetsu ga
When the time comes for you to grow up from the boy that you once were,
kanashii utatte afurenai you ni
rather than just stand here, singing this sad song,
saigo ni nanika kimi ni tsutaetakute
I want to say one last thing before you go away.
Read the diary
on top of the desk !
"sayonara" ni kawaru kotoba wo
I've been searching for the words to say...
boku wa sagashiteta
The words that mean goodbye.
mothers of friends.
Mothers of Friends.