I'm sorry for calling you out like this.
No problem.
Um...
Do you think I might have done
something to make Hase-kun mad?
I don't understand why he's avoiding me.
I think you should be talking to him instead.
Even if I did, I feel like he wouldn't tell me.
Isn't he just afraid of being with you?
He's been comparing himself to Kujou.
Kujou-kun?
You two were really close
in elementary school, right?
Just like how you
are now with Hase.
Wait, that's—
He probably doesn't think that the same thing would happen again.
That being said, there's no way of knowing
what might reset your memories again.
And for him, seeing you
lose your memories again
would be the worst possible scenario.
I didn't understand
Hase-kun's feelings at all,
and I call myself his friend...
Thank you.
What to do...
Seriously...
#12 - would you please be my friend
Good morning, Hase-kun.
Morning.
Good morning, Kujou-kun.
Yeah, mornin'.
Oh, I need to give Maiko-chan
the notes she wanted.
Morning.
Classics first thing
in the morning sucks, huh?
I guess...
School Cleanup
All right, group reps.
Let's decide where
you'll be cleaning.
You get one shot. No re-dos.
I'm sorry!
It's cold...
I said, I'm sorry!
Well, complaining
won't get us anywhere.
Let's just get it over with.
Sounds good.
Okay.
Since when was I
lumped in with you guys?
Does it really matter?
Besides, we all sit next to each other.
Well, I guess it doesn't.
You two've been acting
strange lately, you know?
Who are we talking about?
You and Fujimiya Kaori.
You think?
I think we're the same as usual...
Did something happen?
Nothing at all.
Need this?
My bag's full, so I'll go throw it away now.
How's Fujimiya been recently?
What do you mean?
Is she any different from usual?
It seems like she's fine,
but it feels like she's forcing it.
I see.
Hase's the same.
What happened?
The two of them used to get along so well.
And to an extent, they still do.
By the way,
why have you been avoiding me?
I-I'm not avoiding...
I'm not that oblivious.
If you've got something against me,
I'll stop talking to you.
It's not that...
If I hated you, I wouldn't be this confused...
When I asked you to be my husband,
you suddenly got really angry.
You're the one who started acting weird first!
It was back then, huh?
And then I didn't want to talk to you
because you might hate me even more...
The last thing I wanted to hear
was that you'd stop talking to me...
Sorry about that.
It's not like you to apologize like that...
If I think I'm at fault, I'll apologize.
It's just that usually, I'm not
the one who needs to apologize.
I see. That makes sense.
Well then, can I continue to
rely on you from now on?
Well, you sure are straight to the point.
That's fine by me, but don't
expect me to pamper you.
Roger!
Seems like Yamagishi-san
is back to normal.
Good for her.
And what about you?
Are you fine with the way things are?
What do you mean?
Everyone knows that something's up between you and Fujimiya.
I mean, it's not like I don't
get what you're thinking...
I think it's fine the way it is.
She's become friends with
Yamagishi-san and the others.
She's become her usual self in class, too.
I think she'll be able to make plenty of friends from here on.
Maybe so.
I'm happy enough,
and I don't want her to be sad.
She's been suffering
for a long time, after all.
So you don't care
about how you feel?
I told you, I'm...
fine with the way things are now.
So winter break's comin' up, right?
Let's all do something together!
Where do you wanna go, Kaori-chan?
Actually, I'm going
on a trip with my family.
Really?
Yup. My dad really likes traveling.
You all go out and have fun, okay?
Oh, same thing here, actually.
My parents want to go on a trip this year.
Your family does that kind of stuff?
"This year for sure," they said.
It was last-minute.
Really?
Oh, well.
That's no fun...
C'mon, now.
Well, what are we doing?
I'm home!
Welcome back.
Are you already prepping
for New Year's dinner?
Yup.
It's been a while since we've celebrated
New Year's at home, so I figured I should start now.
This is the way things should be, right?
Is something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Here, let me help.
You know what day it is—
It's New Year's Eve.
Is everyone ready for the new year?
Shoppers were quick to fill—
Mom, what's for lunch?
Mom?
New Message
Inbox
Mom
None
I'm off to go hear Beethoven's Ninth.
Inbox
Mom
None
I'm off to go hear Beethoven's Ninth.
Inbox
Mom
None
I'm off to go hear Beethoven's Ninth.
Inbox
Mom
None
I'm off to go hear Beethoven's Ninth.
Inbox
Mom
None
I'm off to go hear Beethoven's Ninth.
Oh, right...
This is how New Year's is every year...
Thank you!
Might as well go for a walk...
Wow, it's cold...
Yeah, I'll just go home.
What am I doing?
I know she won't be here...
Hase-kun?
Fujimiya-san?
What are you doing here?
That's my line...
So why are you here?
What about your trip?
The trip?
Oh, that. It was, uh,
canceled at the last minute...
What about yours, Fujimiya-san?
Well, my dad got called in
to do some overtime,
so we just decided to
take it easy and stay at home.
I see.
I never thought we'd actually
meet each other here, though.
You too?
I decided in advance that if I went for a walk today, I'd definitely come through here!
I thought that maybe
I'd see you here...
I'm sorry. Forget what I just said.
O-Oh... right...
It's fine.
Fujimiya-san...
Yes?
Wanna go for a walk?
Yeah.
A year ago, I never would have even
imagined walking with you like this.
Well, we weren't even in the same class then.
May 12th. That's the day
you first talked to me, right?
You were surprised since it was so sudden, weren't you?
I must've been happy when you did.
I'm sure of it.
Fujimiya-san...
But back then, I probably hadn't told you about my memory problems yet.
I get the feeling I was thinking that being your friend
would cause a whole ton of problems for you.
But if you hadn't continued
asking to be my friend,
even now, I'd probably be alone...
Thank you. From the bottom of my heart.
I didn't...
All I wanted was to be your friend...
Exactly. Thank you!
Clearance
Sale
In Progress
Should we head back soon?
Hase-kun!
Y-Yeah?
Want to grab some crepes?
S-Sure.
Fine by me, I guess...
All right!
Thanks for the food.
Man, these crepes are delicious!
Yup!
We always talked about
coming here, but we never did.
There was a lot written
in the diary about these crepes,
so I was kind of curious.
Today's been like a dream.
First I met with you, and then
we grabbed crepes together...
Fujimiya-san...
I've been worrying you a lot lately,
so I was hoping eating crepes
with you like this would cheer you up.
Hase-kun?
Man, that was good!
I'll go get another one!
Thanks for today. It looks like we
really walked a long ways, huh?
It's nothing.
Well, goodbye.
You're free to leave now, Fujimiya-san.
Right, same for you, Hase-kun.
Hase-kun?
I'll walk you part of the way home.
Who knew there was a shrine over here?
In elementary school, I'd stop by here on my way home to pray.
Oh, is that so?
Oh, I know.
It's a bit early, but how about we have our shrine visit now?
Sure.
What's wrong, Fujimiya-san?
Are you all right?
I don't want to forget today at all.
I want to remember every moment
that we shared today.
Even the tiniest of details...
But what'd be worse
is not being your friend.
If we weren't friends,
no matter how many memories I have,
I still wouldn't be happy...
Fujimiya-san...
I want us to talk like we used to!
I want to spend time together,
like we did today!
I want to be your friend!
But... I...
I don't know what I should do...
I can't believe myself!
I didn't want you
to cry anymore, and then...
What the hell am I doing?
I'm such a stupid, ignorant fool!
I'm sorry, Fujimiya-san.
I forgot the most important thing of all.
Hase-kun?
I want to talk to you as much as I can!
I want to be with you whenever I can!
I want to be your friend
for as long as possible!
That smile gives me hope.
Kaori?
Kaori, if you were going somewhere
with Hase-kun, you should have let me know.
What's wrong?
Hello.
You weren't coming back.
Your father almost called the police.
Though if he saw you two now,
I think he'd be calling an ambulance instead.
I'll be going, then!
Hase-kun!
I'm looking forward to next year.
Me too.
There are things
I don't want to forget.
The memories we've all shared.
The memories the
two of us have shared.
Memories are important things.
But even more important
than those memories
is the chance to continue
creating new ones.
So I'll say those words
again and again.
However many times it takes.
Fujimiya-san.
Would you...
...please...
...be my friend?
kimi no te wo hiku sono yakume ga
I used to think that leading you by the hand
boku no shimei da nante sou omotteta
was what I was supposed to do.
dakedo ima wakattanda bokura nara mou
But I know now, for the two of us,
kasaneta hibi ga hora michibite kureru
the days we shared will lead our way.
kimi ga otona ni natteku sono jikan ga
In time, you will change from the boy you once were.
furi tsumoru ma ni boku mo kawatteku
After all, the layers of time will change both you and me.
tatoeba soko ni konna uta ga areba
But if this song reaches you, no matter where you are,
futari wa itsu mo donna toki mo tsunagatte ikeru
it means that we're connected, forever and always.
totsuzen fui ni nari hibiku beru no oto
Then out of nowhere the sound of the bells ringing.
aseru boku hodokeru te furareteku kimi
You let go of my hand in a hurry, and begin to run off.
muchuu de yobi tomete dakishimeta n da
I call out to you, grabbing you and holding you close.
kimi ga doko ni ittatte boku no koe de mamoru yo
No matter where you are, I'll protect you with my song.
kimi ga boku no mae ni arawareta hi kara
Ever since the day you appeared in my eyes,
nani mo ka mo ga chigaku mietanda
everything around me seemed to look different.
asa mo hikaru mo namida mo utau koe mo
From the sunrise, to my tears, to this very song,
kimi ga kagayaki wo kuretanda
you gave them all this irreplacable shine.
osae kirenai omoi wo kono koe ni nosete
These feelings that I can't control, I put into my song,
tooku kimi no machi e todokeyou
and sing them to your town, no matter how far you are.
tatoeba sore ga konna uta dattara
So if this song manages to reach your ears,
bokura wa doko ni ita toshite mo tsunagatte ikeru
it means that we're connected, no matter where you are.
I wonder what she writes about.
Diary