Hey, Hase-kun. I want to go to the beach!
Huh? The beach?
Well... I wouldn't mind going to the beach together, I guess.
That's good to hear!
I've always wanted to go to the beach and hang out with friends.
Yeah, the beach is nice. No complaints here.
Do you think Kiryuu-kun and Saki-chan would come with us if we asked?
Oh, they're invited, too?
Shougo probably couldn't be bothered, and I don't know how to contact Yamagishi-san...
So...
I see...
Just the two of us might be a bit embarrassing, so maybe we should go another time.
All right! Let's go ask them!
Yeah!
Their relationship to this point
kaisatsu no mae tsunagu te to te
We're at the gate, holding hands.
Their relationship to this point
itsumo no zawameki atarashii kaze
There's the usual bustle, but yet a new wind blows.
The wind feels nice today, huh?
It sure does.
What's wrong?
akaruku miokuru hazudatta no ni
I was supposed to see you off with a smile,
A mosquito bit me.
umaku waraezu ni kimi wo miteita
but here I stand, watching you and trying to hold back my tears.
It's been a long journey...
It'll help with the itchiness.
I noticed that lately you've been itching a lot, so I brought it.
Th-Thanks.
Not a problem.
ashita mo kou shite kimi no soba ni ite
Tomorrow, I want to be with you,
onaji toki wo sugoshite itai na
so we can enjoy the same things we did today.
yukkuri peeji wo mekuru you ni mata
So once again, as we slowly flip these pages,
fuyashite yukou kimi to no shirushi
let's fill them with symbols of what we've done.
kotoba ni dekinai koto oshiyosete kiitemo
I 'm overcoming that which I can't put into words,
daijoubu kowagaranakute ii yo
but it's okay - don't be afraid, please.
kimi wo tsuresari ni yuku yo
I 'll take you with me,
hateshinai ano sora e to
to this boundless sky we'll never forget.
kanjiru mama ni egakou
So while these feelings remain,
ashita to iu niji no hashi wo
let's draw the rainbow bridge we call tomorrow.
kimi ga otoshita wasuremono
If you ever lose something dear,
boku ga kitto sagashidasu yo
I 'll try my best to find it for you,
nandodemo aitai kara
because seeing that smile on your face
taisetsu na kagayaku egao ni
is worth the world to me.
#8 - at the sea with friends
So you're on board with going to the beach, right?
Too hot. Too much trouble.
Aw, come on! Fujimiya-san's really looking forward to this.
Please?
First you say you want to be alone with her, and now you don't?
What am I supposed to think?
But when all's said and done, you're the type that loves helping people, right?
If you go too far, I will abandon you.
S-Sorry!
Oh, also, do you have Yamagishi-san's number?
And why are you asking me?
I want to invite her, but I don't know her number or anything.
I figured since you guys went to the same elementary school, you might have her number.
Now that you mention it,
It might be in my elementary school class directory...
Awesome, Shougo! I knew I could count on y—
Going to the beach with Kaori-chan?
Yeah! I'm in!
Well, it'll be tomorrow then, so see ya.
Oh, I have a favor to ask though.
Yeah?
I have a feeling I'll forget,
so can you remind me tomorrow?
Thanks in advance.
I'm always getting led around by the nose, huh?
How did he have my number, anyway?
Well, whatever.
I got so excited, I couldn't really sleep last night.
What are you, a kid before a school trip?
Good morning, Hase-kun!
Fujimiya-san.
I was so excited last night, so I had trouble falling asleep.
Birds of a feather...
Long time no see, Kiryuu-kun.
Thank you both for coming.
We should be thanking you for inviting us.
Now we're just waiting
on Yamagishi-san, right?
Don't tell me she forgot...
I doubt that.
I gave her a call before I left.
Kaori-chan!
I missed you!
S-Saki-chan?
After realizing that I wouldn't get to see you over summer break, I got really lonely!
Spoil me lots to make up for it, okay?
Uh, okay!
Oh, it's the two guys. Long time no see...
Do you still not remember our names, by any chance?
More like she never bothered to begin with.
All right, let's go!
Sure!
Hold on! You forgot your stuff!
Shinjuku
Over here, you two!
We made it...
We almost got on the wrong train.
Why am I so exhausted when all we had to do was board the train?
Come on!
Wait for me!
Since we all got up early, I figured that
some of you might have missed breakfast.
If you want, dig right in.
Yay.
All right! I'm really hungry.
Help yourself.
I think I will!
It's delicious.
Kaori-chan, your cooking really is the best.
Thank you.
Is something wrong?
Hase-kun, you eat your
octopus-weiners' tentacles first, huh?
You're right. He's saving the head for last.
It's in the diary, but you really do start from the bottom....
Y-You've even written that down, huh?
But why from the tentacles?
Biting off the head first seems kinda unsettling.
Fujimiya-san made them, so it'd be a waste to eat them like that.
That makes me really happy.
You know...
Huh?
It's the ocean.
And now that we've come all this way... it's raining.
That's too bad.
No way around it. Let's go home.
Darn. What'd we do to deserve this?
I thought we'd be able to swim, but...
With this kind of weather, that's not possible.
Yeah. It's dangerous to even go in the water.
Whoa. I'm getting blown away...
Especially for her.
Too true.
Let's just play on the sand instead, then.
C'mon, Kaori-chan!
Hold on!
All right, let's make a sand castle.
The sand might be too wet for that...
From here, those two look like children.
But Fujimiya-san's having fun, and that's all that matters.
It definitely feels like we're chaperones here.
Done.
Are you serious?
That's amazing, Saki-chan.
Let's play with this ball next.
Here it comes, Hase-kun!
Wait, hold on! The wind is—
It's getting blown away...
That's what I'm saying!
Here's your ball.
Thanksies.
You're dripping wet, Hase-kun. Are you okay?
It doesn't really matter.
It's summer, after all.
Here's a towel. If you don't dry yourself off, you'll catch a cold.
Th-Thanks.
This is how you give someone a towel.
What's your problem?
I'm just giving you a facelift.
Screw you! Why you...
Keep away!
Get back here!
Let's wait here until the rain stops, I guess.
This is the first time I've been to an arcade!
Seriously?
Is there anything you want to try?
I can show you how to play them.
Uh, let's see...
This looks interesting.
Crane games aren't my forte,
but my reputation's at stake here!
You can do it, Hase-kun!
Fourth time's the charm.
Shoot! It was so close, too!
You were close...
Crane games seem really tough.
Thanksies.
You're amazing, Kiryuu-kun.
It was just a fluke.
I swear...
What next?
How about a shooting game?
A shooter, huh?
Are you good at those, Shougo?
Kaori-chan, you want to take some pictures?
Yeah. I've always wanted to...
All right, let's grab some shots of the four of us!
Is that okay?!
Of course. Right, Shougo?
Nah, I'll pass.
Shougo says he's in!
Please insert coins
Okay, we're taking it. Everyone smile!
Here we go! Three, two, one!
Come on, get over here.
Came out pretty well.
Shougo, you really don't smile, do you?
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
Is something wrong, Fujimiya-san?
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
e all friends,
right!
We're all friends,
Hase-kun's here, Saki-chan's here, and Kiryuu-kun's here, too.
right!
We're all friends,
I'm just thinking how happy I am, getting to spend my summer vacation with you guys.
Fujimiya-san.
I really like this photo.
I'll treasure it forever.
Looks like the rain stopped.
The ocean is so pretty!
Yup. There's no wind, so it feels nice too.
Oh, sorry. That's my stomach growling.
How about we have some lunch on the beach?
Sounds good!
We already ate what I brought for breakfast, so we'll have to buy some food.
Let's decide who's buying it, then!
All right, rock-paper-scissors!
Why?
You only have yourself to blame for picking the game.
All right, we'll be back soon.
Have fun!
Okay, question.
What do you like about Kaori-chan?
Huh? Wh-Where'd that come from?
Her looks? Her personality?
H-Hold on. I don't see her in that sort of light at all.
We're just really good friends, nothing more, nothing less.
Is that so?
I hug her a lot,
so I know she's not lacking
in that department...
Wha—
Sucks that we couldn't go into the water, huh?
Come on, Yamagishi-san! Quit teasing me!
What should we get?
Let's just buy a bunch of different stuff.
Sounds like a plan.
You seem a lot more comfortable with me now.
Hey, Fujimiya.
How do you feel about him?
You mean Hase-kun?
Yeah.
How do I feel... Well, I think he's a very important friend.
Well, sure, but...
Oh, speaking of...
Hm?
The other day, I felt kinda strange,
seeing Hase-kun talk to somebody else.
Do you have any idea why?
Was the other person a girl?
Yeah. How did you know?
How? I mean...
Actually, never mind.
Anything else you wanna grab?
Um...
This, too.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Welcome back.
There were these cool things, so I bought it.
Ta-dah!
Fun
Fire
Works
Fun
Fire
Works
Fun
Fire
Works
When it gets a bit darker, let's light some fireworks!
Awesome!
This shell looks pretty.
There's a big one over here.
I had no idea how today was gonna turn out,
but I'm glad to see she's having fun.
Are you fine with the way things are?
Huh? What do you mean?
You might wanna push a bit more.
Hase-kun! Are you having fun?
Yeah, totally.
Hey, we found a hermit crab!
And it was this big!
I highly doubt that.
I'm serious! It's over here!
Why don't we take a little walk?
A Warning Has Been Issued
Today was so much fun.
We should've come earlier,
if it's this much fun!
I think so too.
I wonder why I never thought to ask.
I think I'll take a small dip.
Come join me, Hase-kun!
The sea's so nice, isn't it?
It would have been nicer if it didn't rain.
I actually like the rain, you know.
I like the ocean and the sunset too.
Fujimiya-san...
It'd be nice to not forget today...
A warm summer.
A warm evening.
The fireworks sparkle as they burn away,
but the heat shows no signs of fading.
Hase-kun.
Can you share a spark?
Oh, sure.
It's beautiful.
We were able to see the ocean, and play on the sand...
I even got to play at an arcade and play with fireworks, too.
This is the most fulfilling
summer vacation I've ever had.
You say that, but this is only a single day...
You're right.
Oh, it stopped...
You know, Hase-kun...
I really like this.
Playing with fireworks.
Y-Yeah, fireworks are really cool.
Lately, I've been wanting to use the word "like."
How do you describe these feelings?
It's so hot...
I wanted to stay in Hokkaido until it cooled down...
We'll unpack tomorrow.
Anyway, come inside.
Here we are again...
Back in Tokyo.
kaisatsu no mae tsunagu te to te
We're at the gate, holding hands.
itsumo no zawameki atarashii kaze
There's the usual bustle, but yet a new wind blows.
akaruku miokuru hazudatta no ni
I was supposed to see you off with a smile,
umaku waraezu ni kimi wo miteita
but here I stand, watching you and trying to hold back my tears.
kimi ga otona ni natteku sono kisetsu ga
When the time comes for you to grow up from the boy that you once were,
kanashii utatte afurenai you ni
rather than just stand here, singing this sad song,
saigo ni nanika kimi ni tsutaetakute
I want to say one last thing before you go away.
Read the diary
on top of the desk !
"sayonara" ni kawaru kotoba wo
I've been searching for the words to say...
boku wa sagashiteta
The words that mean goodbye.
The final day with friends.
the final day with friends.