Wait up!
Um...
If it's all right...
would you...
Would you please be my friend?
I'm...
I'm?
I'm really happy, but sorry!
If she's happy, then why...
It may seem obvious, but back then,
I didn't know anything about Fujimiya-san's secret.
Why she was always alone.
Why she never tried to make friends.
I didn't know anything.
ashita mo kou shite kimi no soba ni ite
Tomorrow, I want to be with you,
onaji toki wo sugoshite itai na
so we can enjoy the same things we did today.
yukkuri peeji wo mekuru you ni mata
So once again, as we slowly flip these pages,
fuyashite yukou kimi to no shirushi
let's fill them with symbols of what we've done.
kotoba ni dekinai koto oshiyosete kitemo
I 'm overcoming that which I can't put into words,
daijoubu kowagaranakute ii yo
but it's okay - don't be afraid, please.
kimi wo tsuresari ni yuku yo
I 'll take you with me,
hateshinai ano sora e to
to this boundless sky we'll never forget.
kanjiru mama ni egakou
So while these feelings remain,
ashita to iu niji no hashi wo
let's draw the rainbow bridge we call tomorrow.
kimi ga otoshita wasuremono
If you ever lose something dear,
boku ga kitto sagashidasu yo
I 'll try my best to find it for you,
nandodemo aitai kara
because seeing that smile on your face
taisetsu na kagayaku egao ni
is worth the world to me.
#1 - becoming friends
I'm back.
What's up with you?
I tried talking to Fujimiya-san.
Good for you. You can die happy now.
You've been going on and on about how you want to talk to her...
She turned me down though.
Huh?
I asked her if she wanted to be friends.
You said it, huh?
and she replied, "I'm really happy, but sorry!"...
What's that supposed to mean, Shougo?
Hell if I know.
You're so cruel!
And you're so annoying...
Well, that'd be her way of politely rejecting you, I guess.
You think? Maybe you're right...
If you're that hung up about it, why not just ask her?
She was heading towards the roof earlier.
Hold on.
The roof's usually locked, isn't it?
Fujimiya-san!
Hase-kun?
So this is where you always go for lunch, huh?
U-Uh...
Wh-Whoa, what a great view!
It's my first time coming up here, so I had no idea!
There's nobody here, so it's nice and quiet, too!
What a find!
Fujimiya-san?
Do you have a cold or something?
You were coughing earlier, too.
tuesday
C'mon, go ask her...
Really?
Hey, Fujimiya-san...
Yes?
You're the math representative, right?
I forgot to turn in my math homework yesterday.
Can you talk to the teacher and turn it in for me?
Sorry.
See? I told you.
She's really cold, isn't she?
What's with her attitude?
The weather's nice today, isn't it?
Or is it just me?
Mind if I eat up here?
My friend ate without me and fell asleep.
Why...
Why what?
We've got P.E. during fifth period, right?
Having it in the afternoon kinda sucks...
Hase-kun.
What's up?
I can't be friends with anyone.
Huh? What do you mean?
Did someone tell you not to?
That's not it...
Are your parents really strict, telling you to focus on school rather than friends?
It's not that someone told me not to.
Then why?
It's just...
It's...
just impossible.
I'm really sorry.
You weren't actually sick yesterday, were you?
Why didn't you keep up the act?
W-Well...
And why did you thank me afterwards?
Fujimiya-san, you must be—
You must be really good at math. That's why—
Do you have a cold? Want me to carry those for you?
Sorry for bothering.
Um...
Hase-kun.
Uh...
Thank you...
for helping out.
B-Bye.
Wait up!
If you'd kept giving me the cold shoulder, I wouldn't have said that.
So why...
I was avoiding talking to you, yes.
But not thanking someone after they help you...
See?
You're a nice person after all.
We don't have to be friends, per se,
but can we eat together tomorrow too?
What do you mean?
All we'd be doing is eating lunch together.
Not as friends.
That much is fine, right?
All right. Tomorrow, on the roof...
Awesome!
But please don't talk to me in class.
Gotcha.
Thank goodness. I don't know what I would've done if you had said no...
wednesday
Math Storage Room
Hase...
You're gonna fail math at this rate.
Year 2  Class 4  Name:    Yuuki Hase
Given two points (-1, 2) and (3, 4), find the midpoint between them.
We're only a month into the class, Sensei...
I know. It's the first time I've had to worry about a student so early on.
Inoue-sensei! What do I have to do to be excused?
I don't want to miss lunch today!
Listen up, Hase.
You and me both.
Excuse me!
Written Promise
I promise to score at least
a 40 on the next test.
Yuuki Hase
What's up with him?
My bad. You're done eating, I imagine?
I'm not.
You're not?
You told me you'd come, so I waited for you...
Fujimiya-san!
Y-Yes?
Let's start eating!
Yeah.
Man, I'm stuffed.
Food tastes best when you're with somebody, huh?
All right, let's play some cards.
Huh? Why?
Cards and lunch break go hand in hand.
Do they?
Usually people play President...
Wait, you can't play that with two people.
There's Old Maid.
I guess that's not as fun, either...
Let's play Memory, then.
The last one's...
here, I think.
Yay!
That's five in a row...
Man, I can't compete with your memory.
That's not true.
So you're really good at math, right?
I wouldn't say I'm really good at it.
I've just liked math since I was a kid.
And on the flip side, I really suck at math...
I really respect you.
I'm often bored at home, so I just end up studying.
If I'm bored, I just end up hanging out with friends.
Um,
Hase-kun, when you hang out with friends, where do you usually go?
Hm... Karaoke, I guess?
Is karaoke fun?
Wait, have you never been to a karaoke place before?
S-Sorry!
Well, then, would you like to sing some karaoke with me?
That's impossible!
S-Sorry...
Well, it was kinda out of the blue...
Anyway, hopefully you'll get a chance.
Yeah.
Sure...
Thanks for the food.
I'm still a little hungry...
thursday
I should've bought some dessert or something.
I don't have any food to share, but speaking of desserts,
apparently there's a new crepe shop near the station!
Crepes, huh? Sounds delicious.
Do you like crepes too, Hase-kun?
Y-Yeah.
I'm a fan of the chocolate and custard ones.
I love strawberries and cream inside my crepes.
Blueberry cheesecake is good too...
There's this one place where my mom and I go a lot,
but there's only one bench there, and it's always taken.
What do you think? This shop seems to have a lot of places to sit...
I-I was just thinking that other people might be interested in this shop.
I wasn't trying to say we should go together or anything...
For what it's worth, I'd be down—
And we're not even friends, so...
We aren't friends, huh...
Uh, well...
What do you consider to be friends, then?
Huh?
Like, what kind of things do friends talk about?
Love!
Love talk?
Love, huh? That's kinda tough, considering I'm not crushing on anyone right now...
As far as people I might be interested in...
Fujimiya-san!
But since we aren't friends,
we don't need to talk about love.
Right.
I'm home!
Welcome back.
I'll wash this later, so I'm leaving it here.
Limited time!!
Strawberry, Chocolate, and
Whipped Cream
Berry Cheesecake
Strawberry Special
Thu
Fri
friday
Thanks for the food!
Man, that was delicious.
You've hardly touched your food.
I'm not feeling that hungry, that's all...
Huh? Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm fine.
We've got bio next, right?
Honestly, I might just sleep through it.
Don't want to fail it, though...
But I should be more worried about math.
You're pretty good at math, right?
Oh yeah, maybe at some point, you think—
Hase-kun.
What is it?
Don't talk to me anymore.
W-Why?
Did I do anything wrong?
Why are you—
I told you, didn't I?
I can't be friends with anyone.
I want you to act like this never happened.
I'll forget everything, too...
That's impossible...
I won't forget that easily...
You won't really forget me, will you?
I will!
On Monday, all the memories of the fun times we shared...
will disappear.
It's not just the fun memories, either.
I forget everything about the people I get close to and want to continue to be with, too.
My family seems to be the only exception.
That's why I can't remember my friends.
What is this...
But that's okay! We aren't friends, are we?
In that case...
I know this, though.
All my memories of you will disappear.
I...
I can't believe this.
saturday
Been a while since we've done something like this.
Fujimiya-san told me not to talk to her again.
She'd forget everything, and she told me to forget everything, too.
I see. Doesn't that mean...
Yeah?
that she totally hates you?
You think so, too?
That'd be the usual conclusion to draw...
She's always by herself, right?
You never know what she's thinking. What about her appeals to you?
Her face.
Boy, you're simple.
Does it matter?
If you're trying to be friends, you just have to keep talking and see if you get along.
Friendship isn't something you can force.
It'd be different if you were
trying to go out with her, but...
Fujimiya-san isn't as cold as
everyone makes her out to be.
She's bright, loves talking to people,
and waits for you if you're late for lunch.
If everyone tried talking to her, I'm sure she'd be friends with everyone.
She's a nice and sweet girl.
So cheesy.
Wh-What's that supposed to mean?
Sorry. Don't worry about it.
Well, if that's the true Fujimiya,
then you're probably special to her.
You think?
I'd say you made a lot of progress.
Compared to how she was on Monday...
Shougo...
Since you've already come this far, you might as well go for it.
You're right.
Kaori? Dad bought a cake.
Okay. I'll come down later.
We aren't friends.
Fujimiya-san.
Wh-What is it?
I began to understand what Fujimiya-san meant.
There were no lies in her words.
The week we spent together was
completely gone from her memory.
The happiness we shared...
The connections we made...
All those would be reset on Monday, forcing them to be rebuilt.
Fujimiya-san knew about this, and kept herself from making friends.
Excuse me?
If all you're going to do is stand there, then...
Fujimiya-san!
But I knew.
I knew that she...
wanted to make friends, more than anybody else.
That's why I decided to say those words, however many times it took.
Please...
be my friend.
kaisatsu no mae tsunagu te to te
We're at the gate, holding hands.
itsumo no zawameki atarashii kaze
There's the usual bustle, but yet a new wind blows.
akaruku miokuru hazudatta no ni
I was supposed to see you off with a smile,
umaku waraezu ni kimi wo miteita
but here I stand, watching you and trying to hold back my tears.
kimi ga otona ni natteku sono kisetsu ga
When the time comes for you to grow up from the boy that you once were,
kanashii utatte afurenai you ni
rather than just stand here, singing this sad song,
saigo ni nanika kimi ni tsutaetakute
I want to say one last thing before you go away.
Read the diary
on top of the desk !
"sayonara" ni kawaru kotoba wo
I've been searching for the words to say...
boku wa sagashiteta
The words that mean goodbye.
How to spend time with friends.
how to spend time with friends.