You all brought your things, right?
Yup.
This goes without saying,
but we're running short on time.
We're gonna blaze through all of our summer vacation homework today!
Sure.
On the last day of summer vacation,
we decided to face the obstacle that was our remaining homework.
I already finished mine, though.
ashita mo kou shite kimi no soba ni ite
Tomorrow, I want to be with you,
onaji toki wo sugoshite itai na
so we can enjoy the same things we did today.
yukkuri peeji wo mekuru you ni mata
So once again, as we slowly flip these pages,
fuyashite yukou kimi to no shirushi
let's fill them with symbols of what we've done.
kotoba ni dekinai koto oshiyosete kiitemo
I 'm overcoming that which I can't put into words,
daijoubu kowagaranakute ii yo
but it's okay - don't be afraid, please.
kimi wo tsuresari ni yuku yo
I 'll take you with me,
hateshinai ano sora e to
to this boundless sky we'll never forget.
kanjiru mama ni egakou
So while these feelings remain,
ashita to iu niji no hashi wo
let's draw the rainbow bridge we call tomorrow.
kimi ga otoshita wasuremono
If you ever lose something dear,
boku ga kitto sagashidasu yo
I 'll try my best to find it for you,
nandodemo aitai kara
because seeing that smile on your face
taisetsu na kagayaku egao ni
is worth the world to me.
#9 - the final day with friends
We got ten whole pages of math...
That's asking way too much.
Now that I think about it, you procrastinate like this every year, don't you?
For your information,
this is what normal students do!
Let me guess, you finished yours on day one, right?
It'd be a pain to do it later.
How about you, Fujimiya-san?
I've been doing some of it every day, so I've only got a little bit left.
That's what I expected.
Coming from a real honor student
like you it doesn't bother me one bit.
Gee, sorry for being
a bothersome honor student.
I'm more worried about Yamagishi-san, though.
Oh, I've been waiting for you to ask.
Ta-dah.
I knew it...
When I called you yesterday, you didn't even know we had homework.
To be more precise,
I had no idea summer vacation was ending.
How have you gotten by until now?
I just copy someone's answers.
You haven't changed a bit...
Oh, right. You two've known
each other since you were kids, right?
Huh?
We have?
Didn't you two go to the same elementary school?
We did?
Yup.
Were we in the same class?
I only remember the fun things, so...
Oh, speaking of...
Did you remember something?
Yeah, there's a TV show that I want to watch. It's gonna start soon.
Do you want to watch downstairs?
Yippie!
Hey, Kaori-chan, why don't
you join me? It's a really fun show.
But our homework...
A little break never hurt anybody. Let's go.
A little break...
We haven't even started,
so how can you take a break?
I think I know the answer to this one,
but you aren't getting annoyed with Yamagishi-san, are you?
I don't really mind this much.
If you pay attention to how she acts,
it's obvious that she doesn't mean any harm.
You're surprisingly observant.
When all's said and done,
you really are looking out for her.
You really are a considerate guy, huh?
You, on the other hand, do annoy me.
What.
How's it going, Hase-kun? Any progress?
Not really.
If you're ever stuck, feel free to ask.
Sure.
You too, Saki-chan.
Yay!
Everyone needs a
reliable friend like you!
You, especially.
I've brought some tea and snacks.
Hello.
Sorry about the mess.
Don't worry about it. You guys are working on your homework, right?
Thanks for the food.
Want me to help out?
Huh?
Don't you think doing homework would make me feel young again? Just kidding.
Uh...
Oh, I baked cupcakes too, so come downstairs when you can.
Yay!
Well, take your time then.
Your mom's really friendly, isn't she?
You think so?
Well, you guys have fun.
Show some self-restraint.
Oh, I wanna sleep, too...
You too, Yamagishi-san?
What about your homework?
Oh, I nearly forgot.
Let's work on the homework, okay?
If we all work together,
we should finish it pretty quick.
I'm done!
That was fast. You really weren't kidding.
Yup. Need any help?
It's okay, I want to struggle a bit more.
But boy, do I suck at math...
You might just be overthinking it.
Math is like a puzzle, or a game.
There's one answer, and you're going on an adventure to find it.
But there's many different paths you can take,
so it's really rewarding when you reach the goal.
Sometimes, it takes a bit of insight.
Other times, you can craft your own method.
Math 2     Summer Assignment
Even the most convoluted methods can get you to the answer.
And however ugly your solution might be,
the fact that you've crafted it yourself is something to be proud of.
That's why I think problem solving is really important.
I'm sorry! I kinda went off...
Don't worry about it.
Kaori-chan, you really love math, don't you?
Let's take a break, shall we?
Wow, they look yummy!
I heard you guys were coming over,
so I woke up early and started making these.
Have as much as you want.
Would black tea be all right?
Let me help you.
Oh, I'll help out, too.
Can you take this over there, then?
Sure.
Saki-chan, there's a tea can in the top cabinet. Can you grab it?
Green Tea
This it?
Yeah. Thank you.
Was there anyone this tall in my elementary school class?
Green Tea
I'd assume that he
wasn't that tall back then...
Probably...
Those are photos of Kaori
when she was in elementary school.
We went on a family vacation over summer break.
I feel like Kaori's the same now as she was back then.
Kaori seems to be having fun every day now.
She says she can't wait for school to start.
If you told me six months ago,
I wouldn't believe you.
To think she'd be able to
make friends and have fun like this...
The power of friendship is amazing, isn't it?
I haven't really done much...
Oh, or are you two
more than just friends?
I'm kidding, it was a joke.
I still want to be your little sister, Kaori-chan.
I could have delicious cupcakes every day.
Today was just a special occasion.
There are extras, so feel free to have more.
All right! They're so good, I could gobble them all up!
If there are any left, can I take some home?
Of course.
Woohoo!
Oh, Hase-kun.
Do you want more tea?
Y-Yeah, sure.
How about you, Kiryuu-kun?
Sure.
Wait just a sec, okay?
I'm tagging along!
Am I really helping Fujimiya-san?
Huh?
We haven't really figured out anything
about Fujimiya-san's problem, have we?
It might even be impossible to solve.
It's the process that matters, right?
Huh?
Let me paraphrase Fujimiya a bit.
The joy of problem solving is in crafting your solution, not the answer itself.
If that's the case, I wouldn't worry about it.
I see.
You're right.
Hm? What's going on?
Huh?
Oh, we're just talking about
how great those cupcakes were.
You guys are exaggerating.
No, I'm serious!
I should head back home soon.
I said I'd be back by dinner...
Can you finish your homework by yourself?
Well, it isn't due on the first day back,
so I'll figure something out by then.
If you say so...
I've got some shopping to do,
so I should head out soon, too.
You too, Shougo?
I've only got one page left...
Well, you can finish that before you leave.
I'll help you out.
See you tomorrow at school.
Yup!
It's just the two of us now, huh?
Y-Yeah...
I'm this way, so...
Oh, one sec.
What's this?
For the math homework.
All the formulae and the answers.
When did you do this?
I was bored and had nothing else to do just now.
Huh?
I feel like something like this happened before...
When I was in elementary school...
there was a notebook in my shoe locker.
I always wondered who did that.
That was you wasn't it, Kiryuu-kun?
But why?
No real reason.
Back then, people were always teasing you for being dumb,
and you never even tried to change the way things were.
All I wanted was to give you a push in the right direction.
You know, that was the first time anyone did something like that for my sake.
It made me really happy.
I didn't know who it was,
but I always dreamed of having someone who could take care of me.
I think I messed up on the execution.
See you.
Kiryuu-kun.
Thanks for this.
And for what you did
in elementary school.
I'm looking forward to the future.
Moron.
I'm finally done!
Good job.
Having you give me some pointers
when I got stuck was really nice.
That's good to hear.
I hope I'm being helpful to you...
You totally are!
I mean, you've saved me so many times.
Oh, I'll write this down in the diary.
"Hase-kun did his best and finished his summer homework today."
I made a lot of memories this summer...
It's all thanks to you, Hase-kun.
No, I should be thanking you.
Oh, that reminds me.
How have you been able
to remember me, recently?
I know it's kind of a strange question,
and it's not like I'm expecting you to have an answer.
I don't know exactly why.
But it feels like, ever since I met you,
something inside me has changed.
Until recently, I had completely given up on making friends.
In fact, I was afraid of making friends.
Since my memories reset every week,
I figured I wouldn't be able to make any friends,
I'd be better off not having any at all.
But...
Since I met you, I've realized that there are people who will stay by your side, no matter what.
When I read the diary, I know who you are, and I know you're someone I can trust.
It's made my life a lot easier.
I'm less afraid of making friends,
and it's all thanks to you.
Thank you so much.
Fujimiya-san...
Oh, if you want, you should stay for dinner!
I'll go tell Mom.
You don't have to—
S-Sorry! Are you okay—
Fujimiya-san...
Got it.
There was a speck of dust in your hair.
I heard a loud noise. Is everything all right...
Sorry for interrupting!
You've got the wrong idea!
That was an honest-to-god accident!
It's fine. You're high schoolers,
and you must be having a lot of accidents.
I consider myself to be pretty
understanding about these things.
No, seriously, you've got it wrong!
I totally get it.
I tripped, and then Fujimiya-san fell down.
In any case, it's not what you think it is!
Good morning!
Fujimiya-san!
We don't normally see each other in the morning.
We really don't. This might be the first time.
I'm so excited. I think something good will happen today!
Let's go.
Something good happened already...
Hase-kun!
Attendance
Log
We're gonna switch it up a bit by changing seats.
We'll do it by lottery, so come up
and grab your new spot.
Teacher!
I want a spot in the back!
Yeah, and so does everybody else.
Gold star for being so honest, though.
Idiot.
Well, you guys figure out your new seats.
I'm gonna drop by the faculty office real quick.
It's not like I want to do anything wrong,
like take naps in class or eat lunch early.
If I'm in the back, I can look at Fujimiya-san.
That's wrong in so many ways, I don't even...
It's a miracle...
See? Something good happened.
Y-Yeah.
You seem happy.
I've got Ai-chan behind me,
so I should be fine this semester.
I can get help from her.
Hey, I can hear you, you know!
Unlike me, Ai can be pretty strict.
I'm worried for Saki.
Why are you painting me as the villain?
Sit down, guys.
Quick announcement.
We've got a transfer student.
Come in.
Kujou Hajime
This is Kujou. He's from Hokkaido.
The name's Kujou Hajime. Nice to meet you.
You're fine with any seat, right?
Yup.
Then just grab the one in the back.
Wait, are you Fujimiya Kaori?
How do you know my name?
Excuse me? What's with that?
Do you not remember me at all?
I'm sorry, I...
I guess it makes sense.
You were the one who broke our promise.
Guess that shows how meaningless I was to you.
Huh?
You traitor.
Hajime-kun...
Fujimiya-san!
Are you okay?
Fujimiya-san! Fujimiya-san!
Fujimiya-san.
You surprised us all, fainting like that...
But it's good to see you're awake.
Yamagishi-san was worried, too.
Shougo was too, though he'd never admit it.
I was worried to the point
where I couldn't focus in class.
Thank you for worrying about me.
However, I don't seem to recall your name...
I'm sorry. I see that you
were worried about me,
but I'm not very good
with names in general...
Are you okay?
Wh-Why...
Fujimiya-san?
What are you doing?
On that day, Fujimiya-san
forgot every one of her memories of me.
kaisatsu no mae tsunagu te to te
We're at the gate, holding hands.
itsumo no zawameki atarashii kaze
There's the usual bustle, but yet a new wind blows.
akaruku miokuru hazudatta no ni
I was supposed to see you off with a smile,
umaku waraezu ni kimi wo miteita
but here I stand, watching you and trying to hold back my tears.
kimi ga otona ni natteku sono kisetsu ga
When the time comes for you to grow up from the boy that you once were,
kanashii utatte afurenai you ni
rather than just stand here, singing this sad song,
saigo ni nanika kimi ni tsutaetakute
I want to say one last thing before you go away.
Read the diary
on top of the desk !
"sayonara" ni kawaru kotoba wo
I've been searching for the words to say...
boku wa sagashiteta
The words that mean goodbye.
Friends and friends.
friends and friends.