Imamura, Shimada, Sone, Takasawa,
Hase, Mizoguchi, and Yamagishi.
If you heard your name, you better get
a higher grade on tomorrow's make-up test.
Otherwise, I'll share your answers with the class.
Got it?
You're kidding...
Please help me, Fujimiya-san!
Can you teach me some math after school?
U-Uh, sure, if you insist...
For real?
What kind of crap did you
put on your test, anyway?
Hey, at least I tried to answer the questions correctly!
Maybe you should let him share your answers with everyone. Nice little shock treatment.
Well, easy for you to say.
I'd rather die than let people see my answers.
Well I don't have much to do today, so I can do it.
You're a life-saver. Thanks.
Where should we study, though?
We can't be too loud in the library...
It's probably best to stay on campus though.
How about my place?
ashita mo kou shite kimi no soba ni ite
Tomorrow, I want to be with you,
onaji toki wo sugoshite itai na
so we can enjoy the same things we did today.
yukkuri peeji wo mekuru you ni mata
So once again, as we slowly flip these pages,
fuyashite yukou kimi to no shirushi
let's fill them with symbols of what we've done.
kotoba ni dekinai koto oshiyosete kitemo
I 'm overcoming that which I can't put into words,
daijoubu kowagaranakute ii yo
but it's okay - don't be afraid, please.
kimi wo tsuresari ni yuku yo
I 'll take you with me,
hateshinai ano sora e to
to this boundless sky we'll never forget.
kanjiru mama ni egakou
So while these feelings remain,
ashita to iu niji no hashi wo
let's draw the rainbow bridge we call tomorrow.
kimi ga otoshita wasuremono
If you ever lose something dear,
boku ga kitto sagashidasu yo
I 'll try my best to find it for you,
nandodemo aitai kara
because seeing that smile on your face
taisetsu na kagayaku egao ni
is worth the world to me.
#6 - mothers of friends
Is something the matter?
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but you said "my place", right?
Yeah. If we study at my house, we won't
have to worry about bothering other people.
A-At your house?
Yep.
I'd really love to, but...
This guy's saying he doesn't want to go.
Why not?
I'll totally go! I really want to go to your place!
Oh, good.
What do I do, Shougo?
I think it might be a bit risky,
if the two of us are alone in her room...
Are you planning something?
S-Studying, that's all!
It's always been a dream
of mine to invite friends over.
I'm so excited!
Look, she's so pure and innocent.
Wh-What do I do, Shougo...
I think you really should come with us!
Man up a bit and go for it.
I-I guess he's right...
Kaori-chan...
Apparently I've gotta do well on this next test or something.
Teach me math, please...
Are they from our class?
I'm so excited to visit your house!
Do you guys have tatami mats or hardwood floors?
I was so close to being all alone with Fujimiya-san.
Why do I have to come too?
That's my house.
It's huge.
Man, I'm getting nervous...
It's a little late to be asking, but
isn't it rude of us to just barge in?
More than a little.
I'm always telling my mom about you guys, so it should be okay.
I'm home!
Mom, I brought some friends over!
Really?
Sure doesn't sound okay.
Kaori, you should have told me earlier that you were bringing—
Oh, my...
This is my mom.
N-Nice to meet you!
Hello.
Thanks for having us over...
These are my classmates—
Should I bake a cake? Do you guys like cake?
Yay!
I love cake.
Please don't go out of your way for us.
A cake would take too long to bake, wouldn't it?
I'll go make some drinks, then.
Mind if I introduce you later?
Sure.
Well, my room's on the second floor, so let's go upstairs.
This is my room.
You've got a bed!
How nice...
It's nice and fluffy...
Sit wherever you like.
Show some restraint, you guys.
Why should I?
Now I see.
See what?
Yuuki Hase-kun, from the
same class, is my
Friend
Read the diary
on top of the desk!
same class, is my
Friend
Read the diary
on top of the desk!
same class, is my
Friend
Read the diary
same class, is my
Friend
Read the diary
same class, is my
on top of the desk!
Don't look!
same class, is my
Read the diary
on top of the desk!
same class, is my
Read the diary
on top of the desk!
Yuuki Hase-kun, from the
same class, is my
Friend
Read the diary
on top of the desk!
same class, is my
Friend
I see...
So that's how you remember to read the diary.
Wait, then what about the time you lost it?
Somehow it had fallen off without me realizing it.
That makes sense.
Well, let's get started, shall we?
Sure.
I'll try my best to help you two, okay?
We should be the ones trying our best...
We'll try our best and get a good score. Right, Yamagishi-san?
Kaori-chan, can I read this?
Did you forget why we're here?
Shougo, say something.
Huh? You say something?
Besides, I don't need to study.
That's true, but...
Tomorrow's make-up covers the same
material that was on the last quiz, right?
I think so.
All right, let's go over that one, then.
You aced it?
Class
Name
Fujimiya
Please simplify the following expressions.
Amazing.
Kaori-chan sure is smart.
And what'd you guys get?
I regret bringing you along.
I forgot.
And for this problem, you use this formula, right?
Yep, that's right.
Same for this one?
Yeah. These two formulas are actually related.
Wait, what formula is that?
First I've seen of it.
Well, do you remember this one, then?
Who knows...
You should have learned it in your first year...
I don't think my class covered it.
Me neither!
What have you two been doing, then?
Well, I haven't had that much trouble with math...
When can I go home?
I've made some tea, so why not take a break?
Yay.
I'm sorry they're not home-made.
Melon bread! I like melon bread too!
It's so good!
Mom, this is Yamagishi-san, Kiryuu-kun, and Hase-kun.
I apologize again for coming over all of a sudden.
So you're Hase-kun.
Y-Yes.
I'm always causing trouble for your daughter...
Speak a little more politely, will you?
No, thank you. I'm always hearing stories about you from Kaori.
Really?
Yep. I've heard countless stories of you
loving sweet omelettes, or failing at math.
Wow, she knows you well.
Kaori-chan, you sure talk about Hase-kun a lot...
Huh?
Well, I'd hate to distract you.
I'll let you guys focus on studying.
Thanks, Mom.
Now that we're done snacking, let's go for the home stretch.
Hey, mind if I use the bathroom?
It's at the bottom of the stairs.
Thanks.
All right, let's get started, Saki-chan.
Eating kinda made me all sleepy.
Huh?
Calm down.
Am I really that scary?
Uh...
Hase-kun's really easy to talk to,
so it makes you seem scarier in comparison.
Sorry about that.
Huh?
What did you do to her?
Nothing. Obviously.
Uh, it's my fault! I was—
Attention, please...
The "Get Kaori-chan and Kiryuu-kun to be Friends" plan
is now in action.
Uh, what do you mean, Yamagishi-san?
Kaori-chan seems to be scared of talking to Kiryuu-kun, so I thought I'd try and fix that.
Wait, you were listening, Saki-chan?
Yup.
I mean, I can understand. You do look pretty scary, and you never smile.
Either she gets used to it, or we give up on it.
For starters, let's try smiling!
Smile...
Stop laughing.
Sorry.
Seems like you'll just have to get used to it...
Next, let's try talking to each other!
Huh?
Would it be wrong for me to step in and help her?
Very wrong.
Do you like studying? Or do you hate it?
I don't care either way.
W-We've had some nice weather lately!
Sure.
I think the guy's the problem here.
I'm inclined to agree with you.
The friendship plan is on hold.
Kiryuu-kun, you're the problem here.
Don't worry about it, Kaori-chan.
I don't think you need to be friends with him.
Hold on.
I might be scared of him now,
but I'd like to be friends with him at some point.
After all, he's Hase-kun's friend, too.
I don't see why anything needs to change.
I mean, I always end up hanging out with you guys. Get a clue already.
I hope we continue getting along, Kiryuu-kun.
Sure.
You guys should stay for dinner!
Nah, I think we should get going now.
Oh, I forgot my phone.
I forgot where your room is, too.
I'll show you, Saki-chan.
Take this, Hase-kun.
Read it later.
Sorry to keep you waiting...
All right, later.
Yep, today was a lot of fun.
See you tomorrow.
I live this way. Bye-bye.
Fujimiya's mom gave you that, right?
What's it say?
After school tomorrow,
please come to the park
There's something I need to tell you.
Fujimiya's Mom
This is...
She wants to talk...
It's probably about Fujimiya-san, isn't it?
What do I do... I'm so nervous...
Just say something good.
Such as?
"I'll protect your daughter!" or whatever.
A-Are you crazy?
If it's about Fujimiya, it's one of two things.
Two things?
It'll either be about her memories,
or asking you to stop talking to her.
Wanna come with me?
Nope.
Figured as much...
I wouldn't be too worried.
She seemed like a nice mother, after all.
Yeah, but...
What?
I'm thirsty.
The vending machine's over there.
And I didn't bring any cash.
Ah, jeez. Just ask me to spot you!
Throw
away
your
trash
Throw
away
your
trash
For the record, I don't owe you anything.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm thankful to you for always hearing me out.
Throw
away
your
trash
Throw
away
your
trash
When is it?
She didn't write a specific time.
I'm talking about your make-up test, stupid.
Hase-kun.
I'm sorry for being late!
Yeah, I had a make-up test today, so...
No, I'm just glad you could
make it on such short notice.
Here, have a seat.
Thank you.
I can't talk to you if you're way over there.
Come closer.
It's okay. I left a note for Kaori, saying that I'd be a bit late.
But if people saw me like this with a young man like you,
they might think I'm having an affair!
Excuse me?
I'm joking.
I should've guessed.
Anyway, you had
something to talk about?
Before that, may I ask you something?
Sure.
Why did you decide to talk to Kaori?
Uh, well...
Being her friend can be a lot of work.
Is it what I think it is?
Uh, is this related to what you wanted to talk about?
I called you out here because I wanted to tell you what I know about her memories.
You know the gist of
her condition already, right?
Yeah.
I'm still not entirely sure as to why her memories of her friends go away.
However, I do know when it all began.
When she was in sixth grade, she got involved in a traffic accident.
According to witnesses, she tried to cross the street, even though the sign was red...
Bicycles and Pedestrians only
She was hit by a car.
She was taken to the hospital, unconscious, and she remained that way for several days.
And when she came to...
Oh, Mom! You know—
Who are they?
What do you mean, who?
They're your friends, aren't they?
Friends?
According to the doctors, there's nothing wrong with her brain.
To
Kaori-chan
from your classmates
Come on, don't give up. Takahashi
Everyone's waiting~!
Get well, and we'll do our part!!! Kenta
Don't give up  Hisaru
Get better soon. Jun
Don't give up. Hirogi
Get well. Ryuu
Are you okay?
We're waiting for
\you at school, okay. Yumi
We're all
worried about you. Don't give up.
Youko
Get well soon. Tetsuya
We're waiting
for you at
h
school! Mutsuki
We're waiting
for you.
Hirokazu
Get out of the hospital soon. Miyo
Get well soon.
Fight! Mao
Get better
soon. Naoki?
Come back to school soon.
orikao
Let's play!!
Kakeru
When the car hit her, it seemed she had a minor concussion.
But apparently, that's not why she can't remember her friends.
There's a different reason?
In her mind, there might be some emotional weight associated with having friends.
Emotional...
But I don't understand it at all.
When she was young, she had a lot of friends.
She'd make friends with people in an instant,
and she had a lot of fun with them, too.
She would talk about them every day.
Those stories were always fun to hear.
So it's difficult for me to imagine that
there was a problem with her friends...
Much less it all being an act.
Um, when she got into the accident, was she by herself?
Yes. She ran across the street by herself.
I believe that happened on a Sunday evening...
Oh, I think she had left to go meet up with a close friend of hers.
A close friend...
Yeah...
She always seemed to be happy when she left the house.
So why would something like that...
Oh, I'm sorry for making you
remember something so unpleasant.
Don't be. It's Kaori who's suffering, after all.
Every time she tries to remember her friends, I can see her struggle.
She's probably unconsciously keeping herself from remembering them.
Sorry about all this. It's a heavy subject, I know.
No, I'm glad I came.
It's really sad that I can't help her, even though I'm her parent.
But I'm happy enough that Kaori's still here.
You can't change anything if you're stuck in the past, anyway.
You're right.
So, have you two held hands yet?
W-We're just friends!
Anyway...
I should be heading back now.
I imagine Kaori's getting hungry.
Thank you for today.
No, thank you.
Please continue to look after Kaori.
Of course.
What can I do...?
Kaori? Can you do these?
I hope Hase-kun's make-up test went okay...
That'd be nice.
Oh yeah, Hase-kun and Saki-chan said they wanted to study during lunch, but Saki-chan...
So, how'd it go yesterday?
Good morning, Kaori-chan...
G-Good morning.
Morning.
Morning, Fujimiya-san.
Good morning.
Good morning, Fujimiya-san.
We're allowed to talk in the classroom now, right?
Yep. Good morning, Hase-kun.
Class
Name
Hase
Sweet!
Good job passing your make-up test.
Just barely, though.
It's all because of you. Thanks.
I need to thank you, too.
I was kinda shocked when you said
"good morning" in front of everyone, but...
I was really happy.
Really?
Yep.
There's one other thing.
Whenever I read my diary, there's one thing I see every week.
That so?
What do you think it is?
Hm, let's see...
"Would you be my friend again?"
Say, Hase-kun, can I look forward to you asking me that question again next week?
Of course.
I thought I learned something about her past, but it's still so mysterious.
Sometimes, I think that
Fujimiya-san's condition is a pain.
But even so, if it means bringing back her lost smile,
Yuuki Hase-kun, from the
same class, is my
then I'll muster the courage to become her friend.
on top of the desk!
Friend
As many times as necessary.
Yuuki Hase-kun, from the
same class, is my
Friend
Read the diary
on top of the desk!
same class, is my
Friend
Read the diary
on top of the desk!
same class, is my
Friend
Read the diary
on top of the desk!
same class, is my
Friend
Read the diary
on top of the desk!
same class, is my
Read the diary
on top of the desk!
same class, is my
Read the diary
on top of the desk!
same class, is my
Read the diary
on top of the desk!
same class, is my
Read the diary
on top of the desk!
kaisatsu no mae tsunagu te to te
We're at the gate, holding hands.
itsumo no zawameki atarashii kaze
There's the usual bustle, but yet a new wind blows.
akaruku miokuru hazudatta no ni
I was supposed to see you off with a smile,
umaku waraezu ni kimi wo miteita
but here I stand, watching you and trying to hold back my tears.
kimi ga otona ni natteku sono kisetsu ga
When the time comes for you to grow up from the boy that you once were,
kanashii utatte afurenai you ni
rather than just stand here, singing this sad song,
saigo ni nanika kimi ni tsutaetakute
I want to say one last thing before you go away.
Read the diary
on top of the desk !
"sayonara" ni kawaru kotoba wo
I've been searching for the words to say...
boku wa sagashiteta
The words that mean goodbye.
friends that go "ah". friends that go "whew".
Friends That Go "Ah". Friends That Go "Whew".