On rainy days, instead of eating
on the roof, we'd eat on the stairs.
This tastes great!
Guess we should head back.
Yeah.
It was an unspoken rule that we'd
go back to the classroom separately.
Fujimiya-san.
Are you really friends with Kiryuu-kun?
There's a rumor flying around.
For reals?
W-Well...
Dude, Kiryuu, are you friends with Fujimiya?
I guess?
So the rumor was true!
She's friends with Kiryuu!
Seriously?
I hate you right now.
ashita mo kou shite kimi no soba ni ite
Tomorrow, I want to be with you,
onaji toki wo sugoshite itai na
so we can enjoy the same things we did today.
yukkuri peeji wo mekuru you ni mata
So once again, as we slowly flip these pages,
fuyashite yukou kimi to no shirushi
let's fill them with symbols of what we've done.
kotoba ni dekinai koto oshiyosete kitemo
I 'm overcoming that which I can't put into words,
daijoubu kowagaranakute ii yo
but it's okay - don't be afraid, please.
kimi wo tsuresari ni yuku yo
I 'll take you with me,
hateshinai ano sora e to
to this boundless sky we'll never forget.
kanjiru mama ni egakou
So while these feelings remain,
ashita to iu niji no hashi wo
let's draw the rainbow bridge we call tomorrow.
kimi ga otoshita wasuremono
If you ever lose something dear,
boku ga kitto sagashidasu yo
I 'll try my best to find it for you,
nandodemo aitai kara
because seeing that smile on your face
taisetsu na kagayaku egao ni
is worth the world to me.
#4 - a fight between friends
I was friends with her first.
So why are you getting all the attention for being her friend?
Hell if I know.
When did you two get so close, anyway?
You think we're close?
I'm not saying that you shouldn't talk to her when I'm not around.
It's just kind of annoying that you're the first one everyone thinks of when it comes to her friends.
It makes me wonder what's been happening behind my back.
Besides, she actually remembers you, which means—
You're jealous, aren't you?
Don't just say it!
Girls don't like clingy guys.
If you're gonna bite my head off,
you should've just said that you were her friend too.
Sure, but I'm waiting for the right time.
And when's that gonna be?
Keep saying that and nothing's gonna change.
I guess you're right...
Fujimiya-san!
Good morning. How are you doing?
Fine, thanks.
Where's Kiryuu-kun?
Did you need him?
Rumors about us have been going around,
so I thought he might be mad...
I wouldn't worry about it.
If you say so.
Man, eating a hand-made lunch on the roof rocks.
Especially since we had to eat
in the stairwell all week because of the rain.
I've been wondering...
Why do you have a key to the roof?
Well...
Math Storage Room
Fujimiya, could you draft a few problems for the quiz?
But...
I'll lend you this.
It's for the door to the roof.
The roof?
Yep. The roof's pretty sweet.
It's a great place to relax.
I'm not sure if that was very responsible of him...
I think he was just looking out for me.
Wow.
I guess even Inoue's got some good in him.
You're a good person too, Hase-kun.
I've realized what it's like to have fun at school.
Until I became friends with you, I tried not to feel anything at all.
Fujimiya-san...
My memories still haven't returned,
but recently, I've been enjoying school a lot more.
Hey, that's a huge improvement!
Looks like the diary works after all.
Yeah, the diary's part of it.
But honestly, thank you for being my friend.
It's nothing.
Thanks to you, I was able to become friends with Kiryuu-kun too.
Oh, did you hear?
That seal came back to the river.
R-Really?
Everyone was gawking at it
on their way to school this morning.
I take the train, so...
Your house is on the other side of the river, isn't it?
Yep. First right after the bridge.
Hey, I might be able to see the seal from my place.
I'd like to see it too.
Why don't we look for it after school?
We can't leave together, though...
But if Kiryuu-kun's with us...
You two always walk home together, right?
Well, yeah.
Speaking of, he really does
sleep through all his classes.
But when the teacher calls on him,
he still always gets the right answer.
I think that's amazing.
It feels like Kiryuu-kun can do anything.
It's still kind of awkward when it's just me and him,
since I don't have the courage to talk to him,
but I can see that he's a good person.
That's why I want to be friends with him.
Fujimiya-san?
Yeah?
Why do you keep talking about him?
What do you mean?
Fujimiya-san, are you...
Huh?
Are you in love with him?
Me? With Kiryuu-kun?
That's why you keep talking about him, right?
That's not it!
It's okay, you can tell me the truth.
I am!
He's your friend, right? That's why I—
That's why it bothers me!
I'm bothered because we're friends.
It's making me all gloomy.
Can't we just talk about ourselves like before?
I didn't mean to...
I'm not saying you can't talk about him.
I just thought things were getting a bit boring.
Instead of him, I'd like to talk about you—
You idiot!
What did I do?
You're right. I'm boring, aren't I?
No! I wasn't saying that you're boring!
I was saying that talking about him was—
It's okay. It's the truth.
Fujimiya-san? U-Um...
But you have no idea
why I talk about him, Hase-kun!
Fujimiya-san!
Don't follow me!
Tell our teacher that I felt sick and left early.
Please?
What's wrong with me?
Please
Wait
Why...
Sorry! You okay?
Yeah. It was my fault.
I'm really sorry.
Well, here we go...
I'm an idiot.
I made her mad.
What do I do?
Today's Friday, too...
Your first fight, huh?
You're back early.
Wait, did you forget your umbrella?
Yeah.
You better get changed.
Let me get you a towel...
It's okay. I've got one in my room.
Make sure to dry off completely. You don't want to catch a cold.
I just wanted to spend my time chatting with Hase-kun.
Friendships sure are difficult...
Yuuki Hase-kun, from the
same class, is my
on top of the desk!
The diary...
Friend
same class, is my
on top of the desk!
Friend
same class, is my
Read the diary
on top of the desk!
Friend
same class, is my
Read the diary
on top of the desk!
same class, is my
Read the diary
on top of the desk!
same class, is my
Read the diary
on top of the desk!
Friend
Read the diary
on top of the desk!
Friend
Read the diary
on top of the desk!
Friend
same class, is my
Yuuki Hase-kun, from the
Friend
Read the diary
on top of the desk!
Yuuki Hase-kun, from the
same class, is my
Friend
Read the diary
on top of the desk!
Yuuki Hase-kun, from the
same class, is my
Friend
Read the diary
on top of the desk!
Yuuki Hase-kun, from the
same class, is my
Friend
Read the diary
on top of the desk!
Yuuki Hase-kun, from the
same class, is my
Friend
Read the diary
on top of the desk!
Yuuki Hase-kun, from the
same class, is my
Friend
Read the diary
Yuuki Hase-kun, from the
same class, is my
Friend
Read the diary
Yuuki Hase-kun, from the
same class, is my
Friend
Yuuki Hase-kun, from the
same class, is my
Friend
Yuuki Hase-kun, from the
same class, is my
tuesday
What should I do?
Fujimiya-san's gone today, too!
According to Inoue,
she's been stuck in bed since Friday.
Probably just a cold or something.
It's my fault.
How'd you get that idea?
When she left, it was raining outside,
and it's my fault that she left in the first place.
Man, what should I do?
Just apologize when she comes back.
But...
Besides, it's not like she's gonna remember fighting with you.
You should be able
to make up pretty easily.
Ideally, but...
Come with me, Fujimiya-san.
What's your deal?
I'm sorry!
For just now, and for Friday too.
What happened on Friday was entirely my fault.
Oh, I'm Hase Yuuki.
You read the diary,
so you should know who I am.
I'm really sorry.
Excuse me?
I don't know a Hase Yuuki.
Fujimiya-san? You're joking, right?
It's me, Hase Yuuki—
I'm telling you, I don't know you.
But the diary! Didn't you read it?
A diary? I don't keep one.
Besides, how would you know if I kept one or not?
But I do know! We've been friends for over a month!
That's impossible.
After all,
the only person I talk to
at school is Kiryuu-kun.
Dragging me out like this...
You're the creepiest person I've ever met.
Wait, hold on. You don't remember me, nor the diary?
I do not.
Now, please leave me alone.
How'd it go?
Here we go again.
Can you skip first period with me?
Time for class.
You're gonna be sleeping
through it anyway! Help me out!
I don't want things to end like this.
All right.
Fujimiya doesn't remember the diary at all?
Seems like it.
She was treating me like she did before we became friends.
Well, of course she's gonna forget some stuff.
How did she usually read the diary?
Well...
I'm not really sure about the details,
but she used to read it before coming to school.
But not today.
She doesn't want to be my friend anymore.
Really?
She hated me so much before losing
her memories that she threw away the diary.
She threw it away, huh?
What if she just lost it?
Lost it?
What,
do you think Fujimiya's so temperamental
that she'd throw away that
precious diary over a little argument?
No, she wouldn't have thrown it away.
She had it at lunch on Friday.
Which means that on the way back...
I'm gonna go look for it!
Hey, dude!
Fujimiya, got a sec?
Kiryuu-kun!
So you remember me, huh?
Huh?
Just talking to myself.
No omelettes today, huh?
Omelettes?
You honestly don't remember?
What?
Anyway, you usually make your own lunches, right?
My mom made mine today,
since I'm getting over a cold.
I see.
I feel like we ate lunch together,
sometime last week.
Boy, that's vague.
S-Sorry!
I'm not mad at you or anything.
Do you remember what happened last week, after school?
Last week, after school?
I remember you going back to the classroom for me to get something that I forgot...
Which was?
Huh? What was it?
Figures.
I'm forgetting something, aren't I?
Yep. After I told you not to.
After you...
Don't force yourself to remember it.
Last week, you forgot your—
Don't tell me!
I need to remember on my own.
I feel like I'm forgetting something important.
I wonder where it could be...
Someone's looking for it right now.
Huh? Could that be the person from this morning?
Yep. If you see him, can you talk to him?
It'll totally make his day.
But...
Please?
It wasn't on the train, either.
All that's left...
Talk to him.
U-Um...
Are you making food for your friend again?
My friend?
Friend...
I guess Hase's the only one absent.
Midorikawa High
Wh-What are you looking for, so frantically?
Fujimiya-san.
Why are you pushing yourself so hard?
Both yesterday and today...
You've even ruined your clothes.
Because it's important.
Who are you even doing this for?
Is this for yourself?
Or...
I think it's a bit of both.
I know there's something
important that I'm forgetting.
But I don't know what it is.
Could it be related to what you're looking for?
I don't know.
I hope it is, at least.
L-Let me help you!
It's dangerous. Don't worry about it.
But...
Instead, can I ask you something?
Is it possible that you threw away the important thing?
I'm not sure what this important thing is.
But I'd never intentionally throw away something so important.
That's good enough for me.
Thanks for the chat.
Hase-kun!
Are you okay?
Y-Yeah.
Did you just call me Hase-kun?
Huh? I... what?
Found it!
Thank goodness! I finally found it!
Here.
Aren't you gonna look inside?
No, I don't need to.
I know that this is what I was missing.
Your clothes are gonna get dirty!
You're one to talk.
Your hands are even cut from all the grass...
From the bottom of my heart... Thank you.
He owes me one.
I'm amazed you realized
that I dropped it by the river.
Well, it was the only place I could
think of after looking everywhere else.
What were you doing there, anyway?
I can't remember very well,
but I feel like I talked about going there.
I see.
Fighting and making up...
It's not much, but I'm glad we were able to do it.
All right, see you tomorrow.
Wait, Fujimiya-san!
I forgot something!
My name's Hase Yuuki.
Would you be my friend?
In the end, the fight brought us closer together.
And for that, I was happy.
kaisatsu no mae tsunagu te to te
We're at the gate, holding hands.
itsumo no zawameki atarashii kaze
There's the usual bustle, but yet a new wind blows.
akaruku miokuru hazudatta no ni
I was supposed to see you off with a smile,
umaku waraezu ni kimi wo miteita
but here I stand, watching you and trying to hold back my tears.
kimi ga otona ni natteku sono kisetsu ga
When the time comes for you to grow up from the boy that you once were,
kanashii utatte afurenai you ni
rather than just stand here, singing this sad song,
saigo ni nanika kimi ni tsutaetakute
I want to say one last thing before you go away.
Read the diary
on top of the desk !
"sayonara" ni kawaru kotoba wo
I've been searching for the words to say...
boku wa sagashiteta
The words that mean goodbye.
A new friend.
a new friend.